,org,loc,resolvedWith,sentences
0,ABG Container Handling Private Limited,['Mumbai'],['ABG CONTAINER HANDLING PRIVATE LIMITED'],"['<ORG>Pacific International Lines</ORG> (<ORG>PIL</ORG>) M.V. Kota Nabil made a maiden call at <MISC>Dakshin Bharat Gateway Terminal</MISC> (DBGT) in Tuticorin after <MISC>Chairman</MISC> of <ORG>VOC Port Trust A. Chandrabose</ORG> formally inaugurated the cargo operations at the DBGT on Sunday.This maiden call of PILs vessel heralded the opening of the DBGT for operations for the vessels using ships gear.<MISC>Dakshin Bharat Gateway Terminal</MISC> is a special purpose vehicle incorporated by <ORG>ABG Container Handling Private Limited</ORG>, <LOC>Mumbai</LOC>, and is the concessionaire implementing this <ORG>Private-Public Partnership</ORG> project at Berth Number 8 of <ORG>VOC Port Trust</ORG> in Tuticorin.The DBGT has appointed a subsidiary, <ORG>Bollore Africa Logistics (BAL)</ORG>, as its <MISC>Management Contractor</MISC>, who will be responsible for project implementation, including operations, maintenance, commercial/marketing and day-to-day running of this container terminal.This modern container terminal is expected to be completely ready for commercial operations next year. This is BALs first foray into the container terminal business in <MISC>India</MISC>.Bollor <MISC>Africa</MISC> Logistics is the leading integrated <MISC>logistics network</MISC> on the African continent and the leading operator of public-private partnerships in the port and rail sectors, having its presence in 55 countries.Incorporated in 1967, <ORG>Pacific International Lines</ORG> is ranked 16th amongst the top containership operators in the world, offering <MISC>container liner services</MISC> and <MISC>multi-purpose services</MISC> at over 500 locations in 100 countries, according to an official statement from the <ORG>VOC Port Trust</ORG> said.']"
1,ACE Designers Limited,['Bangalore'],['ACE DESIGNERS LIMITED'],"['<ORG><MISC>SALEMDhirajlal Gandhi College of Tech</ORG>nology</MISC>: Seminar on 5s and its applications by K. Amul Chander, Human Resource Department, <ORG>ACE Designers Limited</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, <PER>Dhirajlal A. Gandhi</PER>, <MISC>Chairman</MISC> of the <ORG>college</ORG> presides, 10.30 <ORG>a.m.<MISC>AVS Engineering C</ORG>ollege</MISC> and <ORG><MISC>AVS College of Tech</ORG>nology</MISC>: Inauguration of first year B.E. classes and distribution of merit scholarships, <PER>K.R.S.R. Krishna</PER>, <MISC>Vice President and General Manager</MISC>, <ORG>Petrofac Engineering Services India Private Limited</ORG>, Chennai, chief guest, 9.30 <ORG>a.m.<MISC>Thiagarajar Polytechnic C</ORG>ollege</MISC> and ARK Technosolution and Helios: Workshop on <ORG>National</ORG> Robotics Championship 2015, <PER>Harshal P. Joshi</PER>, <MISC>Design Engineer and Head</MISC> <PER>Trainer</PER> of the company, introductory note, <PER>Thyagu Valliappa</PER>, <MISC>Vice Chairman, Sona Gr<ORG>oup</MISC></ORG> of Institutions, inaugural address, 10 <ORG>a.m.Knowledge Business School</ORG>: Management Development Programme on Self Actualisation, 9.30 a.m.Holy Angels Matriculation <ORG>Higher Secondary School</ORG>: Annual Sports Meet, A. Amalraj, <ORG>City Police</ORG> <MISC>Commissioner, chief</MISC> guest, R.S.D. Wahida Banu, Principal, <ORG><MISC>Government College of Engin</ORG>eering</MISC>, presides, 8.45 a.m.Sri Ramakrishna Mission Ashrama: Srimat Swami Gautamanandaji Maharaj visits Ashrama, Spiritual Initiation,7 p.m.Arulmigu Periya Mariamman Tirukovil, Kottai: Adi Festival, 10.30 a.m.Yogoda Satsanga Soceity of <MISC>India</MISC>: Discourse by Swami Suthananda Giri, <MISC>Tirumalai Ammal Marriage Hall</MISC>, 6 p.m.<ORG>Rotary Club</ORG> of Salem: Weekly Meeting, D. Thirunavukkarasu speaks on Vision 2020, <MISC>Rotary Hall</MISC>, 6.30 <ORG>p.m.NAMAKK<MISC>ALMahendra Engineering College</ORG></MISC>: Guest lecture on <MISC>Data Mining</MISC> and Data Warehousing by <PER>N. Balaji</PER>, <MISC>Professor and Head, Department</MISC> of IT, <MISC><ORG>KLN College of Engine</MISC>ering</ORG>, Sivagangai, 10 <MISC><ORG>a.m.Vivekananda Institute of Engine</MISC>ering and Technology for Women</ORG>, Tiruchengode: Workshop on Digital <MISC>Image Processing</MISC>, <PER>S. Mahesh Anand</PER>, <MISC>Founder and Chief Consultant, Scientific Computing Solutions</MISC>, Chennai, resource <MISC><ORG>person,10 a.m.K.S.R. Rangasamy College of</MISC> Arts and Science</ORG>, Tiruchengode: Conference on Intelligent Computing, M. Thiyagarajan, <MISC>Dean, Research and Development</MISC>, Nehru Group of Institutions, <LOC>Coimbatore</LOC>, chief guest, <PER>K.S. Rangasamy</PER>, <MISC>Founder-president, <ORG>KSR </MISC>Group</ORG> of Institutions, 10 <ORG><MISC>a.m.Muthayammal College of Arts</MISC</ORG>> and Science, Rasipuram: Induction programme for First Year P.G. students, 10.30 <MISC><ORG>a.m.PGP College of Agricultural Sci</MISC>ences</ORG>: Freshers Day celebration, 3 <ORG>p.m.National Book Trust</ORG> and <ORG><ORG>New Century Book House Private Li</ORG>mited</ORG>: 29th <ORG>National Book</ORG> Exhibition, <ORG>Fort Ground</ORG>, 9.30 a.m.ERODEEBET Group of Institutions: Faculty Development Programme on Good to Great, session by <PER>Celestine Paulraj</PER>, Head-Employee Engagement, <ORG>Scope International</ORG>, Chennai, 10.00 a.m.<MISC><ORG>Kongu Engineering Co</MISC>llege</ORG>: Inauguration of <ORG>Citizen Consumer Club</ORG>, 10.00 <ORG>a.m.Adharsh Vidhyalaya Arts and <MISC>Science College</MI</ORG>SC> for Women: <ORG>College Union</ORG> inauguration, K. Sivalingam, Founder and <MISC>Chairman</MISC>, Ideal and Adharsh Educational institutions, presides, 10.30 a.m.<MISC>Velalar <ORG>College of Engine</MISC>ering and Technology</ORG>: Guest lecture on Biomedical Engineering by <PER>D. Srimathi Niranjana</PER>, <MISC>Biomedical Engineer</MISC>, <ORG><PER>Apollo Hosp</ORG>itals</PER>, Karur, 2.00 <ORG>p.m.Erode <MISC>Sengunthar Engineering College</ORG></MISC>: Guest lecture on HERE MapCreator Expert Program 2.00 p.m.; <PER>P. Puviarasu</PER>, <MISC>Associate Profess<MISC>or</MISC> of Mathematics</MISC> speaks on Facts of PI, 4.30 p.m.']"
2,Abhaya Narendra Lotha Foundation,['New Delhi'],['ABHAY NARENDRA LODHA FOUNDATION'],"['Former <MISC>MP</MISC> <PER>Madhu Goud Yaskhi</PER> presented 40 sewing machines donated by the <ORG>Abhaya Narendra Lotha Foundation</ORG>, <LOC>New Delhi</LOC>, to the sewing training centre at the <ORG>Telangana State Special Police</ORG> (<ORG>TSSP</ORG>) 7th Battalion at Dichapally, on Thursday.<PER>He</PER> said on the occasion that training in cutting and stitching would also be provided free of cost to the women at the battalion. The Commandant <PER>Y. Srinivas Rao</PER>, <PER>his</PER> wife <PER>Rajini</PER>, <MISC>assistant</MISC> commandants P. Venkatramulu and G. Amrutha Rao and other police officers were also present.']"
3,Accenture,"['Bangalore', 'Bangalore']","['ACCENTURE INDIA PRIVATE LIMITED', 'ACCENTURE INDIA PRIVATE LIMITED']","['<ORG>Accenture</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, a multinational company will conduct an on-campus recruitment drive for MBA students at <ORG><MISC>KLM College of Engineering</MI</ORG>SC> for Women, here on February 5.', ""<ORG>Chinmaya Mission</ORG>: Shivaparaadha Shapamana Stotram by Adi Sankarar, Nambi Kalyana Mandapam, Sevvapet, 6.45 p.m.Ramakrishna Mission Ashrama: Narai S. Nellaiappan speaks on Vivekananda's Life, Ashrama premises, 7 <ORG><MISC>p.m.Periyar Univ</ORG>ersity</MISC>: Career Counselling and Placement Cell conducts TCS-BPO off campus, <ORG><MISC>Sri Ganesh College of Arts</MISC</ORG>> and Science, 9 <ORG>a.m.Padmavani Arts and Scienc<MISC>e College for W</MISC>omen</ORG>: National seminar on Recent Trends in Nanoscience, <PER>P. Perumal</PER>, <MISC>Professor and Head</MISC> of <ORG>Department of <MISC>Biotech</ORG>nology</MISC>, <ORG><MISC>Salem Periyar Univ</ORG>ersity</MISC>, inaugurates, <PER>R. Rajavel</PER>, <MISC>Assistant Professor</MISC>, <ORG>Department of Chemistry</ORG>, <PER>K. Sathiyamoorthy</PER>, <MISC>chairman</MISC> of the <ORG>college</ORG>, presides, special address, 9.30 <MISC>a.m.Knowledge Institu<ORG>te of Technology</MISC></ORG>: <ORG>Department of EEE</ORG> and <ORG>Electrical Engineer's Association</ORG> conducts National level technical symposium, ELKRAFT'13, M. Sathyabarathi, HR-Special, <ORG>Bosch Electrical Drives India Private Limited</ORG>, Chennai, 9.30 <ORG>a.m.V.M.K.V Engi<MISC>neering College</ORG></MISC>: Soft skill training programme for 2nd and 3rd year students, <PER>Begi Margret</PER>, Lead- Professional Skills Development conducts, 10 <ORG><MISC>a.m.Mahendra College of Engin</ORG>eering</MISC>: <ORG>Department</ORG> of Mechanical Engineering conducts national Level technical symposium, YANTHRA 2013, <PER>V. Nagarajan</PER>, <MISC>Chief Manager</MISC> (Mechanical), <ORG>Seshasayee Paper and Boards<ORG> Limited</ORG></ORG>, <ORG>Erode</ORG>, chief guest, <PER>M.G. Bharathkumar</PER>, <MISC>chairman</MISC> of the <ORG>college</ORG> presides, 10 <ORG>a.m.A.V.S. Engine<MISC>ering College</ORG></MISC>: College Day celebrations, CAPSTONE13, Ku. Gnanasambandam, Tamil Scholar, chief guest, <PER>Jayaprakash A. Gandhi</PER>, <MISC>Advisor</MISC>, AVS and <ORG>Sakthikailassh Group</ORG> of Institutions, felicitates, <PER>K. Kailasam</PER>, <MISC>Chairman of the group</MISC>, presides, 9.30 <ORG>a.m.<MISC>Thiagarajar Polytechnic C</ORG>ollege</MISC>: Annual Day celebrations, <PER>R. Chellappan</PER>, <MISC>Managing Director</MISC>, <ORG>Swelect Energy Systems Limited</ORG>, Chennai, chief guest, 5.30 <ORG><MISC>p.m.Sona College of Tech</ORG>nology</MISC>: <ORG>Department</ORG> of Computer Applications, Inauguration of national level technical symposium, CYBERTALK13, Quin Singh Janner, <MISC>Senior Analyst</MISC>, HR Recruitment, <ORG>Accenture</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, 9 a.m.<ORG>Confederation of Indian Industry</ORG> and SAGOSERVE: Conference on Latest Trends in Sago and Starch Industry, <PER>K. Dhanavel</PER>, <MISC>Secretary</MISC>, <ORG>Department of MSME</ORG>, <ORG>Government of <STA>Tamil</ORG> Nadu</STA>, inaugural address, K.K. Kaushal, <MISC>Special Officer and Managing Directo<MISC>r</MISC>, SAGOSERVE,</MISC> keynote address, <PER>R. Ramesh</PER>, <MISC>Chairman</MISC>, <ORG>CII</ORG> <ORG>Tamil Nadu State Council</ORG> and <MISC>Joint Managing Director</MISC>, TVS and <ORG>Sons Limited</ORG>, special address, <MISC>Hotel Park Plaza</MISC>, 9 a.m.TANSTIA-FNT <MISC><ORG>Service C</MISC>entre</ORG>, <STA>Salem District</STA> <ORG>Small Scale and Tiny Industries Association</ORG> and Friedrich-Naumann-Stiftung fur <MISC>die Freiheit</MISC>: Programme on Solution and Road Map to minimize power crisis through Solar Energy Projects, <PER>K. Dhanavel</PER>, <MISC>Secretary</MISC>, <ORG>Department of MSME</ORG>, <ORG>Government of <STA>Tamil</ORG> Nadu</STA>, inaugural address, <PER>C. Muthusami</PER>, <MISC>vice-president, TANSTIA</MISC> and <PER>Gunasingh Chelladurai</PER>, <MISC>Chairman</MISC>, <ORG>TFSC</ORG>, special addresses, GRT Grand Estancia, 9.30 a.m.Nehru Yuva <PER>Kendra Sangathan</PER>: <MISC>Inauguration of State level Youth Festival</MISC>/Yuva Kriti by <PER>S. Semmalai</PER>, <MISC>MP</MISC>, M. Sadacharavel, Zonal <MISC>Director of the Kendra</MISC>, <STA>Tamil Nadu</STA> and <STA>Pondicherry</STA> Zone, Chennai, Nehru Kalaiarangam, 11 a.m.<ORG>Malabar Gold</ORG> and Diamonds: Jewellery exhibition, Sri Saptharishi Iyer Kalyana Mahal, <MISC>Square Market</MISC>, Mettur, 10 a.m.<ORG>Rotary Club</ORG> of <MISC>Salem Fort</MISC>: P. Rajamanickam speaks on Present Economic trends, <MISC>Rotary Hall</MISC>, 7.30 <ORG>p.m.NAMAKKALDeputy Directorate of Health Services</ORG>, Namakkal: Free medical camp for government employees, 9 <ORG>a.m.Paavai<MISC> Polytechnic College</ORG></MISC>, Pachal: <MISC>NSS Special Camp</MISC> at Kurukapuram, 9.30 <MISC>a.m.Excel <ORG>College of Engine</MISC>ering</ORG> and Technology, Pallakapalayam: Erudition Carnival  Mechions13, 9.30 <ORG>a.m.<MISC>Excel Engineering C</ORG>ollege</MISC>, Pallakapalayam: Guest lecture on <MISC>Web Development Techniques</MISC>, 9.30 <MISC>a.m.Gnanamani College<ORG> of Engineering</MISC></ORG>, Pachal: Workshop on <MISC>Total Station</MISC>, 10.30 <ORG><MISC>a.m.Mahendra College of Engin</ORG>eering</MISC> and Technology, Mallasamudram: Guest lecture on Introduction session Network Simulator-NS2, 11 a.m.""]"
4,Aditya Birla,['Mumbai'],['ADITYA BIRLA SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY COMPANY PRIVATE LIMITED'],"[""R. Chidambaram (centre), Principal <MISC>Scientific Advisor</MISC> to the <ORG>Union Government</ORG>, with <PER>Kumar Mangalam Birla</PER> (right), <MISC>Chairman</MISC>, <ORG>Aditya Birla Group</ORG>, and <PER>Rajiv Dube</PER>, <MISC>Director, Corporate R&D Centre,</MISC> <ORG>Aditya Birla</ORG> Science, at Panvel in <LOC>Mumbai</LOC> on Saturday. PHOTO: PAUL NORONHAThe <ORG>Aditya Birla Group</ORG> is keen on stepping up its research and development (R&D) efforts and will focus on basic research for which it plans to dedicate one per cent of its turnover in the near future.Speaking at a launch of the <ORG>Aditya Birla</ORG> Science & Technology Centre (ABSTC) on Saturday, <PER>Kumar Mangalam Birla</PER>, <MISC>Chairman</MISC>, <ORG>Aditya Birla Group</ORG>, said the centre would be the hub of the group's global R&D network, supplementing the R&D footprint that already exists within our businesses.We cannot depend only on sourcing technology and knowhow through collaborations or licensing agreements for three important reasons. First, licensing technology is expensive; second, licensees cannot always get the best available technology; and third, and most important, only by actively developing our technology, will we create the institutional knowledge that sets us apart from the pack.ABSTC will be hub of the group's R&D network inclusive of <ORG>Novelis</ORG> and Colombian Tech Centres in <MISC>North America</MISC>, the <ORG><MISC>Thai Chemical Epoxy Centre</MISC</ORG>> in Thailand, the pulp laboratories in <MISC>Sweden</MISC> and several others.The R&D centre will undertake white space work in <MISC>some platform technologies</MISC> and has till date, spent in excess of Rs.250 crore in creating the facility.<PER>Luca Fontana</PER>, <MISC>CEO</MISC>, <ORG>ABSTC</ORG>, and <MISC>CTO</MISC>, <ORG>Aditya Birla Group</ORG>, said, We were relying on <MISC>licensed technology</MISC> and are now trying to develop own technologies and develop products and processes for the future here.As of now, the <ORG>centre</ORG> has over 100 scientists and engineers and this talent pool is slated to grow substantially.""]"
5,Adityajyot Eye Hospital,['Mumbai'],['ADITYA JYOT EYE HOSPITAL PRIVATE LIMITED'],"['<LOC>PUNE</LOC>: <MISC>Age-related macular degeneration (ARMD)</MISC> is one of the most common forms of macular problems today. It is an eye condition that affects a tiny part of the retina at the back of the eye, which is called the macula.With increase in life expectancy, cases of <MISC>age-related macular degeneration</MISC> are also on the rise, said experts at the symposium on macula held in the city on Sunday.""Many are not aware that they have <MISC>macular degeneration</MISC> until they have a noticeable vision problem or until it is detected during an eye examination,"" said <MISC>senior eye surgeon</MISC> <PER>Pran Nagpal</PER>, founder-chairman of <ORG>Retina Foundation</ORG>, <ORG>Ahmedabad</ORG>.The macula makes up only a small part of the retina, yet it is much more sensitive to detail than the rest of the retina. The macula is what allows you to thread a needle, read small print, and read street signs.The symposium was organised by <MISC><LOC>Pune</LOC>-based Nationa<ORG>l Institute of Op</MISC>hthalmology</ORG> (<ORG>NIO</ORG>), <ORG>Retina Foundation</ORG>, Ahmedabad and <ORG>Adityajyot Eye Hospital</ORG>, <LOC>Mumbai</LOC>, under the aegis of the <ORG><STA>Maharashtra</STA> Ophthal</ORG>mic Society and <ORG>Poona Ophthalmological Society</ORG>.""ARMD is one of the leading causes of visual impairment in individuals more than 50 years of age in developed countries. It is a major challenge in the new millennium in the developing countries also, as the size of the elderly population continues to rise due to betterment of medical facilities and increased life expectancy,"" <PER>Nagpal</PER> said.Besides, incidence of ARMD in diabetics is even higher. ""Around 60% of <MISC>diabetics managing diabetes</MISC> for more than 15 years are likely to develop ARMD. Hence, they should go for periodic eye check-up,"" <PER>Nagpal</PER> said.\'Epidemiology of <MISC>Age-Related Macular Degeneration</MISC>\' - conducted by experts from <ORG>department of <MISC>Ophthal</ORG>mology</MISC>, <ORG><MISC>Postgraduate Institute of Medical Education</MISC></ORG> and Research (<ORG>PGIMER</ORG>), Chandigarh and <ORG>Department of <MISC>Ophthal</ORG>mology</MISC>, <ORG><MISC>Government Medical C</ORG>ollege</MISC>, Chandigarh - states that apart from age the other non-modifiable personal risk factors for ARMD include short height, vital capacity, <MISC>hyperopia</MISC> or <MISC>farsightedness</MISC> and body mass index (BMI).In addition, the study also reported higher incidence of ARMD in individuals with <MISC>peripheral cataracts</MISC> than <MISC>central cataracts</MISC>. <MISC>Central cataracts</MISC> could have a protective influence on ARMD by cutting the solar rays reaching the macula, the study said.""Good vision is crucial to ones overall quality of life. Hence, there is an urgent need to raise awareness about ARMD,"" <MISC>said eye surgeon</MISC> <PER>Aditya Kelkar</PER> of <ORG>NIO</ORG>.Eye <MISC>surgeon</MISC> S <PER>Natarajan</PER>, <MISC>chairman and managing director</MISC> of <ORG>Adityajyot Eye Hospital</ORG>, <LOC>Mumbai</LOC>, spoke about newer treatment modalities like intra vitreous implant meant for treating eye conditions like <MISC>retinal vein occlusion</MISC> and <MISC>uveitis</MISC>.Intravitreal injection has been in use for more than 10 years in <MISC>India</MISC> to directly deliver medication to treat eye conditions. ""For a year now, we have also started using biodegradable implants - drug effects of which last for a longer period than injection,"" <PER>Natarajan</PER> said.The implant is slowly dissolved inside the eye by the vitreous gel that fills the eye, releasing the drug. It is used to treat adults with <MISC>retinal vein occlusion</MISC> and <MISC>non-infectious uveitis</MISC>, <MISC>inflammation</MISC> of the middle layer of the eye.""Trials are currently on to find how effective these implants are in treating <MISC>diabetic macular edema (DME)</MISC>,"" <MISC>said eye surgeon</MISC> <PER>Ajitbabu Majji</PER>, <MISC>head</MISC> of <ORG><MISC>Retina Department L V Prasad Eye Ho</ORG>spital</MISC>, <LOC>Hyderabad</LOC>.DME occurs when blood vessels in the retina of patients with <MISC>diabetes</MISC> begin to leak into the macula.']"
6,Agricultural Insurance Company,['New Delhi'],['AGRICULTURE INSURANCE COMPANY OF INDIA LIMITED'],"['Jorhat, Dec. 7: <ORG><STA>Assam</STA> Agricultural</ORG> University vice-chancellor <PER>K.M. Bujarbaruah</PER> today called for the setting up of a national-level agricultural risk management authority to ensure that <MISC>insurance benefits</MISC> percolate down to the right stakeholders. Addressing the inaugural session of the national-level workshop on Risk Assessment and Insurance Products for Agriculture organised by the universitys department of agricultural economics, <PER>Bujarbaruah</PER> said such an authority could mitigate risks in the agricultural sector. <PER>He</PER> said agricultural <MISC>insurance companies</MISC> had a slew of products for farmers but most of them were not aware of this most probably because of the failure of extension linkage. A mechanism should be set up by the <ORG>National Centre for Agricultural Economics and Policy Research</ORG> (<ORG>NCAP</ORG>), <LOC>New Delhi</LOC>, and the <ORG>Agricultural Insurance Company</ORG> India, <LOC>New Delhi</LOC>, to disseminate awareness of products meant to benefit farmers, <PER>he</PER> added. <PER>He</PER> urged members of the two agencies and other NGOs present at the session to stress on livestock and <MISC>poultry insurance</MISC> besides <MISC>crop insurance</MISC> as poultry farmers in the region had suffered huge losses in recent times because of the outbreak of avian flu. Nabard official <PER>Mayur Bora</PER> said one of the reasons why farmers were not benefiting from <MISC>insurance instruments</MISC> was that most of them were written in English. As most farmers do not know the English language, it is necessary to translate all the products into the regional language and distribute leaflets and pamphlets among them so that they can become aware and approach the <ORG>regional crop insurance office</ORG> in Guwahati to get their crops insured, <PER>he</PER> added. <PER>Nivedita Deka</PER>, <MISC>professor</MISC> of the <ORG>department</ORG> of agricultural economics and farm management, said the AAUs extension <ORG>education department</ORG> would soon start working on this. <PER>S.S. Raju</PER>, <MISC>principal scientist</MISC> of <ORG>NCAP</ORG> and one of the resource persons of the workshop, said a sound national policy was required to promote <MISC>suitable insurance products</MISC> in agriculture like poultry or crops for farmers as agriculture in <MISC>India</MISC> is highly risk prone, more so for the small and marginal farmers. Another resource person, <PER>K.M. Rao</PER>, said 25 million farmers in the country and 50,000 farmers in <STA>Assam</STA> had opted for agricultural <MISC>insurance products</MISC> while millions were yet to go for it to overcome the risks in agriculture, which are growing with global warming and climate change. <PER>He</PER> stressed an integrated risk management approach in which <MISC>the farmer</MISC>, the state and <MISC>insurance agencies work</MISC> together to tackle risks. <PER>Rama Subramanim</PER>, <MISC>a scientist</MISC> with the <MISC>New Delhibased Indian <ORG>Agricultural Statistical Research Inst</MISC>itute</ORG>, said it was developing a computer-based programme on <MISC>weather systems</MISC> to help farmers take quick decisions on weather fluctuations.']"
7,Agriculture Insurance Company Limited,['Bangalore'],['AGRICULTURE INSURANCE COMPANY OF INDIA LIMITED'],"['The <ORG>Department of Studies</ORG> in Commerce, <MISC><ORG>University of M</MISC>ysore</ORG>, will organise a conference on Agri-risk management under the Special Assistance Programme of the <ORG><MISC>University Grants Comm</ORG>ission</MISC> here on Tuesday.Vice-Chancellor K.S. Rangappa will inaugurate the conference on the department premises at 10 a.m. He will also release four books authored by <MISC>conference coordinator</MISC> <PER>G. Kotreshwar</PER>.M.J. Bhende of <ORG>Institute for Social and Economic Change</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, will deliver the keynote address and <PER>K. Eresi</PER>, <MISC>retired professor</MISC> of <ORG><MISC>Bangalore Univ</ORG>ersity</MISC>, will be the guest of honour.Invited speakers will conduct three technical sessions after the inaugural ceremony. Padmavathi of <ORG>Indian School of Business</ORG>, <LOC>Hyderabad</LOC>, will speak on <ORG>Agriculture</ORG> production risks: Need for Disaster Risk Management; D. Dilip Dange, <MISC>Deputy General Manager</MISC>, <ORG>Agriculture Insurance Company Limited</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, on Performance of Agri-Risk Insurance and <PER>M.R. Shollapur</PER>, <MISC>director</MISC>, <MISC>Siddaganga Institu<ORG>te of Technology</MISC></ORG>, <PER>Tumkur</PER>, will speak on Financial literacy.The books which will be released at the conference are in the field of <MISC>finance</MISC> and derivatives  A Dictionary of Managerial Finance; Capital Budgeting; Capital Market Instruments: Stocks, Bonds and Derivatives; and Finance Derivatives.']"
8,Air India,['Mumbai'],['AIR INDIA LIMITED'],"[""<ORG>Air India</ORG> deployed a larger aircraft apparently to accommodate the family of the then Civil Aviation <MISC>Minister</MISC> <PER>Praful Patel</PER> on its <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>-<MISC>Maldives</MISC> trip in April 2010, file notings disclosed by the national carrier have indicated.There were claims earlier that since the business class seats were already booked on the A319 aircraft IC-965 from <LOC>Bangalore</LOC> to Male, <ORG>Air India</ORG> switched to the bigger <MISC>A320</MISC> with 20 business class seats to accommodate seven members of the Deshpande family  in-laws of <PER>Mr. Patel</PER>'s daughter <PER>Avni</PER>. The passenger list, disclosed on the directives of the <ORG>Central Information Commission</ORG>, shows that the Deshpandes  <ORG>Congress</ORG> <MISC>leader</MISC> <PER>R.V. Deshpande</PER>, <PER>Radha Deshpande</PER>, <PER>Prasad Deshpande</PER>, <PER>Meghna Deshpande</PER> and <PER>Master Dhruv</PER>, in addition to <PER>Avni</PER> and her husband <PER>Prashant Deshpande</PER>  were indeed on board IC-965 on April 25, 2010 for the <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>-Male and IC-966 from Male to <LOC>Bangalore</LOC> on April 28, 2010.The file notings show that instructions were issued through email from the <MISC>Mumbai headquarters</MISC>. The order, a copy of which was supplied with the RTI reply said, Due to heavy demand in J Class on <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>-Male on April 25, 2010 and Male-<LOC>Bangalore</LOC> on April 28, 2010, the J Class capacity is increased on the above two dates by rotation change in equipment.The order for the change was evidently from top officials of <ORG>Air India</ORG>, as the copy on the decision was sent to <PER>Aben Lal</PER>, who is <MISC>now <MISC>General M</MISC>anager, Commercial,</MISC> with the note this is in reference to your telecon with Mr. F J Vaz [<MISC>now <MISC>Executive Di</MISC>rector, Commercial].'</MISC>'The reply stated, <MISC>Station Manager</MISC>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, received an e-mail on April 8, 2010 from <PER>Harjeet Sawhney</PER>, the then <MISC>Manager</MISC> (scheduling), <MISC>Commercial Headquarters</MISC>, <ORG>Air India</ORG>, <LOC>Mumbai</LOC>, regarding change of equipment on April 25 and 28, 2010.'' With the change in the aircraft, the carrier had to fly with six vacant seats in the business class and 47 in the economy class on the way from <LOC>Bangalore</LOC> to Male, the passenger list revealed under the RTI Act to activist <PER>Subhash Agrawal</PER> shows. Similarly, while returning on April 28, eight business class seats and 52 economy seats were vacant on the flight IC-966 from Male to <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>.The carrier, which was hesitant to disclose the passenger details even after the orders of the <ORG>CIC</ORG>, was issued show cause notice for non-compliance.While furnishing details, <ORG>Air India</ORG> said: Though keeping in view the spirit of RTI Act, 2005, we are complying with the orders of <MISC>the Information Commissioner</MISC> [Sushma Singh] and providing the information to the appellant, it is humbly requested that this may please not be allowed to be treated as precedent since the company, keeping in view its commercial interests, follows the practice of not disclosing the <MISC>travel particulars</MISC> of its valued passengers, which are personal to them, to any third party.""]"
9,AirAsia,['Chennai'],['AIRASIA (INDIA) PRIVATE LIMITED'],"['<LOC>NEW DELHI</LOC>: The joint venture of Malaysian low-cost carrier <ORG>AirAsia</ORG> and <ORG>Tata Group</ORG> may take off soon in Indian skies. On Tuesday, <ORG>Tata Group</ORG> <MISC>chairman</MISC> emeritus Ratan <ORG>Tata</ORG> and <MISC>LCC chief</MISC> <PER>Tony Fernandes</PER> met <MISC>aviation minister</MISC> <PER>Ajit Singh</PER>. After the meeting <PER>Singh</PER> said <ORG>AirAsia India</ORG> had applied for a no-objection certificate and the process of clearing all required steps ""will not take too long.""Ratan <ORG>Tata</ORG> said: ""This is a different type of enterprise which <PER>Fernandes</PER> is bringing. Hopefully, it will spread <MISC>air travel</MISC> across <MISC>India</MISC> and give a new dimension (to the aviation sector). The <ORG>Tata Group</ORG> is pleased to be associated with it."" When asked about the long gap after which Tatas were making a foray into aviation despite flying being a passion with <PER>him</PER>, <PER>he</PER> said: ""We didn\'t come earlier because we chose to stay out.""<PER>Fernandes</PER>, who was also accompanied by new <ORG>AirAsia India</ORG> <MISC>CEO</MISC> <PER>Mittu Chandilya</PER>, said the meeting with <PER>Singh</PER> was ""to apprise <MISC>the minister</MISC> about the developments that have taken place and our visit to <LOC>Chennai</LOC> (the <MISC>proposed airline</MISC>\'s headquarters)."" <PER>Fernandes</PER> promised low fares on <PER>his</PER> India JV, despite the inherently high cost structure. ""We think we will be able to reduce fares by increasing volumes, creating an economic stimulus and creating more jobs. Almost 50% of the <MISC>air travel market</MISC> is between <LOC>Delhi</LOC> and <LOC>Mumbai</LOC>. We will try to rebalance that so that <MISC>India</MISC> has a more equal distribution of air traffic. We have a much better understanding of the market in the south,"" <PER>he</PER> said. While <ORG>AirAsia</ORG> will be based in <LOC>Chennai</LOC>, the operational bases could be at <LOC>Chennai</LOC>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC> or <LOC>Kochi</LOC>.<PER>Ajit Singh</PER> said the names of <ORG>AirAsia India</ORG>\'s <MISC>airline</MISC>\'s top brass had been sent to the home ministry for security clearance. ""They are working on that. When they get security clearance, they will apply to the DGCA (for flying permit). I don\'t expect that it will take too long,"" <PER>he</PER> said. <ORG>Tata</ORG>, <PER>Fernandes</PER> and <PER>Chandilya</PER> <MISC>also met commerce minister</MISC> <PER>Anand Sharma</PER>.<ORG>AirAsia India</ORG> is a JV between <ORG>AirAsia</ORG>, <ORG>Tata Group</ORG> and <ORG>Telestra TradePlace</ORG> with they having a 49%, 30% and 21% stake each, respectively. The <ORG>Foreign Investment Promotion Board</ORG> had cleared this proposal in March.<ORG>Tata</ORG>, <PER>Tony</PER> meet <MISC>civil aviation minister</MISC>']"
10,Ajith Balakrishnan Foundation,['Mumbai'],['AJIT BALAKRISHNAN FOUNDATION'],"[""The innovative <MISC>teacher</MISC> awards instituted by the <ORG>Ajith Balakrishnan Foundation</ORG>, <LOC>Mumbai</LOC>, and the <ORG>North Malabar Chamber of Commerce</ORG> (<ORG>NMCC</ORG>) will be bestowed on three schoolteachers at a function here on August 13.<ORG>NMCC</ORG> <MISC>president</MISC> <PER>B. Maheshchandra Baliga</PER> said at a press conference here that the awards comprising Rs.1 lakh each would be presented to three teachers selected from primary, middle, and high school/higher secondary school categories at a function at the <MISC>Chamber Hall</MISC> here at 10 a.m.The awards would be presented by district panchayat <MISC>president</MISC> K.A. Sarala.The names of the awardees would be announced at the function.<PER>Mr. Baliga</PER> said the women's wing of the <ORG>NMCC</ORG> would be formally launched at a function at the <MISC>Chamber Hall</MISC> at 10.30 a.m. on August 14. National <MISC>teacher</MISC> award winner Venu Balakrishnan would inaugurate the women's wing. <ORG><ORG>Redif</ORG>f.com</ORG> <MISC>chairman</MISC> <PER>Ajith Balakrishnan</PER> would deliver the keynote address.""]"
11,Alkem,['Mumbai'],['ALKEM LABORATORIES LIMITED'],"[""<MISC>An official</MISC> of the <ORG>Oriental Insurance Company</ORG> presents bouquets to <ORG>Alkem Laboratories Limited</ORG> <MISC>chairperson</MISC> <PER>Samprada Singh</PER> (centre) and the firms <MISC>managing director</MISC>, BN Singh, at a function in <LOC>Patna</LOC> on Tuesday. Pictures by <ORG>Nagendra Kumar Singh Vedanta Group</ORG> <MISC>executive chairperson</MISC> <PER><PER>Anil Ag</PER>arwal Both</PER> are sons of the soil, both are big names of <ORG>India Inc.</ORG> and both are apprehensive about investing in their own state. And in their stand, both have sent out a message, loud and clear, to <MISC>chief minister</MISC> <PER>Nitish Kumar</PER>: unless the government offers incentives, it would be difficult for entrepreneurs to set up shop in the state. <PER>Samprada Singh</PER>, the 87-year-old <MISC>chairman</MISC> of <ORG>Alkem Laboratories Limited</ORG> who was recently named as the 48th richest Indian by Forbes, has made it clear that incentives have to be given to attract industry. <PER>His</PER> younger brother, <ORG>Alkems</ORG> <MISC>managing director</MISC> <PER>Basudev Narain Singh</PER>, told <MISC>The Telegraph</MISC> on Tuesday that <PER>his</PER> company was keen on investing in <STA>Bihar</STA> provided the government offered financial incentives in the form of excise and income tax relief as extended by states such as <STA>Goa</STA>, <STA>Sikkim</STA>, Uttarakhand, <STA>Jammu and Kashmir</STA> and <STA>Himachal Pradesh</STA>. <PER>Basudev Singh</PER> said <ORG>Alkem</ORG>, based in <LOC>Mumbai</LOC>, was keen on investing in the state and added that <PER>he</PER> was hopeful the government was working towards allowing incentives for the <MISC>pharmaceutical sector</MISC>. We are always keen to invest in <STA>Bihar</STA>. Not just we, there are <MISC>many other p<MISC>harmaceutical companies</MISC></MISC> which are interested. But the state should be giving us incentives in the <MISC>pharmaceutical sector</MISC>. By incentives, we mean I-T (income tax) and excise relief. There are many states in <MISC>India</MISC> which have offered these benefits and investments have been made there. Some of these states are <STA>Sikkim</STA>, <STA>Goa</STA>, J&K, Uttarakhand etc, <PER>Basudev Singh</PER> told <MISC>The Telegraph</MISC> on the sidelines of the felicitation ceremony of <PER>Samprada Singh</PER>, organised by <ORG>Oriental Insurance Company Limited.</ORG> <PER>Samprada Singh</PER>, who hails from a farming family in Okri (Jehanabad), had started <PER>his</PER> career as <MISC>a small retail chemist</MISC> in <LOC>Patna</LOC> in 1953. <PER>He</PER> launched <ORG>Alkem Labs</ORG> in 1973. Tax incentives given to the <MISC>pharmaceutical sector</MISC> in <STA>Sikkim</STA> has been able to attract investments worth more than Rs 3,500 crore. More than 14 <MISC>pharmaceutical companies</MISC>, including <ORG>Alkem</ORG>, have made significant investments in the <MISC>northeastern <MISC>Him</MISC>alayan</MISC> state. Asked whether <ORG>Alkem</ORG> had contacted the <STA><ORG></STA>Bihar government</ORG> regarding the incentives, <PER>Basudev Singh</PER> said <PER>he</PER> was sure that the state was doing its best. We hope the <ORG>state government</ORG> is doing its best, the MD said. <PER>Anil Agarwal</PER>, the <LOC>Patna</LOC>-born <MISC>chairperson</MISC> of the <MISC>UK</MISC>-based <ORG>Vedanta Group</ORG>, had also pledged help for the state last year. <PER>Agarwal</PER> is an active member of the Bihar State <ORG>Industrial Investment Advisory Council</ORG>, which was formed by the <ORG>state government</ORG> last year. <PER>He</PER> was present at the first meeting of the <ORG>council</ORG> in <LOC>Patna</LOC> on September 16 last year. A US$ 50 billion group listed at <ORG>London Stock Exchange</ORG>, <ORG>Vedanta</ORG> is a natural resources-based organisation dealing in aluminium, copper zinc, lead, silver iron ore, <MISC>oil and gas</MISC>. While addressing a meeting of the <ORG><STA>Bihar</STA> Chamber </ORG>of Commerce and Industries last year, <PER>Agarwal</PER>, while stopping short of committing any big-ticket investment for <STA>Bihar</STA>, had pledged Rs 100-crore financial support for the <ORG>government</ORG> in the education and <MISC>healthcare sectors</MISC>. We are a natural resources-based company. There are no mines available in <STA>Bihar</STA> at present. But the state has huge potential in sugarcane production. We are exploring what we can do for the state. Right now, we have pledged financial support of Rs 100 crore to the <STA><ORG></STA>Bihar government</ORG> in healthcare and the education sector, <PER>Agarwal</PER> had announced. But the pledge remains a pledge until now. The Telegraphs attempts to contact <ORG>Vedanta</ORG> by email did not elicit any response. <PER>He</PER> (<PER>Agarwal</PER>) had clearly stated that <STA>Bihar</STA> didn't have any mines. But <PER>he</PER> had also promised a sum of Rs 100 crore, said <PER>Satyajit Kumar</PER>, <MISC>chairman</MISC> of the PHD Chamber of Commerce and Industries. In an earlier talk with <MISC>The Telegraph</MISC>, <MISC>senior BJP leader</MISC> and former <MISC>deputy chief minister</MISC> <PER>Sushil Kumar Modi</PER> had said that even if the state were successful in getting special status, investments would be difficult to come by. Special status means incentives and sops, but the state has got a bigger issue in the form of land scarcity. Unless this problem is solved, big-ticket investments will not come. Even if our (the BJPs) government comes to power, it will be a major challenge for us, <PER>Modi</PER> had told <MISC>The Telegraph</MISC>.""]"
12,Ampere Vehicles Pvt Ltd,['Coimbatore'],['AMPERE VEHICLES PRIVATE LIMITED'],"['A woman performing duties to the fullest is as much an achiever as the one who succeeds by virtue of holding a high position, J. Uma Maheshwari, <MISC>Additional Secretary</MISC> - Higher Education, <ORG>Government of Tamil Nadu</ORG> said.The country can develop only by according due importance to women, Ms. Uma said, addressing the World Womens Day celebration at <MISC>Bannari Amman Institu<ORG>te of Technology</MISC></ORG> recently.AwardsThe countrys success lies in the hands of women who must come forward to make the country proud, she said during the celebrations that had as its highlight presentation of Women of Excellence Awards. The awardees constituted <PER>Andal Priyadharshini</PER>, <MISC>Head Programme Officer</MISC>, <PER>Doordharshan Kendra</PER>, <LOC>Coimbatore</LOC>; and Hemalatha Annamalai, Founder & <MISC>Chief Executive Officer</MISC>, <ORG>Ampere Vehicles Pvt Ltd</ORG>, <LOC>Coimbatore</LOC>. <MISC>The Chairman</MISC>, <MISC>Bannari Amman Institu<ORG>te of Technology</MISC></ORG>, S.V. Balasubramaniam presided over the function.']"
13,Antrix,['New Delhi'],['ANTRIX CORPORATION LIMITED'],"[""<PER>K. Radhakrishnan</PER>, <MISC>Secretary</MISC>, <ORG>Department of Space</ORG>, flanked by V. S. Hegde, <MISC>Scientific Secretary</MISC>, <ORG><ORG</ORG>>ISRO</ORG> (left) and <PER>T. K. Alex</PER>, <MISC>Director</MISC>, <ORG>ISRO Satellite Centre</ORG>, during a <MISC>media conference</MISC> after the <ORG>Space Commission</ORG> meeting which also discussed the cancellation of the agreement between <ORG>Devas</ORG> and <ORG>Antrix</ORG>, in <LOC>New Delhi</LOC> on Saturday.  Photo: V. SudershanWhile the <ORG>Department of Space</ORG> has recommended to the <ORG>Union Cabinet</ORG> the termination of the deal between <ORG>Antrix Corporation</ORG> and <ORG>Devas Multimedia</ORG>, the latter on Saturday claimed it was still to receive any formal communication regarding a review of the entire deal.Emerging from the crucial <ORG>Space Commission</ORG> meeting, its head, <PER>K. Radhakrishnan</PER>, who is <MISC>also Secretary</MISC>, <ORG>Department of Space</ORG>, and <MISC>Chairman</MISC>, <ORG>Indian Space Research Organisation</ORG>, told journalists the contract needed to be annulled given the requirement of S-band spectrum for strategic purposes.The demand of the strategic sector for the scarce spectrum had increased five-fold over the last five years. Notably, if the deal is terminated, <ORG>Antrix Corporation</ORG> might have to pay penalties for delay in the delivery of the two satellites that <ORG>ISRO</ORG> was to launch as part of the deal, and the annual payment for the life of the satellite. <ORG>Antrix</ORG> is <ORG>ISRO</ORG>'s commercial arm.The issue will now be discussed at a meeting of the <ORG>Cabinet Committee on Security</ORG>. In July 2010, the <ORG>Space Commission</ORG> had decided to annul the agreement, signed between <ORG>Antrix</ORG> and <ORG>Devas</ORG> in January 2005. The <ORG>Law Ministry</ORG> had also favoured cancellation of the deal in the national interest.But <ORG>Devas Multimedia</ORG> is not calling it quits. In a video interview put on the company's website and also on <ORG>YouTube</ORG>, its <MISC>president and CEO</MISC> <PER>Ramachandran Viswanathan</PER> claimed that despite all the controversy and the government's decision to review the deal, <PER>his</PER> company was still to get any official communication on the issue.We have still not been informed [about the review panel set up]there has been no notification in respect of the contract either by <ORG>Antrix</ORG> or <ORG>ISRO</ORG> or by any other govt agency, <PER>he</PER> said. We were never formally informed about any concerns with regards to the <ORG>Law Ministry</ORG> or any other aspect [regarding the deal] that the government may have been contemplating despite regular dialogue we have been having with [the] seniormost levels [at <ORG>ISRO</ORG> and <ORG>Antrix</ORG>], <PER>he</PER> added.<PER>Mr. Viswanathan</PER> claimed that during the last six months, <ORG>Devas</ORG> had been in regular contact with senior <ORG>ISRO</ORG> and <ORG>Antrix</ORG> officials.As part of the contract, operational reviews of the progress of the construction of the satellite have been continuing for the last three years, including the last six months. I had last met <ORG>ISRO</ORG> <MISC>Chairman</MISC> a few months back since then we have continued to meet senior executives of <ORG>ISRO</ORG> and <ORG>Antrix</ORG>.The <ORG>Space Commission</ORG>'s decision to scrap the deal notwithstanding, periodic joint reviews by <ORG>Devas</ORG>, <ORG>Antrix</ORG> and <ORG>ISRO</ORG> to monitor the status of satellite and the contract were held even as recently as January 2011.<ORG>Devas</ORG> also made presentations on its security and strategic applications to various <ORG>Government of <MISC>India</M</ORG>ISC> agencies last month, <PER>Mr. Viswanathan</PER> added.""]"
14,Apollo Hospitals,"['New Delhi', 'Hyderabad']","['APOLLO HOSPITALS ENTERPRISE LIMITED', 'APOLLO HOSPITALS ENTERPRISE LIMITED']","['<ORG>Apollo</ORG> Transplant Institutes continues to lead in solid <MISC>organ transplant</MISC> programme in the world by performing 1,456 transplants in 2013, said <PER>Anupam Sibal</PER><MISC>, Group Medical Director</MISC>, <ORG>Apollo Hospitals Group</ORG> and <ORG>Senior Paediatric Gastroenterologist</ORG>, here recently.Interacting with experts in the State and <MISC>media persons</MISC>, <PER>Prof. Sibal</PER> said <ORG><MISC>Apollo Hospital</ORG></MISC> Delhi became the busiest transplant centre in the world by performing 952 transplants in 2013.In 2012, 1200 solid <MISC>organ transplants</MISC> (840 kidney and 360 liver) in children and adults were performed. In 2013, <ORG>Apollo</ORG> Delhi performed 283 liver and 669 <MISC>kidney transplants</MISC> and under the <ORG>Apollo</ORG> transplant programme, 388 liver and 1053 <MISC>kidney transplantations</MISC> were performed, <PER>he</PER> said.Similarly, A.C. Anand, <MISC>Senior Consultant</MISC> Gastroenterologist with <ORG>Apollo Hospitals</ORG>, said: Apollos <MISC>liver transplant</MISC> programme aims to provide effective treatment to patients with liver failure.In the meanwhile, <ORG>Apollo Hospitals</ORG>, Bhubaneswars department of Gastroenterology (Medical and Surgical) organised a national level Continuing Medical Education (CME) Programme, which was inaugurated by <PER>Prof. Ashok Kumar Mohapatra</PER>, <MISC>Director</MISC> of All <ORG><MISC>India Institute of Medical Sc</ORG>iences</MISC> (<ORG>AIIMs</ORG>), Bhubaneswar.Many eminent and senior consultants like Padmashree D. K. Bhargav of Indraprastha <ORG>Apollo Hospitals</ORG>, <LOC>New Delhi</LOC>, <PER>Avinash Supe</PER>, Dean of <ORG><MISC>LT Medical C</ORG>ollege</MISC>, <PER>Pune</PER> and <PER>G. V. Rao</PER>, <MISC>Chief</MISC> of GI Surgery of <MISC><ORG>Asian Institute of Gastroenter</MISC>ology</ORG>, <LOC>Hyderabad</LOC> attended the CME.Around 175 doctors from various parts of the State and country attended this national CME programme.', '<LOC>NAGPUR</LOC>: Awareness about eye donations may have spread in the bigger cities, but is still to reach the smaller towns and villages. Also, there is a lack of infrastructure and trained surgeons when it comes to corneal <MISC>transplantation</MISC>, believe experts.This was opinion of doctors during \'Corneawareness\' programme organized by the ophthalmology department of <ORG><MISC>NKP Salve Institute of Medical Sc</O<ORG>RG>iences</MISC> and EYEDU Foundation</ORG>. Along with discussion on the basics and recent advances in management of <MISC>corneal diseases</MISC>, the programme also had a hands-on training session where demonstrations and spot diagnosis of difficult cases was arranged for the post graduate students. The local faculty <PER>Dr Ajay Kulkarni</PER> spoke about pterigium <MISC>surgery</MISC> and keratoplasty.""The number of donations in the country is not high enough with the annual requirement being one lakh corneas and the number of donations being 30,000. Of these, only half can be used for transplants as the others are either diseased or not of the desired quality. Eye banks in the country are capable of handling much more work than they presently do,"" said <PER>Dr Aashish Bansal</PER>, <MISC>director</MISC> of <ORG>EYEMAX Eye Foundation</ORG> and <MISC>head of the ophthalmology department</MISC> at <ORG>Apollo Hospitals</ORG>, <LOC>Hyderabad</LOC>.<PER>He</PER> said the awareness level in villages and smaller towns was low. ""Also, there is a severe shortage of surgeons trained for <MISC>corneal transplants</MISC>, especially in <MISC>northern <MISC</MISC>>India</MISC>. In states like <STA>Punjab</STA> and <STA>Haryana</STA>, the collection is good but the corneas have to be sent to other states for <MISC>transplantation</MISC>,"" <PER>he</PER> said. Transport can also cause deterioration in quality, <PER>he</PER> added.It is no longer difficult to convince a person or family about eye donation, the problem is not asking at the right time, believes <LOC>Mumbai</LOC>-based <MISC>cornea consultant</MISC> <PER>Dr Nikhil Gokhale</PER>. ""A grief-stricken family does not have eye donation as top priority. If people were to be asked after the death of their loved ones for donating eyes, at least 10% would agree straightaway,"" <PER>he</PER> said. This onus, <PER>he</PER> says, lies with the doctors issuing the death certificates. Earlier, the death certificate in <STA>state of Maharashtra</STA> had a column asking this question, which served as a gentle reminder, <PER>he</PER> added. ""What we need today are more tissue collection, more trained surgeons and infrastructure that makes eye donation easier and affordable,"" <PER>he</PER> said.Cornea\'s is among the most successful <MISC>organ transplants</MISC> where the chances of rejection are very low, informed <PER>Dr Rekha Khandelwal</PER>, <MISC>professor and head of the ophthalmology department</MISC> at NKPSIMS. ""Even corneas that are not transplanted are utilized for research. The number of donations has definitely gone up. Yet, there also needs to be an attitudinal shift of donors who take these donations for granted,"" <PER>she</PER> said.']"
15,Apparel Export Promotion Council,['New Delhi'],['APPAREL EXPORT PROMOTION COUNCIL.'],"['Textile export units in Karur and elsewhere would benefit immensely from the Registration, Evaluation, Authorisation and Restriction of Chemical Substances (REACH) programme organised by the international testing agency <ORG>TUV Rheinland</ORG>, according to <PER>Bhaskar</PER>, <MISC>Director</MISC> (Finance and <ORG>General Administration</ORG>), <ORG>TUV Rheinland India</ORG>.Speaking at the high-level Summit and Best Practice Exchange Forum seminar held here to mark the successful completion of the REACH programme, which the <ORG>TUV Rheinland</ORG> undertook in association with Europes <MISC>largest development finance company</MISC> <ORG>DEG Germany</ORG>, <PER>Mr. Bhaskar</PER> noted that the public private partnership programme was aimed at enabling the home textile units implement global best practices for Substances of Very High Concern and comply with REACH regulations <MISC>EC</MISC> No.1907/2006 adopted by the European buyers.<ORG>TUV Rheinland</ORG> helped 13 home textile manufacturing units get the necessary training and consultancy to fill the gaps in their <MISC>supply chain</MISC> and procurement besides demonstrating the units ability to produce REACH <MISC>compliant products</MISC> consistently, <PER>Mr. Bhaskar</PER> pointed out. The pilot programme ran from September 2011 to now. With the experience gained from the programme <ORG>TUV Rheinland</ORG> was all set to commercially offer the expertise to individual home textile production units. Our clients would then be able to address issues relating to awareness, registration, notification and implementation of REACH to avoid rejection, <PER>he</PER> added.The <ORG>Handloom Export Cloth Manufacturers Association</ORG> and the <ORG>Apparel Export Promotion Council</ORG> were also part of the programme whose objective was to improve protection of human health and environment through better and early identification of intrinsic properties of <MISC>chemical substance</MISC> right from the raw material stage to the <MISC>final product</MISC> in the home textile units, said <ORG>TUV Rheinland</ORG> <MISC>General Manager, <ORG>Industry Services</ORG>, Shanmu</MISC>ghasundaram.Ensuring sustainabilityTo ensure sustainability <ORG>TUV Rheinland</ORG> would offer <MISC>clients complete solutions</MISC> in the field of testing and other support services related to Substances of Very High Concern mandated under regulations such as REACH, RoHS and ELV, <PER>Mr. Shanmughasundaram</PER> noted. The agency has been accredited by the <ORG>National Accreditation Board</ORG> for Testing and Calibration of Laboratories for all hazardous substances.<ORG>TUV Rheinland</ORG> has the expertise in providing services for <MISC>pressure equipment</MISC>, <MISC>material technology</MISC>, <MISC>energy</MISC>, environment, automotive engineering, type approval, solar and <MISC><MISC>fuel cell tech</MISC>nology</MISC> and certification of management systems, <PER>Mr. Bhaskar</PER> added.Those who spoke at the seminar included <MISC>Director</MISC>, <ORG>Apparel Export Promotion Council</ORG>, <LOC>New Delhi</LOC>, Chandrima Chatterjee, <ORG>Handloom Export Cloth Manufacturers Association</ORG> <MISC>president</MISC> <PER>Anboli Kaliappan</PER> as <MISC>also Associate Professor of Chemistry and Textile Chemistry</MISC>, <ORG><MISC>AVVM Sri Pushpam C</ORG>ollege</MISC>, Thanjavur, G. Chandramohan and K.G. Prithvi of the <ORG>Textile Manufacturers Exporters Association</ORG>.<ORG>TUV Rheinland</ORG> helped 13 home textile manufacturing units get the necessary training and consultancyWith experience gained from the programme <ORG>TUV Rheinland</ORG> was all set to offer the expertise to individual home textile production units.']"
16,Aspiring Minds,['Delhi'],['ASPIRING MINDS ASSESSMENT PRIVATE LIMITED'],"['<STA>Andhra Pradesh</STA> figures among the bottom 25 percentile of States as far as employability of engineering students for IT jobs goes.The National Employability Report  Engineering Graduates 2014 ranks the State alongside <STA>Chhattisgarh</STA>, <STA>Uttar Pradesh</STA>, <STA>Kerala</STA> and <STA>Tamil Nadu</STA>. According to the report, released by employability solutions company <ORG>Aspiring Minds</ORG> , <LOC>Delhi</LOC>, <STA>Bihar</STA>, <STA>Punjab</STA> and Uttarakhand figure in the top 25 percentile of States of most employable engineers.18 StatesThe report is based on the graduate class of 2013 and covers data from more than 1.20 lakh engineering students from 520 engineering colleges across 18 States.Compared to other metros, <LOC>Hyderabad</LOC> seems to be way behind given that only 1.7 per cent students were found to be employable for <MISC>software jobs</MISC>, while for non-IT jobs, its performance was found to be satisfactory.In the Associate ITeS operations sector however, 35.6 per cent were found employable.SectorsSimilarly, 40.2 per cent were found employable in the ITeS and BPO sectors in non-IT roles.It is therefore concluded that most engineering students from the city are being picked up for non-IT jobs. The poor quality of engineers in the State is directly related to the large number of colleges and the intake, the report revealed, a phenomenon which is also reflected on the national stage.States like A.P. and <STA>Tamil Nadu</STA>, which have the highest number of engineering colleges, continue to have lowest employability.States need to be conscious towards better education quality rather than building more capacity, said <ORG>Aspiring Minds</ORG> <MISC>CEO</MISC> <PER>Himanshu Aggarwal</PER>.<STA>Andhra Pradesh</STA> ranked alongside <STA>Chhattisgarh</STA>, <STA>Uttar Pradesh</STA>, <STA>Kerala</STA> and Tamil NaduReport based on graduate class of 2013, covers data from over 1.20 lakh engineering students']"
17,Atria Convergence Technologies (ACT),['Bangalore'],['ATRIA CONVERGENCE TECHNOLOGIES PRIVATE LIMITED'],"['<MISC>Tennis</MISC> taken to BBMP schoolsBangalore, Feb 22, 2013, DHNS: 1:16 ISTFor 2,000 children from 50 Palike-run schools, it was an occasion to get a feel of the game of tennis and use high speed <MISC><MISC>bro</MISC>adband Internet</MISC> for the first time, at <MISC>the <ORG>Karnataka State Lawn Tennis Associ</MISC>ation</ORG> (<ORG>KSLTA</ORG>) stadium in the City.The occasion was the launch of the International Tennis Federations (ITF)Play Tennis, an initiative aimed at providing all BBMP schools with <MISC>free internet connectivity</MISC> and empower the underprivileged children with cutting edge technology.The project also aims at making the game of <MISC>tennis</MISC> accessible to them, with shorter rackets and softer balls which provide a scientific way for a child in the 5-12 year age group to learn <MISC>tennis</MISC>. The event was jointly organised by BBMP, <ORG>Atria Convergence Technologies (ACT)</ORG>, a <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>-based <MISC>internet <MISC>broadband</MISC> ser</MISC>vice provider, and <ORG>KSLTA</ORG>.The children in the age group of 6 and 11 thronged the <MISC><ORG>KSLTA</O</MISC>RG> stadium and, for many a wide-eyed and excited kids, it was their first ever visit to the historic playing arena. The stadium, which in the past hosted World <MISC>Davis Cup</MISC> matches, ATP World doubles championship and WTA womens championship, is now all set to host the <MISC>India</MISC>-Indonesia <MISC>Davis Cup</MISC> tie during April.Launching the programme, <MISC>Deputy Chief Minister</MISC> <PER>R. Ashoka</PER> said, This provides an opportunity for the children to explore talent in sports. Often many talents are lost as there are no proper facilities to identify them.<MISC>Mayor</MISC> D Venkatesh Murthy said: For all the children present here, it is their first visit to this wonderful stadium. We are proud that BBMP is the first municipal corporation in the country to adopt an <MISC>Olympics</MISC> sport such as <MISC>tennis</MISC> in its schools and provide an opportunity for the students to excel. Hopefully this initiative would produce many champions in the future.H N Girisha, the silver Medallist at the London Paralympics, who was a special guest, was felicitated by the <ORG>KSLTA</ORG>. <PER>Ashoka</PER> presented him a cheque of Rs one lakh in recognition of <PER>his</PER> achievement.']"
18,Avesthagen,['Bangalore'],['AVESTHAGEN LIMITED'],"['The fifth convocation programme of <ORG><MISC>Karnataka State Womens Univ</ORG>ersity</MISC> (<ORG>KSWU</ORG>) will be held on the University premises on Monday.Informing that at a press conference here on Friday, <MISC>Vice-Chancellor</MISC> <PER>Meena Chandavarkar</PER> said this was for the first time, the convocation was being organised on the university premises. Past four events were held at the Ranga Mandir.<PER>Prof. Chandavarkar</PER> said the event would start around 10:30 a.m., which would be inaugurated by Higher <MISC>Education Minister</MISC> <PER>R. V. Deshpande</PER>, while <MISC>Chancellor and governor</MISC> <PER>H. R. Bharadwaj</PER> was expected to preside over the function.<PER>She</PER> informed that this time, the <ORG>University</ORG> would be giving honorary doctorate to six persons for rendering excellent service in various fields.They include, <PER>Viloo Morawala Patell</PER>, <MISC>founder chairperson and managing director</MISC> of <ORG>Avesthagen</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, <PER>Lalita Srinivasan</PER>, noted <MISC>dancer</MISC>, <PER>Maduri Devdhar</PER>, noted environmentalist, <PER>Motamma</PER>, Former <MISC>Minister</MISC> for her works to help self-help groups Meeratai Koppikar, the follower of Acharya Vinoba Bhave and <MISC>chief</MISC> of Vatsallya Dhama, and <PER>Shantadevi Kanavi</PER>, noted <MISC>writer and novelist</MISC>.<PER>Prof. Chandavarkar</PER> said during the convocation, as many as 40 gold medals would be given to students for the excellent academic performance.Of these forty gold medals, one is introduced by <MISC>Minister</MISC> <PER>R. V. Deshpande</PER> in the memory of <PER>his</PER> mother <PER>Vimalabai Deshpande</PER>, she said, and added while last year, the <ORG>university</ORG> had 34 gold medals, this year, six more have been added. In response to a query, <PER>she</PER> said the <ORG>university</ORG> was making efforts to encourage more people to introduce such gold medals, in that regard, the <ORG>university</ORG> was approaching the right people.A total of 7,035 graduates, post graduates, and diploma students would get the convocation certificate.Some 11 students would get Ph.D and nine students would be honoured with an M.Phil, <PER>he</PER> said. <ORG>Registrar S. A.</ORG> Kazi was present.With an objective of preventing any forgery of convocation certificates, the <ORG><MISC>Karnataka State Womens Univ</ORG>ersity</MISC> has for the first time introduced some security features in the convocation certificate.']"
19,Avesthagen Ltd.,['Bangalore'],['AVESTHAGEN LIMITED'],"[""<MISC>India</MISC> has become the destination of choice for providing world-class research, <MISC>clinical and manufacturing services</MISC> to the global industry, Villoo Morawala-Patell, <MISC>Founder Chairperson and Managing Director</MISC>, <ORG>Avesthagen Ltd.</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, said here on Saturday.She was delivering the second graduation day address at the JSS Mahavidyapeetha - <MISC><ORG>Sri Jayachamarajendra College of Engine</MISC>ering</ORG> (<ORG>SJCE</ORG>) here.India was being touted as the one of the key countries that would help drive the global adoption and acceptance of biotech crops in the future, she said.Innovative seed for <MISC>food</MISC>' and <MISC>food</MISC> for medicine' programmes were needed to provide a multi-faceted hedge against hunger, sickness and environmental degradation, Ms. Morawala-Patell said. <MISC>India</MISC> had become <MISC>a dominant player</MISC> in the area of <MISC><MISC>biotech</MISC>nology</MISC>, according to <MISC>the entrepreneur</MISC>.<MISC>Biotechnology</MISC> was poised to play a major role in the advent of a new future, she said.""]"
20,Axis Bank,['Hyderabad'],['AXIS BANK LIMITED'],"[""<LOC>HYDERABAD</LOC>: It now transpires that <ORG>Deccan Chronicle Holdings Ltd</ORG> borrowed nearly Rs 1584 crore through short-term and long-term loans in the last couple of years at interest rates as high as 15% from various banks and financial institutions.The loans were raised by mortgaging various properties and assets, the details of which have been declared by the company to <MISC>the Registrar</MISC> of Companies at <LOC>Hyderabad</LOC> and were downloaded by TOI on July 30 and 31, 2012, from the website of the ministry of corporate affairs.The promoters of <ORG>DCHL</ORG> raised funds from <MISC>private banks</MISC> like <ORG>ICICI Bank</ORG>, <ORG>Axis Bank</ORG>, <ORG>Yes Bank</ORG>, as well as nationalized banks like <ORG>Canara Bank</ORG> and <ORG>Corporation Bank</ORG>. They also resorted to loans from <MISC>non-banking financial institutions</MISC> like <ORG>Tata Capital Ltd</ORG> and financial institutions like <ORG>Infrastructure Development Finance Corporation (IDFC)</ORG>. Interestingly, some of these loans were obtained by the company over the past six to nine months.The company mortgaged assets not only in cities like <LOC>Hyderabad</LOC>, Chennai, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC> and even <LOC>Mumbai</LOC> and <LOC>Delhi</LOC> but also in other locations in <STA>Andhra Pradesh</STA>, it has come to light.Interestingly, <ORG>ICICI Bank</ORG> has one of the largest exposures to the troubled <ORG>DCHL</ORG>. <ORG>ICICI Bank</ORG>'s <LOC>Vadodara</LOC> branch extended loans of around Rs 490 crore to the company in mid-June this year for which a mortgage on the company's current assets and moveable property was created.<ORG>Axis Bank</ORG>, <LOC>Hyderabad</LOC>, has an exposure of Rs 300 crore and <ORG>Canara Bank</ORG>'s corporate branch at Secunderabad has lent around Rs 280 crore, including a short-term loan of Rs 30 crore extended at 14% rate of interest in <ORG>mid-March</ORG> 2012.The company offered as collateral a plot at Guindy in Chennai to <ORG>Canara Bank</ORG>, it also offered an exclusive first charge on its <MISC>printing press equipment</MISC> at Chennai and <STA>Andhra Pradesh</STA> to <ORG>Canara Bank</ORG>.The other banks with exposure to <ORG>DCHL</ORG> include <ORG>Corporation Bank</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, which has an outstanding of around Rs 100 crore, and <ORG>Yes Bank</ORG> with an exposure of Rs 144 crore.Interestingly, <ORG>DCHL</ORG>, which borrowed the money from <ORG>Yes Bank</ORG> by creating a charge on current and moveable fixed assets of <ORG>Deccan Chargers</ORG> and Odyssey in late November 2011, offered more properties at locations like <LOC>Vijayawada</LOC>, Dowleswaram village in <MISC><STA>East God</MISC>avari district</STA>, a house on Road No 14 <MISC>Banjara Hills</MISC>, as well as some properties at Green Park in <LOC>New Delhi</LOC> as collateral to the <MISC>bank</MISC> in January 2012.In fact, the company raised Rs 170 crore from <ORG>IDFC</ORG>, Chennai, at a whopping 15% interest by creating a mortgage on uncalled share capital, moveable property, book debts, revenues and receivables, intangibles as well as goodwill as late as July 2, 2012.<ORG>DCHL</ORG> also raised Rs 100 crore by way of two-year loan from <ORG>Tata Capital</ORG>, <LOC>Mumbai</LOC>, in April 2011 at 12% interest by creating a charge on immoveable property at Mathuradas Mills Compound as well as property at Lower Parel.""]"
21,Azim Premji Foundation,['Bangalore'],['AZIM PREMJI FOUNDATION'],"[""Bharathiar <ORG>School of Management</ORG> and <MISC>Entrepreneur</MISC> Development (BSMED) will host AXIS '11 at <LOC>Bangalore</LOC> on December 20.According to a release, the event is to bring together the 26-year old strong alumni of the <ORG>school</ORG> and also provides avenues for industry-institution interaction.FocusThe event will focus on ethics in business and its impact on the Indian economy.Resource persons include Sudheesh Venkatesh, <MISC>Chief People Officer</MISC>, <ORG>Azim Premji Foundation</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, K. Vaitheeshwaran, Founder and <MISC>CEO</MISC>, <MISC><MISC>India</MISC></MISC> Plaza, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, <PER>K. Shankaran</PER>, <MISC>Director</MISC>, <ORG>TTK Prestige Limited</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, <PER>Shyam Mohan</PER>, <MISC>Managing Director</MISC>, <ORG>Griffith Laboratories</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, <PER>Sesh Velamoor</PER>, <MISC>Director, Foundation</MISC> of the Future, Bellevue, the <MISC>U.S.</MISC>, and Sabbas Joseph, <MISC>Founder Director</MISC>, <PER>Wizcraft</PER>, <LOC>Mumbai</LOC>.For details, contact 0422-2428275 / 99442-50701.""]"
22,BEML Limited,['Bangalore'],['BEML LIMITED'],"['A new 8-wheeler Over Head Equipment Inspection Car has been introduced in Tiruchi division for inspection and maintenance of <MISC>overhead equipment</MISC> on electrified broad gauge rail routes.The Rs.3.69-crore self-propelled tower wagon procured from M/s. <ORG>BEML Limited</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, can be used for preventive as well as breakdown maintenance of equipment.The vehicle, which can also be used for new electrification works, will improve reliability and enable prompt restoration of overhead equipment failures in minimal time.The Tiruchi division has 217 km of electrified broad gauge lines between Villupuram and Tiruchi and Villupuram-Puducherry sections. Electrification work is in the advanced stage in the Villupuram-Vellore section.Till now, 4-wheeler tower wagons were used for maintenance of <MISC>overhead electric equipment</MISC> .The new tower wagon is equipped with a self-contained mini workshop, generator, electro-hydraulic platform lifter, double engines for fail-safe operations, inspection dome, staff rest rooms, and a kitchenette.The Inspection Car can carry all tools including masts and wires required for erecting new overhead lines. There are two generators for generating power in the wagon.Using the electro-hydraulic platform lifter, the platforms used for installing/inspecting the overhead lines can be lifted/ lowered or rotated. This platform can also be operated manually. The wagon also has an improved braking system.The wagon is powered by two independent under-slung engines.The engines are fitted under the wagon for natural cooling and there is more working space inside the wagon. It can be run at a maximum speed of 110 kmph. It can also haul a tailing wagon of 60 tonnes.The overhead lines can be inspected from an Insulated Inspection Dome provided at the top. Wiring can be done from the car itself as it is provided with masts and wires in the mini workshop, a Southern Railway press release here said.']"
23,BVG India,['Pune'],['BVG INDIA LIMITED'],"['<LOC>PUNE</LOC>: Eight years since it was mooted, the state\'s emergency response centre (ERC) that began functioning on January 26 has been sending ambulances to help people during emergencies. The centre, set up in the <ORG><MISC>Aundh Chest Ho</ORG>spital</MISC>, <LOC>Pune</LOC>, receives hundreds of calls every day.Last Monday, a bus fell into a trench when <MISC>the driver</MISC> failed to negotiate a dangerous \'S\' bend outside <MISC>Khambatki tunnel</MISC> in <STA><ORG>Satara</OR</STA>G> district. The ERC received calls and the nearest ambulance was sent to the spot.As many as 82 state-certified ambulances are now posted at public health centres in <LOC>Nashik</LOC>, Aurangabad, <ORG>Satara</ORG>, Kolhapur, <LOC>Nagpur</LOC>, Amravati and parts of the <LOC><MISC></LOC>Mumbai-<STA>Goa</S</MISC>TA> highway. As many as 937 ambulances will be posted all over the state once the <ORG>Maharashtra Emergency Medical Services (MEMS)</ORG> comes into force.Their locations have been identified and with <MISC>GPS</MISC> fittings, the software allows the operator to choose from five locations in the vicinity of the specified spot. Each ambulance has been given a geographical area of coverage and drivers have been asked to move around to acquaint themselves with the topography and locations.""We have mapped the location for all the 937 ambulances. The ERC operators will be able to identify the exact location of each <MISC>GPS</MISC> tracked and navigated ambulance, to ensure that the nearest ambulance reaches the spot,"" said <PER>Dnyaneshwar Shelke</PER>, <MISC>chief operating officer</MISC> of <ORG>MEMS</ORG>.The centre has electronic servers that can hold call data for 15 years, with sufficient power and telecom backup. The centre currently has 60 operators responding to emergencies split under 34 heads in three broad categories of fire, medical and police. As many as 614 hospitals have been identified in the state, which will admit the patients brought in by the ambulances.Soon, a police control room will be setup in the ERC to coordinate with local police stations. A team of doctors posted in the ERC 24X7 guide the medical professional in the ambulance, based on the readings of the vital stats of the patient. <MISC>Public health minister</MISC> <PER>Suresh Shetty</PER> said, ""The idea is to ensure medical aid during an emergency and reaching the <ORG>nearest hospital</ORG> at the earliest. With the police team in the ERC, there will be coordination with local police station in case of accidents or other emergencies.""The emergency medical service was first proposed after the serial bomb blasts in trains in <LOC>Mumbai</LOC> in 2006. The much-delayed and controversy-hit project still faces legal hurdles.A petition filed in the Bombay high court last month alleges that several tender specifications for the ambulances were not adhered to. <PER>Shetty</PER> said, ""<ORG>The court</ORG> case will not affect the rollout of the services as there is no stay.""H R <PER>Gaikwad</PER>, <MISC>chairman and managing director</MISC>, <ORG>BVG India</ORG>, a <LOC>Pune</LOC>-based company that is implementing the <ORG>MEMS</ORG> project for the <ORG>state government</ORG>, said they were confident of running the service successfully.']"
24,Bharat Coking Coal Company,['Dhanbad'],['BHARAT COKING COAL LIMITED'],"['<ORG>Coal India Ltd. (CIL)</ORG> closed last fiscal with a production of 462.5 million tonnes, which was 19.5 million tonnes off the target set for 2013-14. While CILs growth rate stood at 2.3 per cent, at least two of its seven <MISC>coal-producing subsidiaries</MISC> showed a drop in production.However, undeterred by the slippages, <ORG>CIL</ORG> <MISC>Chairman</MISC> <PER>S. Narsing Rao</PER> said that the company would go all out to touch the half-a-billion mark in production this year.Enquiries revealed that while five million tonnes of production was lost to Cyclone Phailin, another 6 million tonnes were lost to law and order problems or sudden bandhs called by Maoists in <STA>Jharkhand</STA> (where Central Coalfields) is headquartered, and Odisha (where Mahanadi Coalfields) is based.However, two other eastern region companies, of which one is still in the fold of the <ORG>Board for Industrial and Financial Reconstruction</ORG> (<ORG>BIFR</ORG>) have bettered the performance of their parent. While Eastern Coalfields, based in <LOC>Asansol</LOC>, is still a <ORG>BIFR</ORG> company, <ORG>Bharat Coking Coal Company</ORG>, based in <LOC>Dhanbad</LOC>, came out of the <ORG>BIFR</ORG> fold a few years ago.Eastern Coalfields closed the year with a growth rate of 6.3 per cent, exceeding its targeted production, and BCCL clocked a 4.5 per cent growth rate hitting its target on the dot. Together, these two companies accounted for 30 per cent of the 10.5 million tonne increase in production by <ORG>CIL</ORG>.Lower targetAccordingly, the memorandum of understanding that <ORG>CIL</ORG> signed with the <ORG>Coal Ministry</ORG> was for producing 507 million tonnes which is lower than the target envisaged originally.']"
25,Bharat Dynamics Limited (BDL),['Hyderabad'],['BHARAT DYNAMICS LIMITED'],"['N.B. Singh, AVSM, VSM (Retd) assumed charge as <MISC>Director</MISC> (Technical) of <ORG>Bharat Dynamics Limited (BDL)</ORG>, a <LOC>Hyderabad</LOC>-based <ORG>Miniratna</ORG> category  1 company under the <ORG>Union Ministry of Defence</ORG>.']"
26,Bharat Electronics Limited,"['Bangalore', 'Bangalore']","["" 'BHARAT ELECTRONICS LIMITED"", 'BHARAT ELECTRONICS LIMITED']","['8 experts in electronic warfare to be fetedBangalore, Sep 18, 2014, DHNS 0:38 <ORG>ISTThe Association of Old Crows</ORG>, <MISC>India</MISC> chapter, will honour eight people for their contribution to the field of Electronic Warfare (EW) at an event to be held in the City on Saturday.The best contributor award in EW from <ORG>Defence Research and Development Organisation</ORG> (<ORG>DRDO</ORG>) will be presented to J <PER>Manjula</PER>, <MISC>Scientist</MISC> H and <MISC>Director, DARE,</MISC> <ORG>DRDO</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC> and <LOC>Dr M Lakshminarayana</LOC>, <MISC>Scientist</MISC> G, DLRL, <ORG>DRDO</ORG>, <LOC>Hyderabad</LOC>.Best contributor award in EW from Indian Armed Services will be given to <PER>Capt Babu Joseph</PER>, <ORG>Indian Air Force</ORG>, presently Project <MISC>Director</MISC> (RWR & UEWS) at DARE, <ORG>DRDO</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC> and <PER>Capt Rishi Mohan</PER>, <ORG>Indian Navy</ORG>.The best contributor award in EW from public sector units will be presented to <PER>Dr Ajith T Kalghatgi</PER>, <MISC>Director</MISC> (R&D), <ORG>Bharat Electronics Limited</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC> and <PER>Philip Jacob</PER>, <MISC>Executive Directo<MISC>r, Central D&E</MISC>,</MISC> <ORG>Bharat Electronics Limited</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>.The best contributor award in EW from private industry will be given to V <PER>Anuradha</PER>, Vice President-Designs,Rangsons Defence Solutions Pvt Ltd, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC> and <PER>Col (Retd) Ramachandran Mahesh</PER>, <MISC>Program Director</MISC> (C4I &EW), <ORG>TATA Power</ORG> SED, <LOC>Hyderabad</LOC>.DH <ORG>News Service</ORG>', 'Ground breaking ceremony for the construction of 9 Mega Electron Volt Advanced Container <MISC>X-Ray</MISC> Inspection System (AXIS Project) was performed at Customs House in Tuticorin on Friday to enhance the security of the port and curb smuggling. The first stone for the Project was laid by <PER>D.K. Srinivas</PER>, <MISC>Commissioner</MISC> of Customs, followed by <PER>S. Natarajan</PER>, <MISC>Deputy Chairman</MISC> of <ORG>V.O.C. <MISC>Port</ORG> Trust.N.J</MISC>. Kumaresh, <MISC>Additional Commissioner</MISC> of Customs, explained it was a flagship project of the <ORG>Directorate of Logistics New Delhi</ORG> and would be executed by M/s <ORG>Bharat Electronics Limited</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>. M/s Smiths Detection <MISC>USA</MISC> is the supplier of the <MISC>equipment</MISC>. The Rs. 24- crore project is expected to be operational by March 2014.The state-of-the-art scanner system will use a high power <MISC>X-ray</MISC> capable of penetrating 5 <MISC>inch thick steel</MISC> and is capable of material discrimination useful to detect organic and inorganic substances with natural colour differentiation. The installation of scanner is one of the important trade facilitation measures as it can help examine the cargo without the need for opening or de-stuffing the container.']"
27,Bharat Heavy,['Jhansi'],['BHARAT HEAVY ELECTRICALS LIMITED'],"['BATHINDA: It\'s no secret that electric power is one of the main election planks for parties in <ORG>Punjab</ORG> to wield political \'power\'. Thus, after sweating it out with long power-cuts last summer, <ORG>Punjab</ORG> residents are looking forward to a comparatively comfortable summer this time, hoping there would be no power-cuts as the state is inching closer to assembly elections.Till last week, even <ORG>Punjab Power Corporation Ltd</ORG> had been assuring uninterrupted power supply during summer months this year, but now, with abig technical snag in two units of Guru Nanak Dev thermal plant in Bathinda, the state power corporation\'s arrangements to keep voters in good humour are all set to go astray. Out of four power generation units at <PER>Guru Nanak</PER> thermal plant in Bathinda, transformers of units 1 and 2 were burned last week. Unit 3 of the thermal plant has already been lying closed for over a year for renovation, so only unit 4 of the thermal plant is functional. With burning of two transformers, total power generation loss in <ORG>Punjab</ORG> is around 50 lakh units every day.Though the state power corporation has summoned a team of engineers from <ORG>Bharat Heavy</ORG> Electrical Ltd, <LOC>Jhansi</LOC>, <STA>Uttar Pradesh</STA>, to rectify the faults in transformers, there is little hope for rectification of faults in the burned transformers, which are already 37 years old. These transformers need to be replaced, an exercise that could take at least a month, said experts in the thermal plant. Kastauri Lal, <MISC>chief engineer</MISC>, <PER>Guru Nanak</PER> thermal plant, said <ORG>BHEL</ORG> engineers are expected to rectify the fault within the next 10 days. Technical staff in the thermal plant said transformers had outlived their utility. Besides causing huge power loss, burning of transformers will increase the financial burden on the state power corporation to increase its power purchasing targets from other states, said sources.In keeping with the wishes of the ruling party in <ORG>Punjab</ORG>, the state power corporation has already reportedly set a target- to spend over Rs 5,500 crore on purchase of power from other states. With burning of transformers, the burden on the power corporation has increased as the cotton cultivation season has already started and paddy plantation time is fast approaching. With the temperature increasing, power consumption is thus registering a steep rise. The corporation <MISC>chief managing directo<MISC>r</MISC> KD Chaudhary</MISC> said the power supply to the domestic connections in the state would be uninterrupted as <ORG>Punjab</ORG> had already signed power purchase agreements with various sources to import <MISC>electricity</MISC> from other states. ""We are committed to providing eight hours power supply to the agriculture sector every day,"" said <PER>Chaudhary</PER>, saying almost all tubewell-feeders had been separated from domestic ones so as to ensure <MISC>round-the-clock electricity supply</MISC> to all villages in <ORG>Punjab</ORG>.This would also provide roundthe-clock drinking water supply in rural areas, <PER>he</PER> said. So, in the election year, when the <ORG>state government</ORG> wants to keep all sections of society, agriculture, domestic and industrial consumers in good humour, the state power corporation, with its weak finances, is facing a testing time.']"
28,Bharat Heavy Electricals Limited,['New Delhi'],['BHARAT HEAVY ELECTRICALS LIMITED'],"['P. Manikandan, <MISC>Correspondent</MISC>, <ORG><MISC>Shanmuganathan Engineering C</ORG>ollege</MISC>, Thirumayam, <STA>Pudukottai district</STA>, giving away certificates to students;a workshop on personality development under way at <ORG><MISC>AVC C</ORG>ollege</MISC>, Mayiladuthurai; <MISC><ORG>Cheran College of Engine</MISC>ering</ORG> conducting a model examination in mathematics for Plus Two students in Karur.<MISC><ORG>Cheran College of Engine</MISC>ering</ORG> conducted a model examination in mathematics for Plus Two students. More than 1,000 students from 60 schools in and around Karur wrote the model examination, says a press release from the <ORG>college</ORG>. The examination was meant to help students overcome examination fear and develop time management skills. <PER>K. Karuppanan</PER>, <MISC>chairman</MISC>, and <PER>R. Manoharan</PER>, <MISC>secretary</MISC>, wished all success for the students in the public examinations.Workshop on electrical projectsTwo hundred students from various polytechnic colleges in Tiruchi, Pudukottai, Sivaganga, Ramanathapuram, and Thanjavur districts took part in a two-day workshop on electrical projects using microcontroller. The workshop, which was organised by <ORG><MISC>Shanmuganathan Engineering C</ORG>ollege</MISC>, Thirumayam, <STA>Pudukottai district</STA>, and <ORG>Interlogicx Embedded Solutions</ORG>, Puducherry, was inaugurated by <PER>Ragavan</PER>, former <MISC>senior manager</MISC>, <ORG>Bharat Heavy Electricals Limited</ORG>, <LOC>New Delhi</LOC>.<PER>Vijayakumar</PER>, <MISC>senior manager</MISC>, <ORG>Interlogicx Embedded Solutions</ORG>, and <PER>his</PER> team members handled a practical session. Pichappa Manikandan, <MISC>Correspondent</MISC>, gave away certificates to the participants in the presence of KL. Muthuramu, Principal.Focus on personality developmentTarget CE of <ORG><MISC>AVC C</ORG>ollege</MISC>, Mayiladuthurai, and <ORG>Lions Club</ORG> of Mayiladuthurai New Century organised a workshop on personality development for students preparing for the civil services examination. A total of 135 students participated in the workshop. <PER>K. Thiyagesan</PER>, former principal, <ORG><MISC>AVC C</ORG>ollege</MISC>, was the resource person.Need for ethics in researchV. <PER>Manickavasagam</PER>, <MISC>Registrar</MISC>, <ORG><MISC>Alagappa Univ</ORG>ersity</MISC>, stressed the importance of ethics in research and publishing books and articles. Inaugurating a one-week faculty development programme on research methodology at the <MISC><ORG>Bharathidasan Unive</MISC>rsity</ORG> here, <PER>he</PER> said researchers and authors should be sensitised to the importance of ethics while undertaking research projects and publishing books.It would enhance the quality of research and creativity in writing books. Each and every <MISC>researcher</MISC> and guide should give top priority for ethics in research.Students, staff, infrastructure and governance were the four pillars of higher education, <PER>Mr. Manickavasagam</PER> said. <PER>D. Muthuramakrishnan</PER> and <PER>T. Nallathambi</PER>, syndicate members, <MISC><ORG>Bharathidasan Unive</MISC>rsity</ORG>, N. Murugeswari, <MISC>Publication Officer</MISC>, and <PER>Lakshmi Prabha</PER>, <MISC>Associate Professor</MISC>, <MISC>Plant Science</MISC>, spoke. <PER>Mr. Muthuramakrishnan</PER> stressed the need to upgrade the infrastructure for publication relating to workshops and seminars.Contributed by C. Jaisankar and G. Prasad.']"
29,Bharat Heavy Electricals Ltd. (BHEL),['Bangalore'],['BHARAT HEAVY ELECTRICALS LIMITED'],"['The Electronics Division of <ORG>Bharat Heavy Electricals Ltd. (BHEL)</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, on Friday celebrated Karnataka Rajyotsava.The programme also featured an exhibition-cum-sale of Kannada books and Karnataka Janapada Siri  an introduction to folk culture of <STA>Karnataka</STA> by <ORG>BHEL</ORG> artistes. It also felicitated employee-artistes and employees retiring in the next one year, along with several distinguished personalities.']"
30,Bharat Petroleum Corporation Limited,['Mumbai'],['BHARAT PETROLEUM CORPORATION LIMITED'],"['<LOC>NAGPUR</LOC>: There can be no better <MISC>teacher</MISC> for farmers than <MISC>a farmer</MISC> himself. Following this principle, the <ORG>MS Swaminathan Research Foundation</ORG> (<ORG>MSSRF</ORG>) is promoting <MISC><MISC>sustainable farming techno</MISC>logies</MISC> among farmers with the help of other farmers. For this, the <ORG>foundation</ORG> is setting up \'farm schools\' where the farmers can learn farming techniques from other farmers who have already implemented them successfully.<ORG>MSSRF</ORG> has set up two farm schools in <STA>Tamil Nadu</STA> and one each in <STA>Kerala</STA> and Odisha. The fifth, and the only one in <STA>Maharashtra</STA>, was inaugurated in Takarkheda village in Arvi block in <STA>Wardha district</STA> on Friday by <MISC>the foundation chairman</MISC> MS Swaminathan. The school has come up on the premises of Sri Sant Lahanuji Maharaj Sansthan with support from <PER>Suresh Pawde</PER>, an agriculture expert who is also <MISC>the secretary</MISC> of the sansthan and engaged in running the Village Resource/Knowledge Centres (VRCs) by the <ORG>foundation</ORG> in <STA>Wardha district</STA>.<PER>Swaminathan</PER> told TOI that the farm school was based on the idea of \'land-to-land\' where a successful <MISC>farmer</MISC> shares <PER>his</PER> technology with fellow farmers from the area. The school at Takarkheda has brought together farmers who cultivate same crops and will be conducting season-wise training and demonstration programmes. ""Basic purpose of these farm schools is to facilitate increase in knowledge and skills of farmers through land-to-land approach. The farmer-to-farmer learning can be an effective method of transferring technology and innovations among farmers to help them overcome the risks and challenges associated with agriculture,"" said <PER>Swaminathan</PER>.Keeping with the <ORG>foundation</ORG>\'s thrust on ensuring <MISC>food</MISC> and nutrition security at all levels and leveraging agriculture for this, the Takarkheda school in particular will focus on training and awareness about production practices related to <MISC>food crops</MISC> that have high nutritive value. Besides addressing the farm community in general, programmes will also be designed to address specific needs of women farmers with whom the <ORG>MSSRF</ORG> is working in the region.The farm school is governed by a steering committee comprising agricultural experts from government departments in the district, Krishi Vigyan Kendra, research institutions and progressive farmers of the region. Good agriculture practices will be also documented and disseminated to the farmers of the region. The first-of-its-kind in the region, this school will also be able to use two soil testing laboratories already established in the VRCs in Wardha and Yavatmal districts by <ORG>MSSRF</ORG> in partnership with <ORG>Bharat Petroleum Corporation Limited</ORG>, <LOC>Mumbai</LOC>.Basically, the farm schools project is a <ORG>CSR</ORG> initiative of <ORG>Indian Overseas Bank</ORG> (IOB) being implemented by <ORG>MSSRF</ORG>. The <ORG>foundation</ORG>\'s <MISC>executive director</MISC> <PER>Ajay K Parida</PER>, <PER>Aswin Kumar Jamadagni</PER>, <MISC>chief regional manager</MISC> of <ORG>IOB Bhavani RV</ORG> and <PER>Nancy J Anabel</PER> from the <ORG>foundation</ORG> were also present on the occasion.* A residential school set up on an agriculture field where farmers learn cultivation methods being practised by successful farmers* Run on the principle of land-to-land transfer of technology from one <MISC>farmer</MISC> to another* Scientists basically teach new technologies to progressive farmers and they pass it on to other farmers through horizontal transfer of knowledge']"
31,Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd,['Mumbai'],['BHARAT PETROLEUM CORPORATION LIMITED'],"['Rs 10L ex gratia sought for tanker accident victimsSeptember 5, 2015,Bengaluru/Manipal, DHNS 2:37 <MISC>ISTIndustries minister</MISC> R V Deshpande has sought Rs 10 lakh compensation from the <ORG>Ministry of Petroleum and Natural Gas</ORG> for the victims of LPG tanker explosion in Kumta, in <STA>Uttar Kannada district</STA>, on September 1.In a letter dated September 3, addressed to <MISC>Union Minister</MISC> <PER>Dharmendra Pradhan</PER> and <PER>Varadarajan</PER>, <MISC>Chairman and Managing Director</MISC>, <ORG>Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd</ORG>, <LOC>Mumbai</LOC>, Desphande has sought an interim relief amount of Rs two lakh to the families of the deceased.Of the 15 persons injured, five have succumbed to their injuries.The rest have sustained more than 90 per cent injuries, and are in a critical condition. They are in no position to earn their livelihood even if they were to survive the accident, <PER>he</PER> has said.<PER>He</PER> has also sought compensation for losses of movable and immovable property at market rates.One more injured diesMeanwhile, one more person injured in the accident died at <MISC><ORG>KMC Hos</MISC>pital</ORG> in Manipal on Friday. With this, the toll in the mishap went to six, five of them from a family.The deceased is <PER>Dheeraj</PER>, 18, from <PER>Bargi</PER> in Kumta. <PER>He</PER> is the son of <PER>Srikanth Bargi</PER> (57) and Jayashri (54) who succumbed to the burn injuries on Wednesday and Thursday respectively. With this, the death toll in the family has risen to five.Doctors at <ORG><MISC>Kasturba Ho</ORG>spital</MISC> said that condition of three others was critical. As many as 14 persons with burn injuries were brought to the <ORG>hospital</ORG> on September 1.Another patient who was treated at Kumta government hospital is admitted to the <ORG><MISC>Kasturba ho</ORG>spital</MISC> for treatment. <PER>He</PER> has suffered minor burn injuries.']"
32,Bharat Sanchar Nigam Limited,"['Coimbatore', 'Vijayawada', 'Coimbatore']","["" 'BHARAT SANCHAR NIGAM LIMITED"", "" 'BHARAT SANCHAR NIGAM LIMITED"", "" 'BHARAT SANCHAR NIGAM LIMITED""]","['<ORG>Bharat Sanchar Nigam Limited</ORG>, <LOC>Coimbatore</LOC>, is offering a summer training programme on fundamentals of telecommunication to college students.A release said the programme, aimed at benefitting the student community, would start on May 5, 10, 16 and 23.Limited seatsStudents should book seats to participate in the programme as only limited seats were available. Those interested may contact Rangasamy SDE (HRD) on <MISC>94861-05243</MISC> or <ORG>JTO Training Centre</ORG> on <MISC>94861-05161</MISC> for further details.', 'Employees and officials of <ORG>Bharat Sanchar Nigam Limited</ORG>, <LOC>Vijayawada</LOC>, on Tuesday launched a lunch-hour demonstration on the premises of <ORG>BSNL</ORG> Bhavan in protest against what they called anti-employee stand of the government.They were protesting against slashing of the retirement age to 58, implementation of voluntary retirement scheme, and merger of loss-making units with <ORG>BSNL</ORG>.', 'The <ORG>Bharat Sanchar Nigam Limited</ORG>, <LOC>Coimbatore</LOC>, will conduct <MISC>broadband</MISC> customers meetings on Monday. Meetings would be held at <MISC>Coimbatore Principal General</MISC> Managers office on Mettupalayam Road in <LOC>Coimbatore</LOC>, <MISC>telephone exchange</MISC> near <MISC>Tirupur Railway Station</MISC>, Mettupalayam <MISC>telephone exchange</MISC>, Avinashi <MISC>telephone exchange</MISC>, Palladam <MISC>telephone exchange</MISC>, Pollachi <MISC>telephone exchange</MISC>, and Udumalpet telephone exchange.Customers may avail of the opportunity to have their <MISC>broadband</MISC> related grievances redressed.']"
33,Bharat Sanchar Nigam Limited (BSNL),['Nashik'],['BHARAT SANCHAR NIGAM LIMITED'],"['<LOC>NASHIK</LOC>: Having achieved 99.39% fault clearance within seven days of filing a complaint in case of landlines, the <ORG>Bharat Sanchar Nigam Limited (BSNL)</ORG>, <LOC>Nashik</LOC>, is now aiming to repair faults within a span of three days.""We have achieved the seven-day-mark in clearing the faults registered by consumers. Hence, we were able to promise repayment of rentals for the numbers of days for which the services remain unrestored after a period of seven days to the consumers. We are now tightening our belts to achieve the same in three days - the percentage of which currently is at 87.43%,"" <MISC>general manager</MISC> of <ORG>BSNL</ORG> Nashik, <PER>Praveen Malhotra</PER> told TOI.The <ORG>BSNL</ORG> had announced in the middle of 2012 that it would clear the faults - landline as well as <MISC>broadband</MISC> - within a stipulated time of seven days. The company had, therefore, announced that the connections that were not restored on or after the seventh day would be compensated with reduced rentals, depending on the number of days the connection was defunct.Since then the <MISC>fault repairing services</MISC> were strictly monitored and efforts were taken to ensure that the faults were cleared in the minimum possible time.During the month of January 2013, the fault booking system registered 5,568 faults in landline while 1,264 faults in <MISC>broadband</MISC> connections. While 59% of the faults in both the categories were resolved in a single day, nearly 88% were cleared on the third day and by seventh day, 99.13% were cleared.""Considering that the fault clearance by the seventh day has now reached the ultimate, we have decided to focus on the three-day promise, though we have not announced about the compensation yet,"" <PER>Malhotra</PER> said.""We are having dialogues with our linesmen and other field staff to ensure that things go smoother on the ground. The timely fault rectification has not only contributed to better services for the customers, it has also helped in the growth of revenueas the system would lay idle for the minimum time and thus result in revenue generation,"" <PER>he</PER> said']"
34,Bharati Shipyard Limited,['Mumbai'],['BHARATI SHIPYARD LIMITED'],"['<ORG>Karwar Coast Guard</ORG> gets ultramodern interceptor boatFeb 19, 2015, <MISC>Karwar</MISC>, Dhns 2:58 ISTThe coastal security in <STA>Uttara Kannada district</STA> is set to get a boost with the ultramodern C-155 interceptor boat reaching the Indian Coast <MISC>Guard</MISC> Station at <MISC>Karwar port</MISC> on Wednesday.The Rs 30-crore vessel built by the <ORG>Bharati Shipyard Limited</ORG>, <LOC>Mumbai</LOC>, is capable of patrolling the coast for 10 hours uninterruptedly. The 27.6 m-long boat weighs 71 tonnes and can sail at a speed of 35 nautical miles per hour (64.82 kmph). It is equipped with a radar system which can detect water-borne and air-borne objects up to a distance of 45 nautical miles.The boat is armed with a heavy and light machine gun among other weapons. A team of 10 personnel led by <PER>Commandant Jagannath Behr</PER> will be in charge of the boat. It is expected to be commissioned in March this year.DH <ORG>News Service</ORG>']"
35,Bosch Rexroth India,['Bangalore'],['BOSCH REXROTH (INDIA) LIMITED'],"['The <ORG>VTU-Bosch <ORG>Rexroth Centr</ORG>e of Competence</ORG> in <MISC>Automation Technology</MISC> in the city will be upgraded into a world-class facility to meet the exacting standards of the industry.<MISC>Visvesvaraya <ORG>Technological Unive</MISC>rsity</ORG> (<ORG>VTU</ORG>) <MISC>Vice-Chancellor</MISC> <PER>H. Maheshappa</PER> told mediapersons here on Thursday that there were plans to open a similar centre in <LOC>Bangalore</LOC> to upgrade the faculty, students passing out of engineering colleges, and working professionals.In a significant departure from the norm, the <ORG>centre</ORG>, which trains graduates in engineering and working professionals, would also train diploma students and those passing out of ITIs, <PER>he</PER> said.The Mysore centre was established in 2007 and has helped bridge the gap between the industry and the academia. Over 2,000 students and 600 faculty members from different technical institutions in the State have availed themselves of the facilities here, according to <PER>Dr. Maheshappa</PER>.<PER>He</PER> said the demand for skilled professionals in the automated age was immense, but there was a shortage of trained manpower. Hence the <ORG>VTU</ORG> and <ORG>Bosch Rexroth</ORG> have joined hands to provide programmes in <MISC><MISC>automation tech</MISC>nology</MISC> to meet the requirements of the industry.<PER>He</PER> said the <ORG>VTU</ORG> had braced up to meet the requirements of the industry through tie-ups with the later and had introduced courses that obviated the need for industries to train freshers. Expanding the facility required greater investment from the industry.However, <PER>he</PER> said, none of the bigwigs in the <MISC><MISC>information tech</MISC>nology sector</MISC>, including a few home-grown ones, had bothered to invest in the universities to help upgrade skills of students.<PER>Rajkumar</PER>, <MISC>executive vice-president</MISC>, <ORG>Bosch Rexroth India</ORG>, <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>, said the <ORG>Mysore centre</ORG> had laboratories in hydraulics, pneumatics, robotics and mechatronics. A laboratory for imparting training in electrical drives and controls would also be established soon.Commenting on the demand and supply situation in the field of automation industry, <PER>Mr. Rajkumar</PER> pointed out that only 6 to 8 per cent of the nearly 5 lakh engineering graduates passing out in the country every year were deemed employable.<PER>Peter Gorzya</PER>, <MISC>head</MISC> of <ORG>Drive and Control Academy</ORG>, <ORG>Bosch Rexroth</ORG>, <MISC>Germany</MISC>, and K.R. Prakash, <MISC>Special Officer</MISC>, <ORG>VTU</ORG>-BR Centre, Mysore, were present.It will also train diploma students and those passing out of it: VTU Vice-ChancellorThere is a plan to open a similar centre in <LOC>Bangalore</LOC>']"
