ASHOK BHANUSHALI TRIKAMJI 	 GUJARAT POLY AVX ELECTRONICS LTD. 
 593550b57be9e061b17364d4 Vadodara: Two heads of <ORG>GUJARAT POLY AVX ELECTRONICS LTD.</ORG>-based IT companies will represent the state in the National Association of Software and Services Companies (NASSCOM) - the national body representing technology companies.While <PER>ASHOK BHANUSHALI TRIKAMJI</PER>, CEO of city-based <ORG>5ce4ca998c5a90d849783e70</ORG> was nominated as member of the NASSCOM national SME council; <PER>5ce4c9738c5a90d849753f9c</PER>, managing director of Ahmedabad-based <ORG>5ce4ca998c5a90d849783e6e</ORG>, was appointed as chairman of the NASSCOM domestic council."It is for the first time that NASSCOM has set up a SME council which has been formed to focus and drive SME specific agenda and issues to help them overcome challenges, increase revenue and global footprint," said <PER>ASHOK BHANUSHALI TRIKAMJI</PER>, vice-chairman of the <ORG>GUJARAT POLY AVX ELECTRONICS LTD.</ORG> and Software Industries Association (<ORG>GUJARAT POLY AVX ELECTRONICS LTD.</ORG>) - the body that represents information and technology companies of <ORG>GUJARAT POLY AVX ELECTRONICS LTD.</ORG>.<PER>5ce4c9738c5a90d849753f9c</PER>, former president of <ORG>GUJARAT POLY AVX ELECTRONICS LTD.</ORG> was part of the executive committee of NASSCOM.The national SME council has representation of members from all the NASSCOM regional councils."In the current times, when the big players are going through turbulence, all eyes are towards SMEs as they are growing well but need support for further scalability. <ORG>GUJARAT POLY AVX ELECTRONICS LTD.</ORG> with at least 1,000 IT SMEs is thriving on this front," said <PER>ASHOK BHANUSHALI TRIKAMJI</PER>, adding that around 50 percent NASSCOM members are also SMEs. "<ORG>GUJARAT POLY AVX ELECTRONICS LTD.</ORG> is now increasingly getting visibility on IT map and stage of India. We are very happy and proud of this," <PER>ASHOK BHANUSHALI TRIKAMJI</PER> said. 
 --------------------------------------------------
ANAND SINGH RATTANDEEP 	 HOTEL AND RESTAURANT ASSOCIATION OF NORTHERN INDIA .. 
 59293fc77be9e0138af8d8cd A closed liquor outlet in Chandigarh on Saturday. Kamleshwar Singh A closed liquor outlet in Chandigarh on Saturday. Kamleshwar SinghTelangana & Andhra PradeshLiquor shops along the highways in Telangana and Andhra Pradesh functioned normally on Saturday despite of the Supreme Court ban as licences are valid till September 30 and June 30, respectively in both states.As the Supreme Court modified its direction on Friday, stating that the existing licences will be valid till September 30, both Telangana and Andhra Pradesh governments wont ask liquor shops on highways to close down or shift immediately.We have plenty of time to enforce the Supreme Court guidelines because all liquor shop licences are valid till September 30 in Telangana. When we auction the licences again this September, we will ensure that Supreme Court guidelines are followed and no shop comes up within 220 metres of the highways, Deputy Commissioner of Excise of Telangana S Qureshi said.In Telangana, there are 1,040 liquor shops on highways. About 500 of these shops are on NH-65 and NH-44, and depending on the location, owners paid Rs 30 lakh to Rs 1.10 crore for licences.The liquor shops are often located at places with good accessibility and business advantage. If we suddenly shift to a new location, we may lose all our old customers, said <PER>5ce4c9ea8c5a90d849767fdd</PER>, owner of Manjunadha Wines on NH-65 where there are at least 300 liquor shops.Excise and police officials are conducting checks at restaurants which have bars attached to discourage them from serving liquor. Action would be taken if they violate the guidelines, Telangana Excise Minister T <PER>5ce4c9ea8c5a90d849767fda</PER> said.In Andhra Pradesh, there are 1,090 liquor outlets on highways, most of them on the coastal NH-16, and Hyderabad-Vijayawada highway. The liquor licence auction was held in June last year and the licences are valid till June 30 this year.We have closed the bars and pubs located on the highways. Restaurants on highways cannot serve liquor and they have to close their bars. The liquor shops will function till June 30 after which we will conduct auction based on the new guidelines, Andhra Pradesh Excise Minister <PER>5ce4c9ea8c5a90d849767fd5</PER> said.KarnatakaWith the existing liquor licences being valid till June 30, liquor outlets on the highways in Karnataka have around three months to move to locations outside highway zones to be considered for renewal of their licences.Out of the 10,149 liquor licences issued by the Karnataka Excise Department for liquor stores, bars and hotels, as many as 5,950 licences are with the outlets located within 500 metres of highways  2,510 wine shops, 1,599 bars, 219 star hotels and 173 clubs.The number will be fewer if a distance of 220 metres is taken in areas with a population that is less than 20,000. The Supreme Court had modified its liquor ban order, reducing the distance to 220 metres in areas having a population of up to 20,000.JharkhandOfficials claimed that there were no liquor vends open along the highways beginning Saturday, and a consolidated report would be prepared over the next couple of days.Its a Supreme Court order. We are following it. Various factors arising out of it are being considered and we will prepare a consolidated report, said Excise Secretary <PER>5ce4c9ea8c5a90d849767fcf</PER>.Of the total 1,432 liquor shops, the state Excise Department has identified at least 670 shops that fall within 500 metres of the highways.As of today all the liquor shops on the highways are closed. Either the operators have closed it on their own or we have sealed them, said another Excise official.With the Jharkhand government planning to enter retail liquor business, over 500 retail liquor vendors have not got their licences extended till August.HaryanaThe Haryana government is likely to lose annual revenue of Rs 100 crore as the state has to close 40 per cent of the total 478 bars located in hotels and restaurants in the state. Most of the bars licensed in Haryana are situated near the highways.On Saturday, Haryana Additional Chief Secretary (Excise and Taxation) <PER>5ce4c39c8c5a90d84965b3c4</PER> confirmed that 194 bars wont be allowed to serve liquor from now on. Its not only the bar licence feebars also attract customers to eat.Those who eat also pay VAT (Value Added Tax) to the state. Loss to the state exchequer would be Rs 100 crore plus because of closure of the barsBars can be relocated but its not easy for the big hotels to move from the current locations, said <PER>5ce4c39c8c5a90d84965b3c4</PER>.But the state government seems relaxed on the issue of liquor vends as it had already made a point in its excise policy that the liquor vends wont be allowed within 500 metres of the highways. We have already auctioned 92 per cent of liquor vends that fall outside the range of 500 m from the highways, said the Additional Chief Secretary.PunjabPunjab Excise department has suspended the licences of about 2500 liquor outlets across the state. Sources said the permits of serving liquor to all such establishments on state and national highways stand cancelled.Not a single outlet served liquor in Punjab on Saturday, said a senior Excise department official. <PER>5ce4c39c8c5a90d84965b3c4</PER> said the department was in the process of compiling the exact number of outlets. We will take a day or two to compile. We have about 1,200 hotels within 500 metres and the rest are other outlets, <PER>5ce4c39c8c5a90d84965b3c4</PER> said.The hotels and marriage venues have, however, contested the number of establishments affected by the order. Over 10,000 outlets, including 3,000 wedding venues, have been affected. Our business has been hit overnight. We are already getting cancellation orders, said <PER>5ce4c9ea8c5a90d849767fce</PER>, President of Punjab Marriage Palaces-Resorts Owners Association.The <ORG>5ce4c9ea8c5a90d849767fd4</ORG>HOTEL AND RESTAURANT ASSOCIATION OF NORTHERN INDIA ..</ORG> has planned to file a review petition in the Supreme Court. Confirming the same, <PER>ANAND SINGH RATTANDEEP</PER>, vice-president of North India <ORG>HOTEL AND RESTAURANT ASSOCIATION OF NORTHERN INDIA ..</ORG>, said,We will be having an all India meeting on April 5 in New Delhi where we will be discussing the review petition.In Ludhiana, 143 vends were located on highways out of which 34 vends will be relocated and licences of rest will not be renewed.Though the SC order was implemented from April 1, all Ludhiana liquor contractors had shut down their vends for about a week. Annual auction of vends was postponed twice on March 29 as well as March 31 and now new dates are yet to be given. Auction has been postponed twice even in Bathinda, Moga, Sangrur districts with contractors boycotting the auction process.West BengalWest Bengal has about 1,800 off-shops within 500 metres of highways, generating a total of over Rs 1,000 crore in revenue for the state, said the state Excise Department. An off shop is essentially a retail outlet that just sells liquor.Last week, the government attempted to preserve its excise revenue by tweaking its liquor licensing policy, by turning off-shops located within 500 metre from the highways into sit-and-drink outlets  a move that the government claimed was within the realm of the SC order. However, the apex courts clarification has now blocked this escape route.An excise department official said, We are following SCs orders and all shops, restaurants and bars that were within the purview of the order have been shut down.The government has targeted excise revenue of Rs 4,778 core in 2016-17. Officials said the state was on course to achieve the target. In 2017-18, the government has budgeted excise collections of Rs 5,781.38 crore.MaharashtraNearly 15,699 liqour outlets shut down in Maharashtra in compliance with the apex courts order. While retail outlets had to shut shop, permit rooms, clubs and hotels had to stop serving liqour.It is a sad day for our industry. It is not only the fear of losing out on business, but hundreds of people working in this industry have lost out on their jobs today, said <PER>5ce4c9ea8c5a90d849767fdc</PER>, president of the Indian <ORG>HOTEL AND RESTAURANT ASSOCIATION OF NORTHERN INDIA ..</ORG>.According to some analysts, Maharashtra has a 12-14 per cent share of the total liquor market. The industry contributes nearly Rs 13,000 crore as revenue in the form of excise through the 25,513 liqour vending licencees in the state.Of these, nearly 15,699 licencees lie within the 500 metre distance from highways. We respect the Supreme Court but are angry with the way the state has handled the issue. Last week we were told that we could continue our business as usual and yesterdays decision has come as a shock. We should at least have been allowed to clear out the stocks in our shops, a beer bar owner from Ghatkopar said.Interestingly, the state government, which fears a loss of Rs 7,000 crore in revenue because of the move, has found a novel way to skirt the ban. In Jalgaon, the government on Friday decided to hand over nearly 20 km of highway to the Jalgaon Municipal Corporation.The move meant that these highways were denotified as city roads to be maintianed by the Corporation, which will allow liquor outlets to continue operations on these roads.The Pune Association of Hoteliers and Restaurants, meanwhile, blamed the state and municipal authorities for failing to denotify old highways which are in the heart of the city and have been replaced by new highways bypassing the cities.There are about 1,950 restaurants in Pune municipality that sell liquor. Out of this as many as 1,600 have been affected by the order, said <PER>5ce4c9ea8c5a90d849767fd8</PER>, president of the association.Hotel owners are now planning to move the Supreme Court with a review petition seeking a remedy of the order.KeralaAround 1,700 liquor vends were forced to shut down in Kerala. Besides, state-run liquor retailers, Bevco and Consumerfed, will now have to relocate 148 outlets from highways out of their 311 shops.Kerala Excise Minister G Sudhakaran said: We are in the process of relocating state-run retail outlets to comply with the SC order. The resistance from locals in places identified for relocation has delayed the process. In case of beer and wine parlours identified for closure, the Excise Department is in the process of sealing the remaining stocks.Of 5,100 toddy shops, 1,080 are located on the highways. Out of 30 five-star category hotels, 11 have had to suspend liquor bar operations. Among the states 34 clubs, 18 cannot operate bars as per the Supreme Court directive.Kerala Finance Minister <PER>5ce4c4b58c5a90d849688c6c</PER> said the decision would impact states revenue. A rough estate showed that the state would lose a revenue of Rs 2,200 crore, <PER>5ce4c4b58c5a90d849688c6c</PER> said.In 2015, when the government banned liquor sale in bars, we had converted them into beer parlours. Without beer business, these hotels would not get any business, said Kerala Beer and Wine Parlours Association president <PER>5ce4c9ea8c5a90d849767fdb</PER>, adding that the 5000 jobs are likely to be hit in wake of the latest ban.GujaratThe Gujarat home department has instructed the states prohibition department to temporarily shut such wine shops operating on highways in the state.A dry state, there were reported to be 56 licensed liquor shops in Gujarat, of which 12 are on highways. On instruction from the home department, the Director of Prohibition and Excise Department B K <PER>5ce4c9ea8c5a90d849767fdd</PER> said that officers had been instructed to shut down wine shops operating on highways temporarily.<PER>5ce4c9ea8c5a90d849767fdd</PER> said, For now, we have asked various Superintendents to temporarily close the wine shops doing retail sale. Based on inputs from the legal department which are awaited by the home department, we may also shut wine shops on highways down permanently In Ahmedabad close to three hotels located on highways including Novotel, TGB and The Ramada have wine shops.<PER>5ce4c9ea8c5a90d849767fd7</PER>, general manager of Novotel Hotel in Ahmedabad, said that while the hotel was awaiting directives on what to do, it was also getting a legal opinion to get more clarity.For all the latest India News, download Indian Express App now 
 --------------------------------------------------
GADICHERLA SUBBA RAO 	 SVS PRODUCTS PRIVATE LIMITED 
 593ade907be9e078a69ddb52 Individual buildings, duplex and apartment complexes will form part of the <ORG>SVS PRODUCTS PRIVATE LIMITED</ORG> Mega Township being constructed at Ganganapalli village on the city outskirts, according to <PER>GADICHERLA SUBBA RAO</PER>, managing director of <ORG>SVS PRODUCTS PRIVATE LIMITED</ORG>Foundation stone was laid for the construction of the township on Wednesday and the firm opened its office at Narasanna Nagar. 
 --------------------------------------------------
SIDHI PARKASH JAIN 	 RELIANCE INFRATEL LIMITED 
 593cf1417be9e00dabcbb056 The Central Bureau of Investigation has arrested six persons in three cases of financial irregularities pertaining to iron-ore mines causing a loss of over Rs.167 crore to the national exchequer.Among those arrested is <PER>5ce4ccad8c5a90d8497de9e1</PER>, a former Additional Managing Director (AMD) of the National Agricultural Cooperative Marketing Federation of India (NAFED).In 2005, during <PER>5ce4ccad8c5a90d8497de9e1</PER> tenure as AMD, <PER>5ce4ccad8c5a90d8497de9e1</PER> is alleged to have conspired with private firms, issued them post-dated cheques and loans without any collaterals. <PER>5ce4ccad8c5a90d8497de9e1</PER> now holds the post of Commissioner of Income Tax in Agra.The others arrested are: <PER>5ce4c8988c5a90d84972d785</PER>, proprietor of Roshal Lal Lalit Mohan; <PER>5ce4ccad8c5a90d8497de9e2</PER>, chairman-cum-managing director of Zenith Mining Private Ltd. (ZMPL); Vinod Gupta, joint MD of ZMPL; <PER>SIDHI PARKASH JAIN</PER>, chairman-cum-managing director of <ORG>RELIANCE INFRATEL LIMITED</ORG>; and <PER>5ce4ccad8c5a90d8497de9e4</PER>, Chief Executive Officer of ITM Impex Private Ltd.The cases were transferred to the CBI from the Delhi Police by a court. 
 --------------------------------------------------
MOHAN KAMESHWARAN 	 MADRAS ENT RESEARCH FOUNDATION PRIVATE LIMITED 
 593d0e497be9e00dabcbc5d1 <PER>5ce4c32a8c5a90d84964965d</PER>, former director, UIORL, having a word with <PER>5ce4ccbd8c5a90d8497e13ba</PER>, Director, UIORL, at the inauguration of the cochlear implantees habilitation club of RGGGH in Chennai on Wednesday. <PER>MOHAN KAMESHWARAN</PER>, director, <ORG>MADRAS ENT RESEARCH FOUNDATION PRIVATE LIMITED</ORG> (third from left), and <PER>5ce4c3d88c5a90d849664754</PER>, Medical Superintendent, RGGGH, are in the picture.  Photo: K. PichumaniA Habilitation club for children who have had cochlear implants, to enable them to hear and speak, was launched at the Rajiv Gandhi Government General Hospital, on Wednesday.A total of 10 children, under the age of five years, have already been fitted with cochlear implants already at the RGGGH, and about 120 children are on the waiting list, according to <PER>5ce4ccbd8c5a90d8497e13ba</PER>, director, Upgraded Institute of Otorhinolaryngology, RGGGH. The club will provide them with support services in auditory and verbal therapy in order for them to cope with the new faculty of hearing. Voice training is necessary for these children in order for them to be able to hear and articulate. Implantees will be invited twice a week for free training by the speech therapists and audiologists.The specialist ENT surgeons will follow up to see the effect of the training on the patients' speech and hearing capacity and on their IQ.<PER>MOHAN KAMESHWARAN</PER>, director, <ORG>MADRAS ENT RESEARCH FOUNDATION PRIVATE LIMITED</ORG>, acknowledged by many to be the leader in cochlear transplantations in the country, stressed the importance of auditory and verbal training for children who receive implants. Even parents of children who live in other districts of Tamil Nadu should make the effort to utilise the facilities made available at the RGGGH, <PER>MOHAN KAMESHWARAN</PER> added. The centre was inaugurated by <PER>5ce4c3d88c5a90d849664754</PER>, hospital medical superintendent. 
 --------------------------------------------------
MOHAN KAMESHWARAN 	 MADRAS ENT RESEARCH FOUNDATION PRIVATE LIMITED 
 593d0e497be9e00dabcbc5d1 <PER>5ce4c32a8c5a90d84964965d</PER>, former director, UIORL, having a word with <PER>5ce4ccbd8c5a90d8497e13ba</PER>, Director, UIORL, at the inauguration of the cochlear implantees habilitation club of RGGGH in Chennai on Wednesday. <PER>MOHAN KAMESHWARAN</PER>, director, <ORG>MADRAS ENT RESEARCH FOUNDATION PRIVATE LIMITED</ORG> (third from left), and <PER>5ce4c3d88c5a90d849664754</PER>, Medical Superintendent, RGGGH, are in the picture.  Photo: K. PichumaniA Habilitation club for children who have had cochlear implants, to enable them to hear and speak, was launched at the Rajiv Gandhi Government General Hospital, on Wednesday.A total of 10 children, under the age of five years, have already been fitted with cochlear implants already at the RGGGH, and about 120 children are on the waiting list, according to <PER>5ce4ccbd8c5a90d8497e13ba</PER>, director, Upgraded Institute of Otorhinolaryngology, RGGGH. The club will provide them with support services in auditory and verbal therapy in order for them to cope with the new faculty of hearing. Voice training is necessary for these children in order for them to be able to hear and articulate. Implantees will be invited twice a week for free training by the speech therapists and audiologists.The specialist ENT surgeons will follow up to see the effect of the training on the patients' speech and hearing capacity and on their IQ.<PER>MOHAN KAMESHWARAN</PER>, director, <ORG>MADRAS ENT RESEARCH FOUNDATION PRIVATE LIMITED</ORG>, acknowledged by many to be the leader in cochlear transplantations in the country, stressed the importance of auditory and verbal training for children who receive implants. Even parents of children who live in other districts of Tamil Nadu should make the effort to utilise the facilities made available at the RGGGH, <PER>MOHAN KAMESHWARAN</PER> added. The centre was inaugurated by <PER>5ce4c3d88c5a90d849664754</PER>, hospital medical superintendent. 
 --------------------------------------------------
NUGGEHALLI GEETHAPRABHU JAYASIMHA 	 HUMANE SOCIETY. INTERNATIONAL: INDIA 
 5903b7e87be9e0266aeadf7a Humane Society International-India has offered a reward of up to Rs. 50,000 for any useful information regarding the death of scores of monkeys at Pandavapura.<PER>NUGGEHALLI GEETHAPRABHU JAYASIMHA</PER>, director of <ORG>HUMANE SOCIETY. INTERNATIONAL: INDIA</ORG>-India, said cash rewards would be given to those giving information that leads to the identification, arrest and conviction of those responsible for the mass killing. The organisation has also sent a notice under Section 55 of the Wildlife Protection Act to the <ORG>5ce4c5ed8c5a90d8496bcb32</ORG> seeking a thorough probe. 
 --------------------------------------------------
KAILASH KUMAR GOYAL 	 EXPORT PROMOTION COUNCIL FOR HANDICRAFTS 
 58ff226a7be9e0429666ddfe The 43rd edition of IHGF- Delhi Fair Spring, 2017, which began on Thursday in Greater Noida, is showcasing sustainable lifestyle products from the northeast and Jodhpur.The fair is being held at India Expo Centre and Mart (IEM) till February 20. More than 3, 000 exhibitors, including 900 permanent marts from all over the country, are showcasing a wide range of 14 product categories of house ware, home furnishing, furniture, carpets and handmade paper products.One of the main highlights of the show is a thematic display of products from the northeastern region and Jodhpur mega cluster.The northeastern region is known for its abundant natural material such as cane, bamboo, timber, clay, natural fiber.<PER>KAILASH KUMAR GOYAL</PER>, executive director of <ORG>EXPORT PROMOTION COUNCIL FOR HANDICRAFTS</ORG> (<ORG>EXPORT PROMOTION COUNCIL FOR HANDICRAFTS</ORG>), said 26 participants from northeast states  Assam, Arunachal Pradesh, Manipur, Nagaland, Mizoram, Meghalaya and Sikkim  as well as the regions welfare organisations such as the North Eastern Handloom and Handicrafts Development Corporation and Cane and Bamboo Technology Centre, Assam, are displaying cane and bamboo-based basketry, lamp shades, gifts items, decorative and utility products as well as furniture.Read I Trade fair 2017 to be back in Pragati Maidan in a new avatarA theme pavilion on wooden handicrafts items produced from legally procured wood and certified under Vriksh  an indigenous Indian timber legality assessment and verification scheme  will also be set up.Buyers from different countries were seen visiting the theme pavilion of NER set up during the fair.<PER>KAILASH KUMAR GOYAL</PER> said another theme pavilion from Jodhpur mega cluster has also been set up in which 10 artisans are displaying their skills in leather embroidery, horn, tie and dye crafts, embroidery and appliqu hand block printing, punja durries, art metalware and woodcraft.This international participation will definitely boost the morale of the small and upcoming entrepreneurs of this region and motivate others to step up their efforts in product design and innovation, so that they can also get connected with the international buying community, <PER>KAILASH KUMAR GOYAL</PER> said. 
 --------------------------------------------------
JWALANT SURESHBHAI SHAH 	 ENVIRONMENTAL RESOURCES FOUNDATION 
 59289e887be9e0138af8badc In its seventh year of production,Sakav,the annual magazine by the <ORG>ENVIRONMENTAL RESOURCES FOUNDATION</ORG> (<ORG>ENVIRONMENTAL RESOURCES FOUNDATION</ORG>),continues to highlight the major issues that are faced by people along the Konkan coastlineIt has been named as one of the 34 global biodiversity hotspots and yet when the question of its sustainable development arises,there are few answers forthcoming. The Konkan belt,home to some of the most important forest lands along the North Western Ghats,has problems but few solutions. A primary reason for that is,most people are unaware of the importance of the area. It is one of the few places that has a lot of forest land available to sustain the bio-diversity of the area. Plus,the surrounding the villages totally depend on this kind of forest produce for their daily livelihood, says <PER>JWALANT SURESHBHAI SHAH</PER>,deputy director,<ORG>ENVIRONMENTAL RESOURCES FOUNDATION</ORG> (<ORG>ENVIRONMENTAL RESOURCES FOUNDATION</ORG>).In the year 2004,when the organisation celebrated its 10-year anniversary,they decided to come up with a magazine,Sakav,that would be dedicated to the Konkan belt and the work that is being done there. The word sakav means a bridge that is built during the monsoons over the rivulets that are formed in these regions. As a result,we named the magazine Sakav so that it bridges the gap between the urban world and Konkan so that more and more people would be aware of the issues here, says <PER>JWALANT SURESHBHAI SHAH</PER>.The magazine,an annual affair,deals with the problems that plague the region. <PER>JWALANT SURESHBHAI SHAH</PER> says,When we began in 2004,we touched upon briefly on all the problems in this area. Since then,we have been concentrating on certain issues on an annual basis. Most importantly,we,as city dwellers,do not do all the writing for the magazines,but we ask people from these regions to write about the problems that they experience first hand. Such an important biologically diverse location needs to be given a platform to express itself through the words of the common people who stay there.The area is still underdeveloped,and given its ecological sensitivity,finding a way to develop it is a tough ask. Some of the major issues that have been highlighted over the last seven years include,the industrial sector in Konkan,coastal and maritime development,water management,and in the latest issue,they have touched upon the issue of mining in the Konkan region. <ORG>ENVIRONMENTAL RESOURCES FOUNDATION</ORG> members have been working with locals in these villages to encourage awareness about it.Progress for any people or community is important but it cannot come at the cost of the natural resources that the regions offer. The importance of the Konkan belt can only be understood if one visits the area and sees the huge patches of primary forests, <PER>JWALANT SURESHBHAI SHAH</PER> says.<PER>JWALANT SURESHBHAI SHAH</PER> mentions that even though the magazine doesnt reach out to a lot of people,their efforts are on so that more and more people understand the importance of the work that is being done. The point is,what are the future generations going to have if we do not bother about important places like these? If we do not ensure that development and preservation of the bio-diversity is done seamlessly? These are serious issues that need to be highlighted. And that is what we will continue to do, says <PER>JWALANT SURESHBHAI SHAH</PER>.For all the latest India News, download Indian Express App now 
 --------------------------------------------------
JAYASHREE VENKATRAMAN 	 TRACTORS AND FARM EQUIPMENT LIMITED. 
 598d138d9855b71bdf9ce9ed b'Responses: Firm has no income, no assets; NRIs not covered by Indian laws; sent money through Liberalised Remittance Scheme; no reporting requirementGarware familyOffshore entities: Rondor Overseas Ltd, othersLocation:BVI and PanamaMF records show that the Garware family, comprisin<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c9</PER>re<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d84980088d</PER>re an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ab</PER>re, is associated with a clutch of offshore entities<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c9</PER>re is a shareholder in Rondor Overseas Ltd, registered in BVI on May 10, 1996, holding 1,000 shares of $1 each and a capital of $10,00<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d84980088d</PER>re an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ab</PER>re hold a Power of Attorney (PoA) in a number of Panamanian corporations that issued bearer share<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c9</PER>re is the executive chairman o<ORG>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b4</ORG>es, earlier known as Garware Offshore Services, which owns and operates a fleet of anchor-handling tugs cum supply vessels and platform supply vessels in India, Europe and the Far East<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d849800897</PER>ya is the managing director o<ORG>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b4</ORG>re. Other firms of the Garware Group includ<ORG>5ce4cd788c5a90d84980089b</ORG>ts<ORG>5ce4cd788c5a90d84980089e</ORG>es and Garware Offshore International Services Pte.Read: $10 million as capital: 10 members of KP Singhs DLF family, three BVI firmsMF documents show tha<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d84980088d</PER>ya an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ab</PER>re held PoAs in at least six Panamian corporations: Avior SA, VRA Team Corp SA, U R Great SA, Wellman SA, Yukon Portfolio SA and Python Corp. All these corporations were floated in 2008 wit<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d84980088d</PER>ya an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ab</PER>ma being issued PoAs for three years. But these companies were inactive since 2009 an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d84980088d</PER>ya signed off their dissolution on July 22, 2014.Another Panamanian entity Orel Corporation SA, too, issued PoAs t<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c9</PER>re and Maneesha Shah in January 2011 and November 2010, respectively, but these were revoked in July 2012. The Garwares also set up Fujiyama Team Foundation with initial assets of $10,000 an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d6</PER>ok<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ab</PER>ma an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d84980088d</PER>ya as the principal beneficiaries. The public deed for the foundation was signed on October 26, 2010, and it was registered on November 1, 2010. However, it was struck off the register on January 15, 2013.When contacted, A <PER>5ce4c33c8c5a90d84964be26</PER>na, company secretary and president Legal & Admin o<ORG>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b4</ORG>es, said: Your questionnaire pertains to matters which are more than five years old, we have once again checked wit<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c9</PER>re an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c9</PER>is family (presently travelling), who recalled that there were some entities owned by foreign friends who were considering investments in India and accordingly granted POAs for the said purpose. However, since the intention with which these companies were set up was not executed, the said POAs lapsed and the entities were dissolved.Watch | Explained: What Do The Panama Papers RevealWe wish to state tha<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d84980088d</PER>re an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ab</PER>re, as POA holders, were not beneficial owners of the said entities and were advised that there is no requirement of reporting the existence of POA to any authorities. The same applies t<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d6</PER>re and Mrs Manisha.We once again reiterate, in view of what is stated above, tha<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d6</PER>re and family are not in any way connected or concerned with the entities mentioned in your email. ENS/MumbaiShishir K BajoriaOffshore entity: Haptic (BVI) LimitedLocation: British Virgin Islands (BV<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ce</PER>ia belongs to one of the oldest business families in Kolkata trading in jute and tea<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ce</PER>He is the promoter of SK Bajoria Group, which has steel refractory units in six countries with an annual turnover of $200 millio<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ce</PER>ia is listed as a beneficial owner of Haptic (BVI) Limited, which was set up in the BVI on October 26, 2015 by Mossack Fonseca & Co (MF) along with First Names Group (Isle of Man), a corporate services provider.MF records show the entity was formed to receive assets from sister company and settle new trust with its activities to be carried out in Isle of Man/UK. The value of its assets was more than $1 million. On December 2, 2015, First Names Group proposed to liquidate the company.Core Holdings Corp (Charlestown, St Kitts and Nevis) was appointed the director and one share was issued to Castle Hill (Nominees) Ltd (Isle of Man). MF records for Haptic include a copy of Bajorias passport (Z002543) as proof of identity and lists Alipore in Kolkata a<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ce</PER>is India address. A close associate of former chief minister lat<PER>5ce4c7248c5a90d8496ef204</PER>su<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ce</PER>ia qui<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ce</PER>is CPI-M membership and joined the BJP in August 2014<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ce</PER>He is one of the key BJP campaigners in the upcoming assembly polls in West Bengal.Response: My family through a private limited company holds majority shareholding o<ORG>5ce4cd748c5a90d8497ffdb6</ORG>td which has a subsidiary IFGL Worldwide Holdings Ltd (IWHL) in Isle of Man. Also, my wife and myself are shareholders of Sonnish Ltd, another Isle of Man company. So I am a client of First Names Group, Isle of Man. I have not, nor have ever, owned (beneficially or otherwise) Haptic BVI Ltd. I believe that any connection to me was made in error, sai<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ce</PER>ia.First Names Group representative C G Hepburn said: We made an administrative error on a form which we sent to Mossack Fonseca. The erroneous beneficial owner information on the form was entirely our fault, as was the enclosure of the copy verification document<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008a7</PER>ar/New DelhiOnkar KanwarOffshore entity: J&S Systems CorporationLocation: BVI(Source: Apollo Tyres) (Source: Apollo Tyre<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d5</PER>ar, chairman of Apollo Group, an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d5</PER>is family members floated an offshore entity, J&S Systems Corporation, in BVI in 2010 and two trusts in 2014.MF records show that the entity holds a million shares of 0.01 pence each in London Stock Exchange-listed Mercom Oil Sands plc, an apartment in Londons iconic The Tower, and accounts in Barclays Bank, Singapore, and Cayman National Bank and Trust Company Ltd in Isle of Man. The balance in Cayman on November 30, 2014 was GBP 3,65,478.26, records show.Apart fro<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d5</PER>ar<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d2</PER>ar an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b8</PER>ar, who became the first shareholders in J&S on October 6, 2010, shares are also held by Onkars wif<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b1</PER>ar. J&S was registered on July 30, 2010 and the promoters disclosed that the source of funds in the entity would be proceeds from business trade.Watch | Panama Papers: A Peek Into India Express 8 Month Long InvestigationOnkar Kanwar is categorised as a Politically Exposed Person by MFs Compliance Department becaus<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b8</PER>he was a board member of the Kerala State Industrial Development Corporation from May 25, 2010 till September 20, 2014.The address o<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b1</PER>ru an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d5</PER>ar in New Delhis Shanti Niketan is the same as that o<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d2</PER>aj an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b8</PER>an. In November 2013, the shareholding of J&S showe<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d5</PER>ar held 440 shares<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d2</PER>aj 570<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b8</PER>an 430<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b1</PER>ru 100. Another 200 shares each were held b<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b8</PER>an an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d2</PER>aj together for their childre<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d4</PER>an an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d84980089f</PER>ra. Records show tha<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d5</PER>ar was a registered shareholder till March 14, 2014.On January 30, 2014<PER>5ce4c3168c5a90d8496462e0</PER>ra an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d5</PER>ar floated a settlement called T&O Trust with Harneys Trustees Ltd. The final beneficiaries of the settlement wer<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d4</PER>an an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d84980089f</PER>ra. On the same day<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d2</PER>aj an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b8</PER>an floated a settlement S&N Trust with Harneys, listin<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d4</PER>an an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d84980089f</PER>ra as final beneficiaries.In both cases, records show, the Trust Fund comprising 100 shares were to be split betwee<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d4</PER>ai an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d84980089f</PER>ra equally upon a terminating even<PER>5ce4c7a18c5a90d849704861</PER>se: A spokesperson of Apollo Tyres stated: India lawfully permits foreign investments in accordance with certain regulations. Any investment abroad, that the Kanwar family may have, is in due compliance with Indian laws, where applicable, including making disclosures wherever required. Much of family mentioned in your mail, are Non Residents of India (NRIs). They are covered by other nations permissible laws for their foreign investments, and are not covered by Indian laws & restrictions on residents, in matters such as Income Tax and RBI. P Vaidyanathan Iyer/New DelhiHarish SalveOffshore entities: Crestbright Ltd, Pyebush Group Ltd, Edenval LtdLocation:BVIOne of the most sought-after lawyers in the country<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008bc</PER>ve has represented celebrity clients in the Supreme Court<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008bc</PER>He was Solicitor General of India between 1999 and 2002.MF records show tha<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008bc</PER>ve an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008bc</PER>is family members registered three offshore companies in the BVI  Crestbright Ltd, Pyebush Group Ltd and Edenval Ltd  through the London-based agent Rawi & Co with Vasant Vihar in New Delhi as the India address. MF records include a recommendation letter fro<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008bc</PER>ve to Rawi & Co in 2007, asking them to set up a company and a trust fo<PER>5ce4cbbf8c5a90d8497b5187</PER>an an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b6</PER>an.MF records show tha<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008bc</PER>ve is listed as a director in Crestbright Ltd, which was registered in 2012 with Salendra Swarup as another director. The other two entities were registered in 2008 with Salves wif<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008bc</PER>ve and daughte<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ca</PER>ve as directors. MF records show that Edenval Ltd is listed as a shareholder in the incorporation documents of Pyebush Group Ltd.Response<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008bc</PER>ve said: I set up Crestbright in 2012  as a holding company to hold my lawfully made and fully disclosed investments based in the UK but the company has zero assets and zero income.I have been remitting funds since maybe 2003 under LRS. Out of these, some were invested in a portfolio in the UK and a patent in the US (a 25% stake with three other friends). Wanted to park these in a BVI company as at that time I was not a UK tax resident and wanted to avoid becoming one. Since 2014, I am a dual tax resident  UK and India, and so have not moved any assets into Crestbright.Edenoval was set up with a friend, and Pyebush was set up by me to hold shares in Edenoval. My friend had suggested some investments outside India and outside UK. Nothing materialsed; no income  no assets. All the three companies are virtually defunct.All my offshore assets upto 2014 were created out of funds remitted from my Indian bank to my UK bank account. After 2014, I have income in the UK too  and made some investments out of that. Since bank accounts are routinely called for by tax authorities, all Indian and UK bank details are filed. Nothing is withheld.Watch | Karnal to London via Bahamas, The Route Indiabulls Promoter TookHowever, the BVI companies have no value in any event  do not represent an asset or investment abroad. Besides, all LRS remittances are disclosed by the remitting bank to the RBI.As far as the letter of refence is concerned<PER>5ce4cbbf8c5a90d8497b5187</PER>an an<PER>5ce4cbbf8c5a90d8497b5187</PER>an are Canadian citizens<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008bc</PER>He came back on a Transfer of Residence, and wanted a company to manag<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008bc</PER>is offshore moneys. It was for that reason that I wrote the letter of reference t<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008bc</PER>im to set up a company<PER>5ce4cd748c5a90d8497ffdc5</PER>in/New DelhiJehangir S SorabjeeOffshore entity: Moonglow Investments Global LtdLocation: BVIJehangi<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c0</PER>ee, son of former attorney genera<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c0</PER>ee and a honorary consultant physician at Bombay Hospital, is the sole shareholder in Moonglow Investments Global Ltd, an offshore entity incorporated in the British Virgin Islands on November 24, 2010. On the same day, MF records show<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c0</PER>he consented to act as a director of the compan<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c0</PER>ee complete<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c0</PER>is MBBS from the Grant Medical College in the UK an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c0</PER>is Masters in Internal Medicine. Subsequentl<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c0</PER>he worked in the UK for five years at different hospitals and obtained a postgraduate medical diploma and diploma in tropical medicine and hygiene from Londo<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c0</PER>He is currently professor of medicine and head of the department of medicine at the Bombay Hospital Institute of Medical Sciences<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c0</PER>He is also a postgraduate teacher at the Maharashtra University of Health Sciences and has authored a number of academic publications and text book chapter<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c0</PER>ee is also a celebrated photographer and images fro<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c0</PER>is book of aerial pictures of Mumbai  Above Bombay  have been included as part of exhibitions at the Venice Biennale in 2006, The Tate Modern in 2007 and the Canary Islands Biennale in 2009.Response<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c0</PER>ee said tha<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c0</PER>he has complied with all disclosure norms. The facts are correct. The company has received funds for investment sent abroad from India through the liberalised RBI scheme and is declared in my Income Tax returns to the Income tax authorities, sai<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c0</PER>ee. ENS/MumbaiMohan Lal LohiaOffshore entities: Venton Group Ltd, Lohia Charitable FoundationLocation:BVI & PanamaWell-known industrialis<PER>5ce4c74c8c5a90d8496f6293</PER>ia is Chairman Emeritus of Indo Rama Synthetics and Chairman of Indo Rama Holdings Ltd. MF documents show tha<PER>5ce4c74c8c5a90d8496f6293</PER>ia is the first director of Venton Group Ltd, registered in the BVI in 2007 with its objectives listed as broad and India address as Greater Kailash in New Delhi. In November 2012, MF was instructed via email to let Venton die a natural death.MF records show tha<PER>5ce4c74c8c5a90d8496f6293</PER>ia also set up the Lohia Charitable Foundation, an NGO, in Panama in January 2010 with a corpus of $10,000. Apart fro<PER>5ce4c74c8c5a90d8496f6293</PER>ia<PER>5ce4c74c8c5a90d8496f6293</PER>is grandso<PER>5ce4cd748c5a90d8497ffdb2</PER>ia and daughter-in-la<PER>5ce4cd748c5a90d8497ffdbc</PER>ia are listed as members of the foundations family council. There are no closure documents available for the foundation, with records listing communication, such as requests for copies of incumbency certificates, till as late as July 2015.Read: Inside the offshore factory of Mossack Secret FonsecaResponse: A company spokesperson said<PER>5ce4c74c8c5a90d8496f6293</PER>ia is father o<PER>5ce4cd748c5a90d8497ffdca</PER>ia, chairman and managing director of our company<PER>5ce4c74c8c5a90d8496f6293</PER>ia<PER>5ce4cd748c5a90d8497ffdbc</PER>ia an<PER>5ce4cd748c5a90d8497ffdb2</PER>ia all are non-residents and are settled abroad. Although I am not aware about the overseas entities as stated in your mail, however, to my understanding activities carried overseas by NRIs are not required to be informed to Income Tax authorities or Reserve Bank of India in India<PER>5ce4cd748c5a90d8497ffdc5</PER>in/New DelhiZavaray PoonawallaOffshore entity: Stallast LtdLocation: BVID<PER>5ce4c38e8c5a90d849658d7e</PER>la (left) wit<PER>5ce4c38e8c5a90d849658d7e</PER>is brothe<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008aa</PER>l<PER>5ce4c38e8c5a90d849658d7e</PER>la (left) wit<PER>5ce4c38e8c5a90d849658d7e</PER>is brother Zavaray PoonawallaBrother of billionair<PER>5ce4c38e8c5a90d849658d7e</PER>la<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008aa</PER>ay heads the managing committee of the Royal Western India Turf Club (RWITC) and is on the board of four companies that deal with real estate, construction, hospitality and stud farms.MF records lis<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008aa</PER>ay, wif<PER>5ce4c5d78c5a90d8496b8e09</PER>ze and daughters Simone and Delna, as directors of Stallast Ltd set up in 2013 in the British Virgin Islands. Stallast was struck off the records in 2014.Response<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008aa</PER>ay said: Yes, we are directors in the company. As we remitted money under the Liberalised Remittance Scheme through the automatic route, no special permission from RBI was necessary. We have disclosed all details to Indian tax authorities. As this was part of an official transaction, it was not necessary for any declaration under the amnesty scheme. Partha Biswas/PuneRajendra PatilOffshore entity: Elgenburg LtdLocation: BVIRajendra Patil is the son-in-law of veteran Congressman and Karnataka Horticulture Ministe<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008a8</PER>pa, a businessman and educationist who owns medical and engineering colleges in Davangere.Patil runs a sugar export company and is also involved with energy, aviation, textile, education and Internet firms run by the Shivashankarappa family. According to MF records, Patil and two associates<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d9</PER>da an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008bf</PER>di, set up an offshore firm called Elgenburg Ltd in the British Virgin Islands in 2007 with an initial shareholding of 50,000 shares with Patil holding 22,500 of them.The records show a commercial complex owned by the Shivashankarappa family in Bengaluru as Patils address in India.Response: Patil said: The company was created in 2007 as a buyer for issuing letters of credit in Europe. We were trading in agricultural commodities. We did one deal but suffered losses of Rs 1 crore so we shut it down the same year. Johnson T A/BengaluruAnil Vasudeva SalgaocarNo. of offshore entities: 11Location:BVIA Goa-based mining baron and former MLA<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008a2</PER>ar had set up 11 offshore companies with the help of MF, mostly in the BVI, with a majority of them being incorporated between 2004-2005 wit<PER>5ce4c4928c5a90d849682f46</PER>ma in south Goa as the India address<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008a2</PER>ar, 75, died in Singapore in January following illness.These offshore entities include Ling Tao Trading Ltd, Horizon Villa Investments Ltd, GBA Shipping Ltd, Jamana Finance Limited<ORG>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008cd</ORG>8498008cd</ORG>ed, Nickon Enterprises Ltd, General Harvest International Ltd and Crown Bright Trading Ltd, among others, with records showing that a majority were set up between 2004-2005. Records show that many of the 11 companies were struck off MFs lists in 2007 and 200<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d849800885</PER>rs so<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008c6</PER>il is also listed as a director in some companies. In 2007<PER>5ce4c85c8c5a90d849723ec9</PER>ar did not disclose these offshore companies to the Election Commission whe<PER>5ce4c85c8c5a90d849723ec9</PER>he contested and won the assembly polls from Sanvordem.Response: A member o<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d849800885</PER>rs family, who did not wish to be identified, said: I am in no position to comment on this since we are not aware of these business interests. Nothing is known to us about these companies<PER>5ce4cd748c5a90d8497ffdc5</PER>in/New DelhiIndira Sivasailam and Mallika SrinivasanOffshore entities: Stanbridge Company LtdLocation: BVIIndir<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d849800895</PER>am, who died in December 2008, at the age of 73, was the wife o<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d849800895</PER>am, chairman of Amalgamations Group<PER>5ce4c5d78c5a90d8496b8e09</PER>he was survived b<PER>5ce4c5d78c5a90d8496b8e09</PER>er husband and two daughters<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008a1</PER>an, chairman and CEO of Tractors an<ORG>TRACTORS AND FARM EQUIPMENT LIMITED.</ORG>E), the third largest tractor manufacturer in the world, and the lat<PER>JAYASHREE VENKATRAMAN</PER>an, director o<ORG>TRACTORS AND FARM EQUIPMENT LIMITED.</ORG>FE (Power Source Division)<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008a1</PER>ka is the wife o<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008cb</PER>an, chairman of TVS Motors.MF records list Indira as a shareholder in Stanbridge Company Ltd, which was incorporated in 1999 in the BVI. Records show that shares of the older couple were transferred to their daughters in 2011 and eventually, in October, 201<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b7</PER>an relinquishe<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b7</PER>er shares for personal reasons to one Ved Prakash Ahuja. They also show that shares of another BVI entity, Auto Engineering Development and Research Limited, were transferred to Stanbridge. MF records show the company was struck off the records in September 2015.Response<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008a1</PER>an stated: I wish to clarify that I did not set up any offshore company and have no connection with Stanbridge Company Limited. It belongs to Mr V P Ahuja, an NRI In a separate response, V <PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d849800888</PER>ja stated: I confirm that Stanbridge Company Limited was set up for my sole benefit by me and that the shares were held by me in entirety<PER>5ce4c4918c5a90d849682e80</PER>an/ChennaiTabasum <PER>5ce4c3098c5a90d849644733<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008a3</PER>re entity: Mondale SALocation: PanamaAbdu<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d849800889</PER>ir (Source: cieworld.com<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ba</PER>ir (Source: cieworld.com)MF records sho<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ba</PER>ir, Cottage Industries Exposition (CIE) founder and CEO, floated Mondale SA on September 4, 2002, in Panama with an authorised capital of $10,000, divided into 100 shares. MF provided three directors and a secretary. The bearer shares were issued ten days later  on September 14  and Mirs so<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d3</PER>eb subscribed as shareholder to the entire authorised share capital of the company on October 8.On December 2, 2002<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ba</PER>ir got a Power of Attorney from Mondale SA to open a bank account with Banque Baring Brothers (Suisse) SA. In account opening documents, Mujeeb Mir, with a Bangkok address, was shown as owner of financial assets of the company while the signature card had the nam<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ba</PER>ir.On January 31, 2005<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d3</PER>eb was murdered in Mauritius. Five months later, on July 11<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d3</PER>is parents<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ba</PER>ir an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d8</PER>ir, were appointed additional directors in Mondale SA. According to MF documents, on July 5, 2007<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d849800889</PER>ir me<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008b2</PER>le of Banque Baring Brothers Sturdza SA, Geneva, Switzerland to cancel, with immediate effect, the discretionary management power granted to the bank over the companys account with the Bank.In March 2011, Mondale SA replaced Geneva-based law firm Secretan Troyanov with Swiss LLC, Geneva, as its administrator. The last available record of the company in MF documents is dated January 15, 2013, when it paid the annual fee as a private company to the Ministry of Economy and Finance, Panama<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d8</PER>ir is a director in 17 Indian companies including CIE which, on its website, claims businesses worth billions in silk carpets alone. The company runs outlets in locations such as Indonesia, Thailand, Cambodia, Mauritius, Dubai and Abu Dhabi.Response<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008d8</PER>ir said: I am a resident citizen of India an<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ba</PER>ir is an NRI. Neithe<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008ba</PER>he nor I have ever held any stake in or any control of Mondale SA which was incorporated and controlled by a trust founded by lat<PER>5ce4cd748c5a90d8497ffdb0</PER>ir who almos<PER>5ce4cd748c5a90d8497ffdb0</PER>is entire life was an NRI. Afte<PER>5ce4cd748c5a90d8497ffdb0</PER>is unfortunate death in 2005, the trustees dissolved the Trust and distributed the proceeds amongs<PER>5ce4cd748c5a90d8497ffdb0</PER>is family members who have fully disclosed the benefit so received by them to the concerned GOI authorities<PER>5ce4cd788c5a90d8498008a7</PER>ar/New Delhi' 
 --------------------------------------------------
DEEPAK MOOLCHAND LAHOTI 	 BAJAJ FINSERV LIMITED 
 58fe14227be9e012c79dfaa5 The 21st edition of the annual market research fair BrandScan, being organised by T.A. Pai Management Institute (TAPMI), was inaugurated here on Friday.Addressing budding managers on the occasion, <PER>5ce4c57e8c5a90d8496aa905</PER>, CEO of <ORG>BAJAJ FINSERV LIMITED</ORG>, said that the first attribute of a brand was its longevity.A product should get higher price for its owner. Identification of customers for a product was essential.If customer segments were different, then product propositions had to be different. Innovation should be given importance. Managers should speak their minds even after they joined corporate companies, <PER>5ce4c57e8c5a90d8496aa905</PER> said.<PER>DEEPAK MOOLCHAND LAHOTI</PER>, Head HR, <ORG>BAJAJ FINSERV LIMITED</ORG>, <PER>5ce4c57e8c5a90d8496aa903</PER>, Director of the Institute, <PER>5ce4c4fe8c5a90d849694f9e</PER>, Chairman of BrandScan, <PER>5ce4c57e8c5a90d8496aa902</PER> and <PER>5ce4c57e8c5a90d8496aa906</PER>, Student Conveners, were present.The BrandScan event in its rural format will be held at Nehru Maidan in Kundapur on Saturday; and in its fair format at KMC Greens here on Sunday. 
 --------------------------------------------------
chandrasekaran.m 	 CONFEDERATION OF INDIAN INTERNET COMMERCE 
 593aad6b7be9e07def1e66fd Students of engineering now have a platform where they can hone their employability skills. <ORG>CONFEDERATION OF INDIAN INTERNET COMMERCE</ORG> has launched a cluster to facilitate more industry-institute interaction across the State. <PER>5ce4cb0b8c5a90d84979638a</PER>, Vice-President, <ORG>5ce4cafb8c5a90d84979349e</ORG>a90d84979349e</PER>, inaugurated the <ORG>CONFEDERATION OF INDIAN INTERNET COMMERCE</ORG> College Excellence Cluster Initiative here on Monday.Fresh recruitmentsOn the occasion, <PER>5ce4cb0b8c5a90d84979638a</PER> said TCS would be recruiting 40,000 fresh engineering graduates this year.Shortage of engineersThere is a shortage of employable engineers available in almost all streams, <PER>5ce4cb0b8c5a90d84979638a</PER> said.<PER>chandrasekaran.m</PER>, Chairman, Task Force on Education, <ORG>CONFEDERATION OF INDIAN INTERNET COMMERCE</ORG> and Vice-President, Corporate Affairs, <ORG>5ce4cae68c5a90d8497903bd</ORG>, said the initiative will offer larger scope for institutions to learn things collectively. Initiatives such as CEO speak, faculty mission and student mission will be held, <PER>chandrasekaran.m</PER> added.Aby Sam, Co Chairman, Task Force on Education, <ORG>CONFEDERATION OF INDIAN INTERNET COMMERCE</ORG> and Director, Hindustan Institute of Technology and Science and <PER>5ce4c4668c5a90d84967bd07</PER>, Chairperson, Rajalakshmi Engineering College spoke.KCG Engineering College, Sree Sashtra Engineering College, Abdur Rahman Cresent Engineering College, Rajalakshmi Engineering College and SRM University are among the institutions that have formally agreed to be part of the <ORG>CONFEDERATION OF INDIAN INTERNET COMMERCE</ORG> Cluster Initiative and sign MoUs. 
 --------------------------------------------------
Lochan Singh 	 GLOBAL AUTOTECH LIMITED 
 590343797be9e026559abfd8 New Delhi, July 29: India plans to intensify its campaign against Britains tough post-study work visa norms and the policies of some of its institutions, such as non-recognition of school-leaving certificates, that pose barriers to student movement to that country. HRD minister <PER>5ce4c7a28c5a90d849704b2c</PER>, who took up these issues with high commissioner <PER>5ce4c57e8c5a90d8496aa677</PER> last month, is likely to raise them again when universities and science minister <PER>5ce4c7a28c5a90d849704b29</PER> visits India later this year. <PER>5ce4c7a28c5a90d849704b2c</PER> told <PER>5ce4c57e8c5a90d8496aa677</PER> these barriers were discouraging Indian students from going for higher studies to the UK. Many top institutions, like the London School of Economics, prefer the General Certificate of Education (GCE) Advanced Levels or the International Baccalaureate certification. They ask Indian students who have cleared the CBSE exam or the Council for the Indian School Certificate Examination to do an add-on course to be eligible for admission to undergraduate courses. The argument given is that school education in India is of 12 years, a year less than the British system. The CBSE has been protesting this practice and had taken up the matter with Universities UK, the organisation that represents British universities. Of late, however, many universities, including Oxford, Warwick and Durham, have been recognising CBSE and CISCE certification as equivalent to UK school board certificates. <PER>5ce4c7a28c5a90d849704b2c</PER> has also claimed that British universities have been treating the IELTS scores, which indicate a students proficiency in English and are asked for by all universities while giving admission, as valid for just one year. Education firms that recruit students for foreign universities say the IELTS score is valid for two years. The third issue <PER>5ce4c7a28c5a90d849704b2c</PER> raised was about the post-study work visa norms  introduced with effect from April 6, 2012  that allow students to work with a minimum salary threshold of 20,000 a year. For foreign students who have just completed their education, its tough landing a job that pays such a package, making it difficult for them to stay back and work. <PER>5ce4c7a28c5a90d849704b2b</PER>, chairman of education overseas consulting firm The Chopras, said the earlier visa policy was misused by foreign students. It prompted the British government to introduce the tough norms, discouraging Indians from choosing Britain as a higher-study destination. If the salary threshold norm is relaxed, many Indian students will prefer to study in the UK, <PER>5ce4c7a28c5a90d849704b2b</PER> said. <PER>Lochan Singh</PER>, <ORG>GLOBAL AUTOTECH LIMITED</ORG>, a Calcutta-based student recruitment firm, said another factor affecting student mobility was that masters degrees given in the UK were not recognised in India. Most UK universities offer one-year masters courses and three-year BTech programmes. Indian institutions offer two-year masters courses and four-year BTech programmes. The University Grants Commission has decided to allow postgraduates from Britain to do a six-month bridge course but no mechanism has been worked out for recognising the three-year BTech degrees UK universities offer. 
 --------------------------------------------------
LAKSHMIKANTHAN KRISHNAN 	 RENAULT NISSAN TECHNOLOGY & BUSINESS CENTRE INDIA PRIVATE LIMITED 
 58fd53ad7be9e06c93719a3e CHENNAI: On a day when the Supreme Court banned firecrackers in Delhi NCR, the Centre indicated that India is close to formulating its own legislation on management and recycling of End-of-life Vehicles (ELVs), whose number is projected to explode to over two crore by 2025.This would be a major step towards cutting down carbon footprint. A recent study by Central Pollution Control Board (CPCB) and Indo German Environment Partnership (GIZ-IGEP) in major automobile hubs like Chennai, Pune, Kolkata, Indore and Jamshedpur has mapped the key problem areas and the trade chain covering informal sector workers engaged in collection, dismantling, trading and recycling of ELVs.Speaking to Express on the sidelines of a workshop on Status and future of ELV recycling in India, at IIT Madras, <PER>5ce4c4eb8c5a90d849691bc3</PER>, scientist in CPCB, said a cautious approach has been adopted. Sectoral study has been done and Automotive Industry Standard (AIS) for ELV has been published with guidelines being formed. Now, the decision on introducing a regulation should be taken by ministries concerned. But one thing is sure, we are not too far behind, <PER>5ce4c4eb8c5a90d849691bc3</PER> said.As per the Society of Indian Automobile Manufacturers (SIAM), 20 million vehicles were sold in the year 2015-16. With government contemplating to go for stringent emission norms, the useful age of vehicles will be reduced which calls for advancements in ELV management, which is currently handled by the informal sector unscientifically causing adverse impact on environment and workers health, said <PER>5ce4c4eb8c5a90d849691bc5</PER>, former secretary of Union Environment Ministry and currently member of the Scientific Advisory Council of the Cabinet.<PER>5ce4c4eb8c5a90d849691bc3</PER> said Extended Producers Responsibility (EPR) was one of the possibilities under consideration at the ministerial level to deal with ELVs. Under EPR, the manufacturer or importer of the product is responsible for the entire life cycle of the product i.e. ELV. This responsibility starts at the design stage of the vehicle. The producers responsibility for a product is hence extended beyond manufacturing to post-consumer stage. This is the norm in several countries like Japan, Korea etc.Government of India has proposed to set-up modern recycling centres like National Automotive Testing and R&D Infrastructure Project (NATRIP) in Chennai. It also proposes an incentive plan for customers to return old vehicles and build eight car scrap centres near ports around the country, <PER>5ce4c4eb8c5a90d849691bc3</PER> said.<PER>LAKSHMIKANTHAN KRISHNAN</PER>, Vice President, Product Engineering, <ORG>RENAULT NISSAN TECHNOLOGY & BUSINESS CENTRE INDIA PRIVATE LIMITED</ORG> and Business Centre India Pvt Ltd, told Express that the company would have no problem with extended producers responsibility, if the government provides fair incentives to OEMs (Original Equipment Manufacturer). If we get good incentives, we can pump that money into the product towards design etc, <PER>LAKSHMIKANTHAN KRISHNAN</PER> said.What is ELV as per AIS-129? End-of-Life Vehicle is a vehicle readdy to be scrapped by its last owner Why recycle? It is estimated that passenger cars contain about 70% steel and 7-8% aluminum Recycling 1 ton of steel conserves 1,134 kg of iron ore, 635 kg of coal and 54,4 kg of limestone, thereby conserving energy besides reducing environmental impact It will generate seconday material sink reducing use of virgin materials Secondary metals are processed using technologies requiring less energyGlobal practices India: There is no ELVs law or recycling policy. There is no concept of de-registration. Currently, inter-ministerial group has been formed to brainstorm the issue and formulate regulations, which are at draft stage European Union: Has ELV law. Vehicle manufacturer is responsible for free take back and recycling cost Japan: Has ELV law. Shared responsibility of owner, manufacturer & recycler China: Has ELV law and traded as valuable secondary resource US: No regulation, but traded as valuable secondary resource 
 --------------------------------------------------
NILADRI SEKHAR ROY 	 MAHANADI COALFIELDS LIMITED 
 58ff6ccc7be9e0420db30e93 Durgapur, July 31: Around 200 workers were stranded in seven coal mines of Asansol for around four hours when a blackout affecting half the country cut off electricity to lifts in their underground pits, an Eastern <ORG>MAHANADI COALFIELDS LIMITED</ORG> offcial said. <ORG>MAHANADI COALFIELDS LIMITED</ORG> authorities used power from the Dishergarh Power Supply Corporation to operate emergency lifts to bring out the workers, who were working in the first shift from 8am. There was no threat to their lives or any reason to panic. We managed to lift all the 200 miners safe by 5.30pm with the help of power from the DPSC. said <PER>NILADRI SEKHAR ROY</PER>, a senior <ORG>MAHANADI COALFIELDS LIMITED</ORG> official. After grids collapsed around 1pm, the workers had got trapped in the mines in Sodepur and Satgram. The exhaust fans and lights at the 400 feet deep tunnels also stopped working, sending the miners into a panic. We were trying to see with the help of battery-operated torches fitted on our safety helmets. But we felt suffocated as the exhaust fans stopped working. We also feared a crack in the walls which can cause a flood in the mine, said a miner at Chinakuri near Asansol. Most lifts in the underground mines of <ORG>MAHANADI COALFIELDS LIMITED</ORG> are operated through electricity though some of them also function with the help of steam. According to the authorities, production at all the 84 underground mines of <ORG>MAHANADI COALFIELDS LIMITED</ORG> had to be stopped in the first shift, leading to a loss of Rs 5 crore. The mines produce around 6,000 to 7,000 tones of coals each in three shifts of eight hours. We have already lost one shift and if power cannot be resumed by tonight, work in the other two shifts will also be hampered, <PER>NILADRI SEKHAR ROY</PER> said. Production was partially possible through diesel-operated machines at some of the open-cast mines. Officials also feared the loss in production would prevent them from supplying coal to the thermal power plants in the state tomorrow. If production is not resumed soon, we will fail to supply coal to the power plants tomorrow, a senior <ORG>MAHANADI COALFIELDS LIMITED</ORG> official said in the evening. 
 --------------------------------------------------
VINOD BIDASARIA 	 FERRO CONCRETE CO INDIA LTD 
 593cb1e47be9e00dabcb80cb Opportunities: <PER>5ce4cc878c5a90d8497d7be5</PER>, chairman of Indian Geotechnical Society, inaugurating the national seminar in Hubli on Saturday.K.S. <PER>5ce4cc878c5a90d8497d7be5</PER>, chairman, Indian Geotechnical Society (IGS), has said that the infrastructure development boom had brought with it enormous opportunities for geotechnical engineers.<PER>5ce4cc878c5a90d8497d7be5</PER> was inaugurating a national seminar on Advances in geotechnical engineering', jointly organised by Hubli-Dharwad Chapter of IGS and Civil Engineering Department of BVB College of Engineering and Technology here on Saturday. <PER>5ce4cc878c5a90d8497d7be5</PER> said that infrastructure development was essential to maintain a steady growth of the Gross Domestic Product.Adverse impactsHe said that geotechnical engineers could be of great help in mitigating the adverse impact of natural calamities on various types of buildings, <PER>5ce4cc878c5a90d8497d7be5</PER> said.<PER>VINOD BIDASARIA</PER>, Managing Director of <ORG>FERRO CONCRETE CO INDIA LTD</ORG> released a newsletter of the IGS Hubli-Dharwad chapter.P.V. <PER>5ce4c3148c5a90d849645d84</PER>, Professor, Indian Institute of Sciences (IISc), Bangalore; <PER>5ce4c3178c5a90d849646680</PER>, Head (Geo Hazards and Hydro-Meteorology Division) of National Institute of Disaster Management, New Delhi; <PER>5ce4cc878c5a90d8497d7be0</PER>, Chairman of IGS Hubli-Dharwad chapter, and <PER>5ce4cc878c5a90d8497d7be3</PER>, honorary secretary, IGS were present. 
 --------------------------------------------------
DILPREET BRAR 	 IBM INDIA PRIVATE LIMITED 
 5923892f7be9e01fcef03a2d A cross-discipline initiative to groom future women leadersBangalore, Oct 13, 2014, DHNS: 3:10 ISTWith the aim to encourage and prepare more women for leadership roles across various business sectors, the Indian Institute of Management, Bangalore (IIMB), IBM, the multinational technology company and <ORG>5ce4c8d28c5a90d8497372a2</ORG> WRC, the non-profit organisation promoting women in business, will collaborate to start a womens leadership development programme called Tanmatra.Taught by the faculty at IIMB, the idea of this cross-industry development programme is for corporations to nominate a few of its high-potential women employees with more than 15 years of experience or above for the programme. It will be spread across 10 months starting from October this year to June, 2015.<PER>5ce4c57b8c5a90d8496a9ebe</PER>, Associate Professor, IIMB and programme director, highlighted how the upward movement of women from junior to mid-level and senior positions in companies was very less in India.While in South East Asian countries like Malaysia, the condition was better than in India, this was only to a small extent.Already, 48 organisations have shown interest in the programme, <PER>5ce4c57b8c5a90d8496a9ebe</PER> said. <PER>DILPREET BRAR</PER>, Vice President, HR, <ORG>IBM INDIA PRIVATE LIMITED</ORG>/ South Asia pointed out that corporates such as Unilever, Walmart, CISCO, ANZ, Dr Reddys and Amazon had shown interest.The programme consists of three modules that will be a blend of academic, reflective and experiential learning on themes like impacting business outcomes, exploring the self and owning careers.It will be taught in three residental modules of five days each over the 10-month period as well as in virtual sessions between the residential modules. The programme will include activities such as cross industry learning, assessments, stretch assignments, mentoring, networking with leaders, to name a few.<PER>5ce4c8d28c5a90d8497372a1</PER>, president and CEO, <ORG>5ce4c8d28c5a90d8497372a2</ORG>, said, Through Tanmatra, we can communicate with working women, discuss the daily challenges they face and suggest effective strategies based on extensive research, <PER>5ce4c8d28c5a90d8497372a1</PER> said.A company can send a maximum of four applications and a minimum of two applications for the programe. Individual or self-sponsored applications will not be entertained.While IBM is the knowledge partner in the collaboration, IIMB the education partner and <ORG>5ce4c8d28c5a90d8497372a2</ORG>, research partner. 
 --------------------------------------------------
SACHIN DHINGRA 	 RELIANCE DEFENCE AND AEROSPACE PRIVATE LIMITED 
 58fd2a5e7be9e06c9371637a BENGALURU: <ORG>5ce4c37e8c5a90d849656358</ORG> and UAE-based Strata Manufacturing PJSC (Strata) have signed a Memorandum of Understanding to collaborate on advanced aerospace manufacturing capabilities between India and the UAE.Strata, the advanced composite aerostructures manufacturing company, is wholly owned by Mubadala Development Company, the UAE. <ORG>5ce4c37e8c5a90d849656358</ORG> is a wholly owned Subsidiary of Reliance Infrastructure Limited.The potential partnership will look at opportunities in the production of Carbon Fibre Composites Aerostructures, Prepregs as well as 3D printing of aerospace components and airframe panels, a Reliance release said.The collaboration is in line with Stratas vision to become one of the top aerospace companies globally, it said.<PER>5ce4c4aa8c5a90d849686fcb</PER>, CEO of Strata, said they are keen to grow their capabilities globally with <ORG>5ce4c37e8c5a90d849656358</ORG> and expand their operational footprint by capitalising on innovative, cost-effective solutions that can benefit their customers whilst enhancing the company's financial performance.Working together with <ORG>5ce4c37e8c5a90d849656358</ORG>, "we see a significant opportunity that can lead to the creation of a new tier-one global supplier: designing, developing and manufacturing major aircraft components - such as wings and empennages - for the next generation of aircrafts," <PER>5ce4c4aa8c5a90d849686fcb</PER> said.<PER>SACHIN DHINGRA</PER>, President, <ORG>RELIANCE DEFENCE AND AEROSPACE PRIVATE LIMITED</ORG>8</ORG> & Aerospace, said :"Indias composites industry is at a nascent stage and projected to reach Four Lakh metric tons by 2020." The project has the potential to bring in significant foreign direct investment and cutting edge technology in this niche composite aircraft manufacturing segment.Under the MoU, Strata and <ORG>5ce4c37e8c5a90d849656358</ORG> will consider new opportunities in the commercial aerospace market, address the emerging market for 3D printing of aircraft components and obsolescence management and consider other areas of growth related to both the Abu Dhabi Economic Vision 2030 and "Make in India" initiative. 
 --------------------------------------------------
ANIL KUMAR GARG 	 AXIS BANK LIMITED 
 58fd4eb77be9e06c9371939d PALAKKAD: Teaching should be such that what is offered is perceived as a valuable gift and not as a hard duty - <PER>5ce4c4e38c5a90d84969094c</PER> words of the master scientist are a perfect tag for <PER>5ce4c4e38c5a90d84969094d</PER>. The native of Karipayil in Pattancherry has dedicated <PER>5ce4c4e38c5a90d84969094d</PER> life to teach students from tribal communities and those from low income families without any remuneration for four decades. The outcome: The Pattancherry panchayat boasts nearly 100 engineers.Currently, 100 students from poor families, who are interested in science subjects, have been selected from various government schools and sent to a private coaching centre in Thrissur. The centre has agreed to subsidise their boarding and tuition expenses. The remaining 60 students are being taught here. In 2016, around 23 students from here secured admission in government engineering colleges and two students in medical colleges, said <PER>5ce4c4e38c5a90d84969094d</PER>.<PER>5ce4c4e38c5a90d84969094d</PER> fruitful journey started in 1973. I joined K K M Higher Secondary School in Vandithavalam as physics teacher and retired in 2005. Even as a full-time teacher, I used to impart free tuition in science and maths. It is a full time job and a passion, <PER>5ce4c4e38c5a90d84969094d</PER> said.<PER>5ce4c4e38c5a90d84969094d</PER> also worked successfully to shift the pre-matric hostel from Walayar to Pattancherry. Currently, there are 78 students from Attappadi, Parambikulam, Nelliampathy and Kadappara in the hostel. This year, 14 students from the hostel came out with flying colours in the SSLC examinations . <PER>5ce4c4e38c5a90d84969094d</PER> imparts lessons to students of Class X, Plus One and Plus Two classes, besides those who want to appear for entrance examinations, said M Krishnadas, a former inmate of the hostel.After seeing the dedication of <PER>5ce4c4e38c5a90d84969094d</PER> we have decided to engage high school students and those who wish to appear for entrance exams from <PER>5ce4c4e38c5a90d84969094d</PER> tuition centre during weekends at IIT, Palakkad. Our faculty and students will provide orientation classes to them, said M C <PER>5ce4c3c58c5a90d8496612cc</PER>, professor in charge of student affairs at IIT, Palakkad.We have decided to associate with <PER>5ce4c3c58c5a90d8496612cc</PER> and have been bearing the tuition expenses of the Plus One and Plus Two students who have showed a spark in science subjects. We are also sponsoring 54 poor students who have secured admission on merit to government medical and engineering colleges in the last three academic years, said K <PER>ANIL KUMAR GARG</PER>, Chief Executive of the <ORG>AXIS BANK LIMITED</ORG>, Mumbai, and Chairman of the Palakkad-based Akshara Foundation. 
 --------------------------------------------------
PRAMOD SARAF 	 NATIONAL SPOT EXCHANGE LIMITED 
 58fd04f47be9e0580d5e045a The <ORG>NATIONAL SPOT EXCHANGE LIMITED</ORG> Investors Forum, on Tuesday, asked the government to supersede the present management of the commodity exchange with a respectable board from the members of the society.We want the government to take over <ORG>5ce4c37c8c5a90d849655b33</ORG>, the holding company of <ORG>NATIONAL SPOT EXCHANGE LIMITED</ORG>, as in the case of Satyam, said <PER>PRAMOD SARAF</PER>, Convenor, <ORG>NATIONAL SPOT EXCHANGE LIMITED</ORG> Investors Forum, here while addressing a press conference.This set up was needed to come out of all liabilities of the exchange, and then allow some others to run it, <PER>PRAMOD SARAF</PER> added. We met the Forward Markets Commission (FMC), the regulatory agency for commodity trading in the country, and they were telling us they would ensure equitable payment to all investors, said <PER>PRAMOD SARAF</PER>.<ORG>NATIONAL SPOT EXCHANGE LIMITED</ORG> Investors Forums objective is to represent and safeguard the interests of more than 15,000 investors in <ORG>NATIONAL SPOT EXCHANGE LIMITED</ORG>, which has defaulted in its payout. In the past 14 days, there have been numerous false statements, inconsistent disclosures, and complete lack of clarity on this issue, the forum said. The press conference was organised by <ORG>NATIONAL SPOT EXCHANGE LIMITED</ORG> Investors Forum in association with Commodity Participants Association of India, Association of <ORG>NATIONAL SPOT EXCHANGE LIMITED</ORG> Exchanges Members of India and BSE Brokers Forum. The forum posed questions to <ORG>NATIONAL SPOT EXCHANGE LIMITED</ORG>, <ORG>5ce4c37c8c5a90d849655b33</ORG> and MCX, Jignesh Shah, FMC, and the government about <ORG>NATIONAL SPOT EXCHANGE LIMITED</ORG> crisis, including why <ORG>NATIONAL SPOT EXCHANGE LIMITED</ORG> and Jignesh Shah have been so slow in making public details of the progress of payments and checking of stocks?<PER>PRAMOD SARAF</PER> also said that how <ORG>5ce4c37c8c5a90d849655b33</ORG> was allowed to run two commodity exchanges, <ORG>NATIONAL SPOT EXCHANGE LIMITED</ORG> and MCX. The directors of <ORG>NATIONAL SPOT EXCHANGE LIMITED</ORG> are the employees of MCX, this shows the conflict of interest.<PER>PRAMOD SARAF</PER> also questioned whether Jignesh Shah and <PER>PRAMOD SARAF</PER> management team still fit & proper to run commodity, currency and stock exchanges, and risk several thousand crores of public and institutions money? ``Why should MCX licence not be suspended, and also why should these promoters be allowed to run international exchanges and risk Indias reputation as well? <PER>PRAMOD SARAF</PER> asked.We want the government to take over <ORG>5ce4c37c8c5a90d849655b33</ORG> 
 --------------------------------------------------
RAMKUMAR VARADARAJAN 	 SRI MAHASAKTHI MILLS LIMITED 
 593cbe3c7be9e00dabcb8a30 S. Dinakaran, Joint Managing Director of <ORG>5ce4c3608c5a90d849651305</ORG>, has been elected chairman of Southern India Mills' Association for 2011-2012. A release here has said, <PER>RAMKUMAR VARADARAJAN</PER>, Managing Director of <ORG>SRI MAHASAKTHI MILLS LIMITED</ORG>, has been elected the Deputy Chairman of the association and <PER>5ce4c3078c5a90d8496441ec</PER>, Managing Director of <ORG>5ce4c4c88c5a90d84968bb58</ORG>, will be the vice-chairman of the association. 
 --------------------------------------------------
KAMAL SINGAL 	 ARVIND LIMITED 
 592861a57be9e0138af8ae06 Poor buying sentiments in the housing market of Ahmedabad seems to be pushing several large real-estate companies to explore business opportunities and diversify their risks in the tried and tested,affordable, format of one-bedroom-hall-kitchen or 1 BHK.<ORG>5ce4c39c8c5a90d84965b4e0</ORG> on Thursday announced their decision to build about 500 housing units in this format at the <ORG>5ce4c39c8c5a90d84965b4e0</ORG> Garden City project,where the firm has been developing two- and three BHK apartments that are currently priced over Rs 35 lakh and Rs 80 lakh respectively. <ORG>5ce4c39c8c5a90d84965b4e0</ORG> will be offering a 600 square feet apartment at prices starting from Rs 16.5 lakh,a company official said.One the top revenue earners for <ORG>5ce4c39c8c5a90d84965b4e0</ORG>,the <ORG>5ce4c39c8c5a90d84965b4e0</ORG> Garden City project contributed revenues to the tune of Rs 49.1 crore in the third quarter of the current financial year. This is a substantial 40 per cent drop in revenues when compared to Rs 82.3 crore it earned from the project during the same period last year.The decision to come up with 1 BHK housing units is seen as a move to bolster revenues in a market that has been stagnating since the last one year or so,say real estate experts.Jones Lang LaSalle (JLL),a global property consultant observes in its report on Affordable Housing,During the demand slowdown in 20082009,residential developers realised that they had concentrated development portfolios in upper-mid- and luxury segments,where the market has become very competitive in the last decade due to the entry of new players. Affordable housing segment provides an appropriate option to diversify their risks.However,we are yet to see a phase seen around 2008-09 when a large number of developers had suddenly taken up affordable housing, says <PER>5ce4c8e38c5a90d84973a265</PER>,head of Ahmedabad operations of JLL.Now that the supply in two and three BHK segments is more than the demand,we see developers moving on to the 1 BHK segment where the demand is high.Similar has been the case with Adani Township & Real Estate which is building a premium development in the city. The firm recently floated a new affordable housing project to tap the demand in this segment,that would release about 800 units of 1BHK and 2BHK houses that are priced between Rs 16-22 lakh.As per Central government figures,the urban housing shortage is estimated to be over 18 million for the next five year plan from 2012-17,of which 96 per cent are in economically weaker section (EWS) and low income group (LIG) categories.Experts also feel that the recent move of the Reserve Bank of India to allow external commercial borrowings up to $1 billion for low-cost affordable housing projects and the plan to allow more FDI in this segment would give a further boost.Another player in the segment,Tata Housing is already in the process of developing 1,800 units in Ahmedabad,jointly with <ORG>ARVIND LIMITED</ORG> Real Estate,is seeing decent demand. We have been able to sell houses in the second phase at a decent pace. We are now planning a third phase as well, said <PER>KAMAL SINGAL</PER>,CEO,<ORG>ARVIND LIMITED</ORG> Real Estate,the realty arm of textile major <ORG>ARVIND LIMITED</ORG>.Tata Housing signed a memorandum of understanding with the Gujarat government worth Rs 3,500 crore to develop affordable homes in Ahmedabad at the recently held Vibrant Gujarat Global Investors Summit 2013 held in January .This edition of the summit attracted about Rs 1.34 lakh crore investments to the sector where firms from United States,Finland,United Kingdom and others had promised investments to bring in technology and provide technical support to build affordable houses in Gujarat.These initiatives by private developers comes at a time when the state government has promised to build 50 lakh affordable homes across the state within five years.To provide the necessary impetus,the Ahmedabad Urban Development Authority in its recent city development plan has earmarked a 76 square kilometre area as a special affordable housing zone.For all the latest India News, download Indian Express App now 
 --------------------------------------------------
SANJAY GUPTA 	 HERO CORPORATE SERVICE LIMITED 
 58fee4ae7be9e04117d22f21 More investors claiming to have lost money in the Rs.400 crore fraud at Citibank's Gurgaon branch have surfaced, taking the total number of such entities to about 40, police sources said on Monday.Most of the investors have approached the police and their complaints are likely to be clubbed together for investigation, sources said.As per the latest estimates, about 40 investors -- including the promoters of Hero Group and high net-worth individual <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f2</PER>, Managing Director of Helion Advisors --lost money in the Ponzi scheme floated by Citibank Relationship Manager <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f6</PER>.The investors have submitted their claims and stated their positions, sources said, adding that out of the 40 investors, nearly 20 are corporate entities.Until now, only one HNI client  <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f2</PER>, who lost about Rs.33 crore -- had filed an FIR in which <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f2</PER> accused the top officials of Citibank NA, including the country head, of being the perpetrators. Based on <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f2</PER> FIR, the police will investigate if there is a criminal conspiracy on the part of the bank, sources said, adding that a few officials of the Gurgaon branch will also be questioned.The entities whose funds were diverted by <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f6</PER> into the accounts of <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f6</PER> relatives include <ORG>HERO CORPORATE SERVICE LIMITED</ORG> (Rs.13.75 crore), OKS Span Tech (Rs.2 crore) and Satyam Auto (Rs.25 crore).Further, Mayar Infratech (Rs.24 crore), Spaid (Rs.62 crore), Karopat Pad (Rs.8 crore), Sunil Kant & Sons (Rs.3 crore), Aero Infratec (Rs.25 crore), Hero Exports (Rs.97 crore), <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f4</PER> (Rs.5 crore), <ORG>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08ee</ORG> (Rs.2.5 crore) and Munab Braej (Rs.71 crore) fell prey to the scam.In another development, the police are likely to question the co-accused in the fraud case, <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08ed</PER> and <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08ec</PER>, who are the maternal grandparents of <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f6</PER>.Meanwhile, SEBI officials have returned to Mumbai after a second round of investigations and may come again, sources said.SEBI is investigating as per its own agenda and the police are sharing information with the capital market regulator, sources said.Asked about <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f6</PER>'s iPad, believed to be crucial evidence in the case, sources said efforts are on to retrieve it. They added that the police have already obtained all the required documents and more evidence is being collected.Sources also said that <PER>SANJAY GUPTA</PER>, Assistant Vice-President of <ORG>HERO CORPORATE SERVICE LIMITED</ORG>, another accused in the case, had received a Rs.20 crore commission from <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f6</PER> for bringing investment into the Ponzi scheme.During interrogation, <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f5</PER> disclosed that <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f5</PER> paid Rs.96 lakh as commission to <PER>5ce4c3df8c5a90d8496657c3</PER>, Rs.5.35 lakh to Bharat Goel and Rs.53.5 lakh to <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f3</PER>. These are officials of Hero Exports that helped divert their company's funds.Hero Exports invested Rs.97 crore in the scheme floated by <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f6</PER>.<PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f5</PER> also told the police that the account of BG Finance in Axis Bank was jointly owned by <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f5</PER> and <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f5</PER> wife <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f5</PER> and a commission of Rs.14.95 crore was deposited in it by <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f6</PER>. Of this, <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f5</PER> invested Rs.7.5 crore in the stock market through <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f6</PER>, sources said.Sources also said that while seeking an extension of <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f5</PER>'s remand the police had argued in court that custody was required so they could arrest <PER>5ce4c6088c5a90d8496c08f6</PER> accomplices. - PTI 
 --------------------------------------------------
UMADEVI MAHESHWARI 	 MUMBAI METRO TRANSPORT PRIVATE LIMITED 
 593fe17e7be9e024e45972ee Versova-Andheri-Ghatkopar corridor,Construction of 175-m-long cable-stayed bridge will kick off in a weekThe construction of the citys second cable-stayed bridge,a section of the Versova-Andheri-Ghatkopar Metro Rail corridor,is all set to commence. With work on the pylons now nearing completion on either side of the Western Express Highway at Andheri,work will begin within a week on constructing a 175-metre-long complex structure that will zoom across the 13-metre-tall Jog flyover 22 metres above ground,approximately the height of a 10-storey building.This cable-stayed portion is one of the most crucial parts of the 11.4-km route of the citys first Metro rail corridor and will run perpendicular to the highway and the flyover.Officials of <ORG>MUMBAI METRO TRANSPORT PRIVATE LIMITED</ORG> have promised there will be no traffic diversions on the road even while work continues 247. We are using a very advanced technology to build this bridge. The entire structure would be constructed segment-wise on site and there would be no need for closure of any road during the construction. The first segment of the bridge would be cast within a week on the Ghatkopar-end of the bridge, said K P <PER>UMADEVI MAHESHWARI</PER>,Director of <ORG>MUMBAI METRO TRANSPORT PRIVATE LIMITED</ORG>.While the deck of the cable-stayed bridge will be 22 metres high,the two pylons on either side stand 41 metres tall. Cable-stayed bridges are built with one or more columns,called pylons,with cables supporting the bridges deck. Such bridges dont require construction of piers on the ground where there are obstacles or lack of space,in this case the very busy Jog flyover.According to <ORG>UMADEVI MAHESHWARI</ORG>49c8c5a90d849684caf</PER>,a form-traveller,a 48-tonne mould of the segment would be used to cast the 3-metre-long segment,which will be later stressed with cables for strength. While a section of Bandra-Worli Sea Link is the citys first cable-stayed bridge,that was constructed with pre-cast segments that were then lifted from barges by cranes and later stressed together.Four such form-travellers would be used to expedite the work. After the segments concrete gains required strength,longitudinal prestressing and stay cables will be installed and stressed as per approved specifications and drawings. We expect the work on the portion to be complete by September, <ORG>UMADEVI MAHESHWARI</ORG>49c8c5a90d849684caf</PER> added.There would be 20 cables to make the bridge look aesthetically beautiful. The sheer complexity of the cable-stayed bridge,that is expected to cost around Rs 16 crore,would force the concessionaire to deploy close to 400 labourers and engineers day and night. Except concreting,for which we require concrete mixers and huge concrete pouring booms,all other work would be done during the day, <ORG>UMADEVI MAHESHWARI</ORG>49c8c5a90d849684caf</PER> added.The <ORG>MUMBAI METRO TRANSPORT PRIVATE LIMITED</ORG> engineers will be aided by Swiss firm VSL International Ltd,experienced in building such bridges.<ORG>MUMBAI METRO TRANSPORT PRIVATE LIMITED</ORG> officials said there will be three spans. The main span over the flyover will be 83 metres long,the other two on either side of the flyover will stretch 46 metres. The four form-travellersworking from the two ends will cast segments and come towards the centre of the flyover to complete the bridge. At that point,we may have to stop use of the flyover. We would do this during the night when there is not much traffic. Motorists can use the road below for a few hours at night, <ORG>UMADEVI MAHESHWARI</ORG>49c8c5a90d849684caf</PER> added.For all the latest Cities News, download Indian Express App 
 --------------------------------------------------
JAYKUMAR KHANDERAO PATHARE 	 DHANLAXMI BANK LIMITED 
 58fd9efa7be9e012bf28478c KOCHI: The call came from Madhya Pradesh a few weeks ago, recalls Rajiv, a native of Kochi and a victim of an attempted phishing call.The caller said that she was calling on behalf of State Bank of India and wanted to confirm my address to issue a new debit card, which was supposed to be safer. Even though the expiry period of my existing card was August 2018, I was glad that the bank is concerned about the safety of my account, he added.But the call quickly took a turn toward the suspicious. After confirming his address, the caller asked for the card number. She even told me the last eight numbers, recalls Rajiv. Then, he was asked for the Card Verification Value (CVV). But Rajiv received an from his bank to confirm a payment of `10,000 providing the CVV. Rajiv spooked and cut the call. She even dared to tell me that I should not disclose CVV to anyone other than her. I smelled a rat , he admitted.Rajiv is not alone. Had he disclosed the number, he might have ended up among the innocent duped that fall for phishing attempts like these every day. Rajiv contacted the bank and they confirmed that it was a fraud and, upon their advice, has applied for a new debit card.The recent data breach brings into stark focus the danger to our hard earned money in a world of electronic, impresonal transactions. Despite the size of the breach, many have been lucky to have not lost any money. But our cards are still vulnerable to financial fraud at all times. According to the <ORG>5ce4c3088c5a90d8496443b2</ORG>, illegal withdrawals linked to the data breach were limited to 641 customers of 19 banks and the total amount was a mere `1.3 crore.But the next such lapse might be more severe and the incident is already raising concerns on the robustness of <ORG>5ce4c3088c5a90d8496443b2</ORG> ATM banking systems. Experts suggest that spread of biometric ATMs and extending the One Time Password (OTP) feature to ATM transactions as safety measures.Banks in India have introduced biometric automatic teller machines (ATMs) as it seems to be an effective way of preventing PIN theft and is also a channel to expand a banks reach to the rural and illiterate masses. Globally, biometric as a method of authentication gains traction, said P G <PER>JAYKUMAR KHANDERAO PATHARE</PER>, Former Managing Director and CEO, <ORG>DHANLAXMI BANK LIMITED</ORG>.The biometric ATMs replace personal identity numbers (PIN) with thumb impressions. The fingerprint scanner fitted in the machine only recognizes thecustomers thumb impression, <PER>JAYKUMAR KHANDERAO PATHARE</PER> suggests.Biometric ATMs might be safer, but the drawback is that If the account holder is bedridden and in need of money from <PER>JAYKUMAR KHANDERAO PATHARE</PER> account <PER>JAYKUMAR KHANDERAO PATHARE</PER> will not be able to get it as <PER>JAYKUMAR KHANDERAO PATHARE</PER> has to present in person at the ATM. The other option is the extension of OTP precautions to ATM withdrawals.The negative side of this extra safety is that it is time consuming and inconvenient.Abraham Tharian, Former Executive Director, South Indian Bank added that in order to avoid skimming the customer must ensure that the card does not go beyond his eyesight.The Reserve Bank is now closely monitoring the situation and in the future it will come forward with safety features in order to safer guard the interest of banking customer, he added.According to <PER>JAYKUMAR KHANDERAO PATHARE</PER>, the massive distribution of cards in the recent years has led to such fraudulent activities. <PER>JAYKUMAR KHANDERAO PATHARE</PER> has a point as there are 69.7 crore debit cards and 2.6 crore credit cards in the country at the end of the month of July, 2016.Safety Tips Always pay close attention to the ATM and your surroundings. Dont select an ATM at the corner of a building. Use an ATM located near the center of a building. It is always safe to use ATMs of your own bank. It also makes it easy to complain if you encounter any problems. Chip cards are safer. So if your card is electromagnetic replace it with a chip card Change PIN number every three months. Do not ever disclose numbers on the card to anyone. Do your automated banking in a public, well-lighted location that is free of shrubbery and decorative partitions or dividers. If you have started a transaction and notice something suspicious, cancel the transaction and take your card. Be wary of people trying to help you with ATM transactions. Be aware of anyone sitting in a parked car nearby. Do not allow people to look over your shoulder as you enteryour PIN. Closely monitor your bank statements and balances, and immediately report any problems to your bank. 
 --------------------------------------------------
SUDHIR BHALLA 	 KARNATAKA POWER TRANSMISSION CORPORATION LIMITED 
 5928be447be9e0137c7802b6 CM's aides transferred without his knowledgeLast updated: 17 December, 2011Bangalore, Dec 17, DHNS: 11:06 ISTTwo special officers to Chief Minister D V Sadananda Gowda were relieved from duty and transferred back to their parent department on Friday. Interestingly, the chief minister himself wasnt in the know of this development.According to sources, special officers <PER>SUDHIR BHALLA</PER> and <PER>5ce4c65f8c5a90d8496cddcf</PER> were appointed by former chief minister B S Yeddyurappa. They were relieved from the posts, on instructions by the family members of Yeddyurappa.Sources said that <PER>SUDHIR BHALLA</PER>, who was earlier with <ORG>KARNATAKA POWER TRANSMISSION CORPORATION LIMITED</ORG> as an assistant engineer, took a transfer to BWSSB as an AEE.<PER>5ce4c65f8c5a90d8496cddcf</PER>, who was a junior college lecturer, took a transfer to the revenue department as a Grade 2 tahsildar. They have now been deputed to these respective departments. 
 --------------------------------------------------
NANDAKUMAR KALATH 	 MANAPPURAM FINANCE LIMITED 
