It has been a quiet first year for <PER>5982d0919855b7221e18525b</PER> at the helm of the $97 billion <ORG>5982d0719855b7221e183731</ORG>. No big-bang acquisitions or divestments, nor any major restructuring of the group companies or such other high profile moves. Much of Mr. Mistrys time since he took over the reins from Ratan Tata in December 2012 has been spent to study and assess the group and understand its businesses.Insiders say that Mr. Mistry has logged thousands of air miles visiting companies and facilities in India and across the world to get a grip on the group and its operations. That, it should be said, is a year well spent because it is not easy to get your arms around a conglomerate as unwieldy and complex as the Tatas. His New Year message to employees acknowledges that it has been a period of learning for him: I have come to realise the distinctiveness of every Tata enterprise, and that each needs to be viewed in a manner that is appreciative of its uniqueness.A careful study of Mr. Mistrys moves offers insight into the mans thinking and his leadership style. First, hes shown a clear preference for a young leadership team, and is taking his time assembling it. Second, he has demonstrated the ability to take tough, unpalatable decisions that are in the long-term interests of the business.Third, he has clearly indicated that he will not hesitate to enter a business that has long-term prospects, even if in the short-term it is vested with uncertainty. Equally, he has also proved that he is not averse to letting go opportunities if they will impede the functioning of the other group businesses.A young teamMr. Mistrys first major move signalled the importance that he attached to the values represented by the Tata brand. He created a position of Brand Custodian and Chief Ethics Officer, and appointed 44-year-old <PER>5982d06d9855b7221e183401</PER>, an 18-year veteran of the group to the post, leaving no doubt that he would march on in the path laid out by his eminent predecessors.Soon after, he set up the <ORG>598994719855b71f8475db9f</ORG> (GEC), which replaced two similar bodies that guided the business during Mr. Tatas time.With veterans such as <ORG>598994719855b71f8475db8f</ORG> <PER>598994719855b71f8475dba5</PER> and <PER>598994719855b71f8475db98</PER> who were Mr. Tatas lieutenants retiring and others such as <PER>5982d07f9855b7221e184312</PER>, <PER>5982d2f19855b7221e1a564a</PER>, and <PER>598994719855b71f8475dba2</PER> moving into non-executive positions on the <ORG>5982d07b9855b7221e183f82</ORG> board, the way was clear for Mr. Mistry to assemble his own team.<PER>598994719855b71f8475dba4</PER>, former CEO of <ORG>5982d06d9855b7221e18340e</ORG>1e18340e</ORG>, who joined the group in 2012 when Mr. Mistry was serving his apprenticeship period, <PER>5982d1cc9855b7221e19543d</PER>, who moved in from <ORG>5982d09c9855b7221e185afb</ORG>, and <PER>598994719855b71f8475dba7</PER> formed the GEC along with Mr. Mistry. Soon, <PER>598994719855b71f8475db9a</PER>, who was Professor of Marketing in the <ORG>5982d2629855b7221e19d199</ORG>, joined them to make up a five-member GEC. Interestingly, the average age of the group is 45, about the same as Mr. Mistrys.Clearly, Mr. Mistry, who will have a clear three decades at the helm if all goes well, is assembling a team for the long haul. There are still a couple of positions that are open, for finance and M&A.Tough movesThree clear instances prove Mr. Mistrys capability to take tough, painful decisions when necessary. The biggest of the three, of course, was the decision to drop the $1.8-billion bid by Indian Hotels for <ORG>598994719855b71f8475db9c</ORG>.The purchase of a 10.1 per cent stake in Orient-Express in 2007 by Indian Hotels and the subsequent bid to acquire the whole equity in 2012 were born out of the personal desire of Mr. Ratan Tata to own an iconic hospitality brand; to withdraw the bid was indeed a significant move. Yet, it was also a pragmatic one. Though this resulted in a charge of Rs.370 crore in Indian Hotels balance sheet, it lifted a huge burden on the company, which was not performing very well in its business anyway.Indian Hotels reported a loss of Rs.433 crore in the second quarter ended September 2013 that includes the write-off.The second bold decision was to take a Rs.2,460-crore asset impairment charge on Tata Powers balance-sheet for 2012-13 due to higher-than-planned coal import prices; this plunged the company into a Rs.1,087 crore loss. Yet again, it was a prudent decision that can be held out as an example of best practice for companies.The third example was the $1.6-billion goodwill write-off in Tata Steels balance sheet for 2012-13. The $13-billion <ORG>5982d2419855b7221e19b854</ORG> acquisition has shrunk in value due to the economic crisis in Europe and falling steel prices, and, therefore, a write-down was warranted. Of course, there are those who believe that the write-off is too little but yet it must be acknowledged that accepting a mistake and taking a penalty for that is not easy.Not intimidated by turbulenceIf success in business is all about taking a long-term view and backing yourself through the short-term problems, then Mr. Mistry demonstrated that by setting foot into two highly controversial sectors  airlines and multi-brand retail.The joint ventures with Air Asia for a budget airline and with <ORG>5982d1169855b7221e18c073</ORG> for a full-service carrier come at a time when the industry is in turbulence and airline companies are bleeding. Mr. Mistry is clearly playing for the long haul, and hoping to ride out the short-term with the power of the respective brands and the expertise that they bring to the table.The joint venture with <ORG>598994719855b71f8475db99</ORG> for multi-brand retail is similar with the added dimension of regulatory uncertainty.The group already has a retail business in Trent but the one planned with Tesco is likely to be qualitatively different. While the promise of business is indeed there given the growing middle-class, urbanisation and the advent of consumer culture, the joint venture has to push past regulatory hurdles. And, it has to do it state-by-state across India.The groups decision to pull out its application for a banking licence from the RBI was a pragmatic one. Here was a tremendous business opportunity for the conglomerate but yet it opted out once it became clear that a licence will be a shackle on the financing arms of some of its other companies and certainly on <ORG>598994719855b71f8475dba6</ORG>, its <ORG>598994719855b71f8475db90</ORG>.Consolidation phaseIf the first year was all about understanding the group, the second one is likely to be one of consolidation for Mr. Mistry. The telecom business is not going anywhere, and it should not be a surprise if a decision is made to exit it. The one bad story of the Ratan Tata-era was the mess-up of the telecom business, and Mr. Mistry will surely be trying to correct it.If his New Year message is any indication, Mr. Mistry is also likely to push for exploiting synergies across group companies. He has also clearly signified his intent to invest in innovation and R&D, which augurs well for the conglomerate.The steel and power businesses need to be steadied while the hotels business needs support.The best thing that can happen for Mr. Mistry will be resurgence in the economy which will lift most of the groups businesses. But that is unlikely to happen before the end of 2014 which means that much of his time and energy will be consumed in managing the present. Moves aimed at the future will have to wait. But then, whats the hurry anyway when he has all the time to lead the group into the next level?raghuvir.s@thehindu.co.in
It has been a quiet first year for <PER>5982d0919855b7221e18525b</PER> at the helm of the $97 billion <ORG>5982d0719855b7221e183731</ORG>. No big-bang acquisitions or divestments, nor any major restructuring of the group companies or such other high profile moves. Much of Mr. Mistrys time since he took over the reins from Ratan Tata in December 2012 has been spent to study and assess the group and understand its businesses.Insiders say that Mr. Mistry has logged thousands of air miles visiting companies and facilities in India and across the world to get a grip on the group and its operations. That, it should be said, is a year well spent because it is not easy to get your arms around a conglomerate as unwieldy and complex as the Tatas. His New Year message to employees acknowledges that it has been a period of learning for him: I have come to realise the distinctiveness of every Tata enterprise, and that each needs to be viewed in a manner that is appreciative of its uniqueness.A careful study of Mr. Mistrys moves offers insight into the mans thinking and his leadership style. First, hes shown a clear preference for a young leadership team, and is taking his time assembling it. Second, he has demonstrated the ability to take tough, unpalatable decisions that are in the long-term interests of the business.Third, he has clearly indicated that he will not hesitate to enter a business that has long-term prospects, even if in the short-term it is vested with uncertainty. Equally, he has also proved that he is not averse to letting go opportunities if they will impede the functioning of the other group businesses.A young teamMr. Mistrys first major move signalled the importance that he attached to the values represented by the Tata brand. He created a position of Brand Custodian and Chief Ethics Officer, and appointed 44-year-old <PER>5982d06d9855b7221e183401</PER>, an 18-year veteran of the group to the post, leaving no doubt that he would march on in the path laid out by his eminent predecessors.Soon after, he set up the <ORG>598994719855b71f8475db9f</ORG> (GEC), which replaced two similar bodies that guided the business during Mr. Tatas time.With veterans such as <ORG>598994719855b71f8475db8f</ORG> <PER>598994719855b71f8475dba5</PER> and <PER>598994719855b71f8475db98</PER> who were Mr. Tatas lieutenants retiring and others such as <PER>5982d07f9855b7221e184312</PER>, <PER>5982d2f19855b7221e1a564a</PER>, and <PER>598994719855b71f8475dba2</PER> moving into non-executive positions on the <ORG>5982d07b9855b7221e183f82</ORG> board, the way was clear for Mr. Mistry to assemble his own team.<PER>598994719855b71f8475dba4</PER>, former CEO of <ORG>5982d06d9855b7221e18340e</ORG>1e18340e</ORG>, who joined the group in 2012 when Mr. Mistry was serving his apprenticeship period, <PER>5982d1cc9855b7221e19543d</PER>, who moved in from <ORG>5982d09c9855b7221e185afb</ORG>, and <PER>598994719855b71f8475dba7</PER> formed the GEC along with Mr. Mistry. Soon, <PER>598994719855b71f8475db9a</PER>, who was Professor of Marketing in the <ORG>5982d2629855b7221e19d199</ORG>, joined them to make up a five-member GEC. Interestingly, the average age of the group is 45, about the same as Mr. Mistrys.Clearly, Mr. Mistry, who will have a clear three decades at the helm if all goes well, is assembling a team for the long haul. There are still a couple of positions that are open, for finance and M&A.Tough movesThree clear instances prove Mr. Mistrys capability to take tough, painful decisions when necessary. The biggest of the three, of course, was the decision to drop the $1.8-billion bid by Indian Hotels for <ORG>598994719855b71f8475db9c</ORG>.The purchase of a 10.1 per cent stake in Orient-Express in 2007 by Indian Hotels and the subsequent bid to acquire the whole equity in 2012 were born out of the personal desire of Mr. Ratan Tata to own an iconic hospitality brand; to withdraw the bid was indeed a significant move. Yet, it was also a pragmatic one. Though this resulted in a charge of Rs.370 crore in Indian Hotels balance sheet, it lifted a huge burden on the company, which was not performing very well in its business anyway.Indian Hotels reported a loss of Rs.433 crore in the second quarter ended September 2013 that includes the write-off.The second bold decision was to take a Rs.2,460-crore asset impairment charge on Tata Powers balance-sheet for 2012-13 due to higher-than-planned coal import prices; this plunged the company into a Rs.1,087 crore loss. Yet again, it was a prudent decision that can be held out as an example of best practice for companies.The third example was the $1.6-billion goodwill write-off in Tata Steels balance sheet for 2012-13. The $13-billion <ORG>5982d2419855b7221e19b854</ORG> acquisition has shrunk in value due to the economic crisis in Europe and falling steel prices, and, therefore, a write-down was warranted. Of course, there are those who believe that the write-off is too little but yet it must be acknowledged that accepting a mistake and taking a penalty for that is not easy.Not intimidated by turbulenceIf success in business is all about taking a long-term view and backing yourself through the short-term problems, then Mr. Mistry demonstrated that by setting foot into two highly controversial sectors  airlines and multi-brand retail.The joint ventures with Air Asia for a budget airline and with <ORG>5982d1169855b7221e18c073</ORG> for a full-service carrier come at a time when the industry is in turbulence and airline companies are bleeding. Mr. Mistry is clearly playing for the long haul, and hoping to ride out the short-term with the power of the respective brands and the expertise that they bring to the table.The joint venture with <ORG>598994719855b71f8475db99</ORG> for multi-brand retail is similar with the added dimension of regulatory uncertainty.The group already has a retail business in Trent but the one planned with Tesco is likely to be qualitatively different. While the promise of business is indeed there given the growing middle-class, urbanisation and the advent of consumer culture, the joint venture has to push past regulatory hurdles. And, it has to do it state-by-state across India.The groups decision to pull out its application for a banking licence from the RBI was a pragmatic one. Here was a tremendous business opportunity for the conglomerate but yet it opted out once it became clear that a licence will be a shackle on the financing arms of some of its other companies and certainly on <ORG>598994719855b71f8475dba6</ORG>, its <ORG>598994719855b71f8475db90</ORG>.Consolidation phaseIf the first year was all about understanding the group, the second one is likely to be one of consolidation for Mr. Mistry. The telecom business is not going anywhere, and it should not be a surprise if a decision is made to exit it. The one bad story of the Ratan Tata-era was the mess-up of the telecom business, and Mr. Mistry will surely be trying to correct it.If his New Year message is any indication, Mr. Mistry is also likely to push for exploiting synergies across group companies. He has also clearly signified his intent to invest in innovation and R&D, which augurs well for the conglomerate.The steel and power businesses need to be steadied while the hotels business needs support.The best thing that can happen for Mr. Mistry will be resurgence in the economy which will lift most of the groups businesses. But that is unlikely to happen before the end of 2014 which means that much of his time and energy will be consumed in managing the present. Moves aimed at the future will have to wait. But then, whats the hurry anyway when he has all the time to lead the group into the next level?raghuvir.s@thehindu.co.in
: In their own words, it was a dream come true for the five young entrepreneurs with their companies incubated at the Startup Village in Kalamassery to tour the cradle of information technology, the Silicon Valley, in December last year under a programme sponsored by the <ORG>5982d0659855b7221e182d87</ORG>.The exciting trip exposed them to the myriad dimensions of the celebrated IT ecosystem in California which they said, at a media conference on Thursday, offered them better awareness on company-building than years of education and reading up had. They said the visit boosted their confidence in their ideas and opened the doors for the second round of funding of their startup initiatives. Young entrepreneur <PER>598996539855b71f847748c5</PER>, founder of <ORG>598996539855b71f847748bd</ORG>, was surprised to see his dream company <ORG>598996539855b71f847748c0</ORG> operating from a space crammed with a bench and four chairs. For fellow entrepreneur <PER>598996539855b71f847748c1</PER>, it opened up a new business avenue as multi-billion mobile app company <ORG>598996539855b71f847748be</ORG> showed its interest in forging partnership with his fledgling firm, <ORG>598996539855b71f847748c2</ORG>The group got selected for the tour from the maiden annual SV Square project of the State government. On return, they were busy sharing their experience with students across colleges. But over the last two days, they got a chance to brief the Chief Minister and the <ORG>5982d1c49855b7221e194d98</ORG> on the fruitfulness of the trip.
The <ORG>5982d06e9855b7221e183508</ORG> (FDA) has banned the import of products from <ORG>598996499855b71f847740ec</ORG> plant in <STA>5982d0659855b7221e182d26</STA> [the companys fourth unit] due to manufacturing violation, a move that will halt shipment of all products of the pharmaceutical company to the U.S.Reacting to the development, the companys scrip tumbled 19.33 per cent to Rs.336.50 from its previous close on the BSE on Friday.In its order issued on Thursday, the FDA prohibited <ORG>5982d1b39855b7221e193e86</ORG> from producing and distributing drugs from its Toansa facility in Punjab.The U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) today [Friday] notified Ranbaxy Laboratories Ltd. that it is prohibited from manufacturing and distributing active pharmaceutical ingredients (APIs) from its facility in <LOC>598995699855b71f847699c5</LOC>, India, for FDA-regulated drug products, it said in a statement available on the regulators website.The FDA ban on Ranbaxys Toansa plant followed an inspection completed on January 11, which identified significant CGMP (current good manufacturing practice) violations.The questions about Ranbaxys Toansa facilities come in the wake of the firm pleading guilty to seven criminal charges relating to fraud last May, and coughing up $500 million in fines. To date the FDA has restricted imports from three other Ranbaxy facilities in India, including Paonta Sahib, Dewas and Mohali.The agency said the Toansa facility was now subject to certain terms of a consent decree of permanent injunction entered against Ranbaxy in January, 2012.Under the decree, the FDA has issued an order prohibiting Ranbaxy from distributing in the U.S. drugs manufactured using API from Toansa, including drugs made by Ranbaxys Ohm Laboratories facility in <STA>5982d2a09855b7221e1a071a</STA>, it said.The U.S. regulator had previously barred products from the companys facilities in Paonta Sahib, Dewas and Mohali in India as part of a 2012 consent decree.We are taking swift action to prevent substandard quality products from reaching U.S. consumers, said <PER>5989965c9855b71f84774e2c</PER>, acting director of the <ORG>5989965d9855b71f84774e2d</ORG> in the <ORG>5989965c9855b71f84774e2b</ORG> and Research.Ranbaxy said it was disappointed with the FDAs action and it had voluntarily suspended shipments of products from the Toansa facility to the U.S. market when it received the inspection findings.In a statement, Ranbaxy Chief Executive Officer and Managing Director <PER>5989965c9855b71f84774e29</PER> said, This development is clearly unacceptable and an appropriate management action will be taken upon completion of the internal investigation.Further, the company said it would like to apologise to all its stakeholders for the inconvenience caused by the suspension, adding that Ranbaxy would co-operate with the USFDA and comply with the consent decree in both letter and spirit.
The U.S. health regulator plans to conduct workshops across India in the next one year to sanitise Indian drug companies about the changing quality requirements in the American market.The matter came up during a meeting between chief executives of drug companies and <ORG>5982d06e9855b7221e183508</ORG> (USFDA) Commissioner <PER>5982d1429855b7221e18e31b</PER>.<ORG>5982d2989855b7221e1a005e</ORG> Chairman <PER>598997849855b71f8478634c</PER> said the plan to conduct workshops in India was part of the USFDAs strategy to let Indian companies be more aware of the changes happening in the U.S. in terms of the requirement for quality.One of their (USFDA) objectives is to sensitise here in India about these changes. In fact, the USFDA is planning a workshop over the next one year at 3-4 locations to clarify what are the new requirements and what are the expectations of the USFDA, Mr. Khorakiwala told reporters here.During the meeting, which was attended by chiefs of pharma companies, including <ORG>5982d1b39855b7221e193e86</ORG> Chief Executive Officer and Managing Director <PER>5989965c9855b71f84774e29</PER>, <ORG>5982d1209855b7221e18c705</ORG> Founder and Managing Director <PER>598997849855b71f8478634d</PER> and Mr. Khorakiwala, the Indian delegation asked the U.S. regulator team to continue with the high-level interactions.  PTI
<ORG>5982d2399855b7221e19b12c</ORG> has appointed <PER>5982d0749855b7221e1839f0</PER> as CEO of the company. Prior to joining RCom, he worked with <ORG>5982d1b99855b7221e194440</ORG> for more than 10 years. <PER>5982d0899855b7221e184a44</PER>, CEO Wireless, has been entrusted with enhanced responsibilities as CEO, Consumer Business. Punit Garg will continue as CEO of <ORG>5982d29e9855b7221e1a055f</ORG> and <ORG>5982d1939855b7221e19210e</ORG> business. <PER>5989976d9855b71f84784d37</PER> is the CEO of <ORG>598997949855b71f84787201</ORG>. An <ORG>598997949855b71f84787204</ORG> has been constituted, comprising the senior management of the company, the company said.  Special Correspondent
The <ORG>5982d0659855b7221e182d87</ORG> on Friday launched a new housing scheme by giving aid to widowed and divorced women of minority religions.Inaugurating the first instalment of the housing aid distribution at a function held at the Collectorate here, Minister for Urban Affairs and Welfare of Minorities <PER>5989946a9855b71f8475d5f7</PER> said that more beneficiaries would be included in the scheme soon.The government is providing Rs. 2 lakh each to 250 minority widows and divorcees across the State.Fifty-four of them are from <STA>5982d0c09855b7221e187a22</STA>.The Minister said that the scheme would be expanded to cover more beneficiaries.Mentioning a series of projects being implemented by the <ORG>5989953c9855b71f84767796</ORG>, Mr. Ali said that the State government was trying hard to change the notion harboured by the people of Malabar that government jobs were unreachable for them.Providing house and drinking water alone will not help to uplift the minorities. What is essential for them is education, said the Minister.Presenting a report, District Collector K. Biju said that 54 beneficiaries were selected in the district from 963 applications. When 938 applicants were Muslim, 25 were Christian.Fifty of the beneficiaries are Muslim and four are Christian.P. Ubaidulla, MLA, presided. <ORG>5989955e9855b71f84769184</ORG> head <PER>598995a39855b71f8476c487</PER> welcomed the gathering.<ORG>598998319855b71f8479072b</ORG> director <PER>598995fb9855b71f84770645</PER>, Malappuram Municipal vice-chairperson <PER>5989947f9855b71f8475e5b1</PER>, Opposition Leader in Municipality Paloli Kunhimohammed, Municipal councillor <PER>598998319855b71f8479072c</PER> spoke.Additional District Magistrate <PER>5982d10a9855b7221e18b7ac</PER> proposed a vote of thanks.Rs. 2 lakh to be provided to 250 widows54 beneficiaries selected from 963 applicants
A 24-year-old postgraduate student of social work died around midnight on Thursday in Vellore, three months after he was bitten by a pup at <MISC>5989954d9855b71f847684bc</MISC>684bc</ORG> in East Tambaram.<PER>598998349855b71f84790aa9</PER> was petting a couple of pups that had strayed into the campus in the second week of November when one of them bit him. A classmate accompanying him was also bitten.Both students were taken to the medical centre on the campus and administered tetanus shots. Alans classmate subsequently underwent a complete anti-rabies vaccination course, while Alan did not, authorities told The Hindu.On Wednesday, Alan developed high fever and began displaying symptoms of hydrophobia. He was taken to a private hospital in the city and then to <ORG>5982d07e9855b7221e1841b0</ORG>rom there, he was shifted to the <ORG>5982d15a9855b7221e18f5df</ORG> of <ORG>5982d1839855b7221e19146e</ORG>9146e</MISC> in Vellore.He failed to respond to treatment and died around midnight, <PER>598995029855b71f84764b1e</PER>, his father, said. We were not aware that it was serious. He had only told us that it was a minor bite from a pup, Mr. Samuel said.Alans death left his relatives, friends and teachers devastated. He loved pets, especially the Labrador they had at home, said <PER>598998349855b71f84790aaf</PER>, his aunt. The family had given away the dog last year after his mother <PER>598998349855b71f84790aaa</PER> fell while taking the Labrador for a walkAlan, an engineering graduate, worked in the software industry for two years but his heart was set on social work and he joined the college in 2013, his friends said.It is really shocking. This is the first such incident in the college and we will take steps to put an end to this problem, said principal <PER>598998349855b71f84790aab</PER>. He said that walls had been built around most of the college compound, except for a small stretch and noted that dogs were a threat to the deer on campus too.The college is spread over more than 360 acres and large parts are covered with thick vegetation. Attempts made with the cooperation of the Tambaram Municipality to trap stray dogs are not always successful as they hide amidst the vegetation, faculty said.With an increase in the number of complaints related to stray dogs from residents, the municipality is looking to expand its animal birth control project.To identify sterilised dogs, a small cut is made on the ear after surgery.The dogs are vaccinated for rabies and are released after their surgical wounds are healed, staff said.A senior official of the <ORG>598994ba9855b71f847613ac</ORG> said, We have to follow certain rules in handling stray dogs and abide by guidelines as laid down by <ORG>5982d0c29855b7221e187bae</ORG> of India.Animal rights activists noted that while precautionary measures were necessary, there should be no large-scale culling of dogs.
A five-member committee set up by the <ORG>5982d0be9855b7221e187851</ORG> to recommend the location of a new Capital for the residuary State of Andhra Pradesh will be headed by former Union Urban Development Secretary <PER>598997de9855b71f8478b8fc</PER>.Among the others appointed as members of the committee are former School of Planning and Architecture dean K.T. Ravindran, <ORG>598999939855b71f847a52ba</ORG>C> of Urban Affairs director <PER>5982d0b09855b7221e186ba1</PER>, <ORG>5982d0ef9855b7221e18a1e1</ORG> of Public Finance and Policy director <PER>5982d2569855b7221e19c87b</PER> and <ORG>598999939855b71f847a52b8</ORG> (<LOC>598994619855b71f8475cf27</LOC> ) director <PER>598999939855b71f847a52bc</PER>.The terms of reference for the committee, which has to submit its recommendation by August 31, include evaluation of various alternatives for the setting up of the Capital of the new State through field visits, consultations with all the stakeholders, including the Centre and the <ORG>5982d0909855b7221e185130</ORG>.The committee will conduct a feasibility study, taking into account judicious sharing of resources between the two States and basic infrastructural availability, including road, rail and air connectivity.While making the recommendation, the committee will consider other essential aspects such as ensuring minimum possible population displacement, their habitation and sources of income.Hyderabad will remain the joint Capital of both the States for ten years, during which the new Capital will be developed.
In a landmark transaction for the Indian pharmaceutical industry, <ORG>5982d1209855b7221e18c705</ORG> on Monday announced that it would acquire 100 per cent of <ORG>5982d1b39855b7221e193e86</ORG> in a $4 billion all-share transaction.The transaction has a total equity value of $3.2 billion and a net debt of $800 million on Ranbaxys books will also be part of the transaction.The combined entity will create the fifth-largest specialty generics company in the world and the largest pharmaceutical company in India with leadership in 13 specialty segments.The combine will have operations in 65 countries, 47 manufacturing facilities across five continents and a swathe of specialty and generics products, including 629 ANDAs (Abbreviated new drug applications). It will also become the largest Indian pharma company in the U.S. with over $2 billion sales and a pipeline of 184 ANDAs.Both companies said that they had entered into definitive agreements under which Ranbaxy shareholders will receive 0.8 shares of <ORG>5982d1209855b7221e18c705</ORG> for every share of Ranbaxy. The exchange ratio represents a value of Rs.457 per share of Ranbaxy which is at an 18 per cent premium to the 30-day volume-weighted average share price and a premium of 24.3 per cent to Ranbaxys 60-day volume-weighted average share price as on April 4, 2014. The transaction is expected to close by December 2014 and will be EPS-accretive a year after.It is a very synergistic transaction, <PER>598997849855b71f8478634d</PER>, Managing Director of Sun Pharma said in a conference call. It strengthens our presence in chronic therapy, acute care and OTC (over-the-counter) segment, all important segments going forward. The U.S. has been the largest market for Sun and this deal will further strengthen our presence there.The transaction has been approved by the boards of directors of both companies and <ORG>5989951a9855b71f84765d83</ORG> which holds 63.4 per cent in Ranbaxy.<PER>5989965c9855b71f84774e29</PER>, Managing Director & CEO, Ranbaxy, said, both companies share similar ambitions to grow globally with complementary strengths. It is a landmark transaction not only for Sun but on the Indian pharma map. I foresee huge opportunities opening for all stakeholders with the coming together of the companies.On a pro forma basis, the combined entitys revenues are estimated at $4.2 billion with operating profit of $1.2 billion for calendar 2013. According to Mr. Shanghvi, although Ranbaxy has been facing regulatory compliance issues with the U.S. <ORG>5982d0949855b7221e185445</ORG>, its India and emerging markets business is robust with a pipeline for growth and profitability. We believe the valuation is justified and are confident of creating future value for the shareholders.He said both companies would use their current infrastructure to sell each others products. The synergy benefits from the transaction will be around $250 million three years after its completion. A large part of this will be derived from growth, procurement and supply chain efficiencies, Mr. Shanghvi said. Daiichi will then become the second largest shareholder in Sun and will have an independent director on <ORG>598999c19855b71f847a7bf0</ORG>.The markets to immediately leverage are India, the U.S. and then the emerging markets. Sun has sales of more than $100 million in South Africa, Russia and Romania and is looking to further strengthen our position in Brazil and Malaysia, Mr. Shanghvi said.After opening the day at Rs.505, in afternoon trade, Ranbaxy shares slid 4.84 per cent to Rs.437.3 while Sun Pharma shares rose 1.21 per cent at Rs.578.8 on the BSE on Monday.
HONG KONG: Asian insurer <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184316</ORG> , the world's second largest by m-cap, will scale up its business in India undeterred by either the boardroom battle at its joint venture partner <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184314</ORG>>5982d07f9855b7221e184315</PER> or the heat and dust of demonetisation.AIA, which was spun off from the <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e18431b</ORG> through a nearly $18-billion IPO in 2010, has emerged as the largest panAsian insurer.In an interview to TOI, <PER>5982d07f9855b7221e184311</PER>, regional chief executive, AIA, said that the Indian joint venture Tata AIA Life Insurance has moved up ten positions in rankings to become the sixth largest life insurance company . "Looking at the Tata brand, we should be among the top three players. In the life business, we had some stop-starts. A key part of that was not having a bancassurance partner.But we turned that cor ner by partnering <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184319</ORG> and <ORG>5982d0699855b7221e18307c</ORG>. We are still a bit away from the top three or four, but we are building the right foundations," said Lisle.On the ongoing boardroom tussle in <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184317</ORG>, Lisle said, "We do not have any concerns. We are in partnership with the Tatas and we trust them to take the right decisions."Lisle sits on the Tata AIA board along with <PER>5982d07f9855b7221e184312</PER>, finance director, <ORG>5982d07b9855b7221e183f82</ORG>. "We have been around for 100 years and Tatas have been around for more than a 100 years. From our perspective, this is very much business as usual," said Lisle.On demonetisation, Lisle said that it was a bold move."Although growth slowed slightly this year, 7.3% is a rate that the West would die for.There is huge opportunity akin to China, GST is expected to come in and that is expected to improve longer term public finances. I think demonetisation will have a short-term impact potentially on growth, but longer term it is the right thing for economy ," he said.
HONG KONG: Asian insurer <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184316</ORG> , the world's second largest by m-cap, will scale up its business in India undeterred by either the boardroom battle at its joint venture partner <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184314</ORG>>5982d07f9855b7221e184315</PER> or the heat and dust of demonetisation.AIA, which was spun off from the <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e18431b</ORG> through a nearly $18-billion IPO in 2010, has emerged as the largest panAsian insurer.In an interview to TOI, <PER>5982d07f9855b7221e184311</PER>, regional chief executive, AIA, said that the Indian joint venture Tata AIA Life Insurance has moved up ten positions in rankings to become the sixth largest life insurance company . "Looking at the Tata brand, we should be among the top three players. In the life business, we had some stop-starts. A key part of that was not having a bancassurance partner.But we turned that cor ner by partnering <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184319</ORG> and <ORG>5982d0699855b7221e18307c</ORG>. We are still a bit away from the top three or four, but we are building the right foundations," said Lisle.On the ongoing boardroom tussle in <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184317</ORG>, Lisle said, "We do not have any concerns. We are in partnership with the Tatas and we trust them to take the right decisions."Lisle sits on the Tata AIA board along with <PER>5982d07f9855b7221e184312</PER>, finance director, <ORG>5982d07b9855b7221e183f82</ORG>. "We have been around for 100 years and Tatas have been around for more than a 100 years. From our perspective, this is very much business as usual," said Lisle.On demonetisation, Lisle said that it was a bold move."Although growth slowed slightly this year, 7.3% is a rate that the West would die for.There is huge opportunity akin to China, GST is expected to come in and that is expected to improve longer term public finances. I think demonetisation will have a short-term impact potentially on growth, but longer term it is the right thing for economy ," he said.
<LOC>5982d0659855b7221e182d49</LOC>: A unit of India's Oil and <ORG>5982d0aa9855b7221e186577</ORG> is in early talks with <ORG>598998739855b71f84794553</ORG> for supply of natural gas through a complex swap involving Russia , China and Myanmar , the head of the unit said on Wednesday.The unit, <ORG>598995029855b71f84764b2c</ORG>, and two other Indian state companies, <ORG>5982d0779855b7221e183c5a</ORG> and <ORG>5989945e9855b71f8475ccb4</ORG> , first discussed the idea with Gazprom a few months ago, said <PER>5982d17a9855b7221e190e46</PER>, ONGC Videsh's managing director."Myanmar is sending gas to China through an existing pipeline ... if Russia can provide equivalent gas to China, then we can reverse the flow of gas from Myanmar to China and bring that gas to India," Verma told reporters on the sidelines of India's Petrotech energy conference."For that we'll need a pipeline from Myanmar to India."He said this was the best way of getting Russia to help India with its gas needs, but would need the cooperation of China and Myanmar.
<LOC>5982d0659855b7221e182d49</LOC>: Don't worry about change, said a <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9e</ORG> employee in the Capital on Monday, when a customer flashed a brand new Rs 2,000 note. The smile on his face along with the long queue at the cash register suggested, it was business as usual for the US burger chain. After taking a severe hit from demonetization, India's Rs 8,000-crore fast-food industry seems to be back on track, thanks to an unbelievable surge in cashless transactions in the sector."Around two years ago, we worked very hard on digitising everything at McDonald's and we were ready with the platform of digital payments, including having e-wallets," said <PER>5982d09f9855b7221e185da4</PER>, vice-chairman, <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9a</ORG>, which operates <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185da0</ORG> in west and south India. "With the recent demonetisation rule, our cashless transactions have gone up to 75% from 25%."It's a similar scenario at other quick service restaurant (QSR) chains across the country. "In the first week after demonetisation, business took a big hit," said <PER>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9d</PER>, senior VP (marketing) at <ORG>5982d0749855b7221e183a23</ORG>, which runs around 1,100 restaurants across 251 cities. "Sales were down by 10-12%. But now, things are turning around and sales are just slightly below normal."Industry experts said the impact of demonetisation on the Indian fast-food market is a temporary phenomenon that will diminish as consumers overcome their initial jitters. "Fine dining restaurants, where the average cost per person is Rs 3,000-5,000 will be hurt more," said <PER>5982d09f9855b7221e185da8</PER>, founder and chairman at retail consultancy Technopak. "For fast food chains, it's just a matter of time before things bounce back."At Indian QSR chain <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185da3</ORG>, which serves South Indian fare, cash transactions have gone down to 10% from around 75% after PM Narendra Modi's demonetisation announcement. "During the first week, we saw a 15-20% decrease in business but this weekend, sales were marginal 2-3% below normal," said <PER>5982d09f9855b7221e185da6</PER>, CEO at Sagar Ratna Restaurants. "For many of us, it's a blessing in disguise operationally because we have to handle less cash."To help consumers make a smooth cash-to-cashless transition, nearly all fast-food brands have doubled their efforts. <PER>5982d09f9855b7221e185da7</PER> of <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9f</ORG>G>5982d09f9855b7221e185d98</ORG>, said the company's delivery boys carry card <ORG>5982d0659855b7221e182d45</ORG> machines. "We as a brand are encouraging consumers to use e-payments and mobile wallets  there is a 15% cashback on <ORG>5982d0669855b7221e182e88</ORG> transactions at all our restaurants," he said.
<LOC>5982d0659855b7221e182d49</LOC>: Don't worry about change, said a <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9e</ORG> employee in the Capital on Monday, when a customer flashed a brand new Rs 2,000 note. The smile on his face along with the long queue at the cash register suggested, it was business as usual for the US burger chain. After taking a severe hit from demonetization, India's Rs 8,000-crore fast-food industry seems to be back on track, thanks to an unbelievable surge in cashless transactions in the sector."Around two years ago, we worked very hard on digitising everything at McDonald's and we were ready with the platform of digital payments, including having e-wallets," said <PER>5982d09f9855b7221e185da4</PER>, vice-chairman, <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9a</ORG>, which operates <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185da0</ORG> in west and south India. "With the recent demonetisation rule, our cashless transactions have gone up to 75% from 25%."It's a similar scenario at other quick service restaurant (QSR) chains across the country. "In the first week after demonetisation, business took a big hit," said <PER>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9d</PER>, senior VP (marketing) at <ORG>5982d0749855b7221e183a23</ORG>, which runs around 1,100 restaurants across 251 cities. "Sales were down by 10-12%. But now, things are turning around and sales are just slightly below normal."Industry experts said the impact of demonetisation on the Indian fast-food market is a temporary phenomenon that will diminish as consumers overcome their initial jitters. "Fine dining restaurants, where the average cost per person is Rs 3,000-5,000 will be hurt more," said <PER>5982d09f9855b7221e185da8</PER>, founder and chairman at retail consultancy Technopak. "For fast food chains, it's just a matter of time before things bounce back."At Indian QSR chain <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185da3</ORG>, which serves South Indian fare, cash transactions have gone down to 10% from around 75% after PM Narendra Modi's demonetisation announcement. "During the first week, we saw a 15-20% decrease in business but this weekend, sales were marginal 2-3% below normal," said <PER>5982d09f9855b7221e185da6</PER>, CEO at Sagar Ratna Restaurants. "For many of us, it's a blessing in disguise operationally because we have to handle less cash."To help consumers make a smooth cash-to-cashless transition, nearly all fast-food brands have doubled their efforts. <PER>5982d09f9855b7221e185da7</PER> of <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9f</ORG>G>5982d09f9855b7221e185d98</ORG>, said the company's delivery boys carry card <ORG>5982d0659855b7221e182d45</ORG> machines. "We as a brand are encouraging consumers to use e-payments and mobile wallets  there is a 15% cashback on <ORG>5982d0669855b7221e182e88</ORG> transactions at all our restaurants," he said.
Hong Kong: Asian insurer <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184316</ORG> , the world's second largest by m-cap, will scale up its business in India undeterred by either the boardroom battle at its joint venture partner <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184314</ORG>>5982d07f9855b7221e184315</PER> or the heat and dust of demonetisation . AIA, which was spun off from the <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e18431b</ORG> through a nearly $18-billion IPO in 2010, has emerged as the largest pan-Asian insurer.In an interview to TOI, <PER>5982d07f9855b7221e184311</PER> , regional chief executive, AIA, said that the Indian joint venture Tata AIA Life Insurance has moved up ten positions in rankings to become the sixth largest life insurance company. "Looking at the Tata brand, we should be among the top three players. In the life business, we had some stop-starts. A key part of that was not having a bancassurance partner. But we turned that corner by partnering <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184319</ORG> and <ORG>5982d0959855b7221e185544</ORG>. We are still a bit away from the top three or four, but we are building the right foundations," said Lisle.On the ongoing boardroom tussle in <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184317</ORG>, Lisle said, "We do not have any concerns. We are in partnership with the Tatas and we trust them to take the right decisions."Lisle sits on the Tata AIA board along with <PER>5982d07f9855b7221e184312</PER>, finance director, <ORG>5982d07b9855b7221e183f82</ORG>. "We have been around for 100 years and Tatas have been around for more than a 100 years. From our perspective, this is very much business as usual," said Lisle.On demonetisation, Lisle said that it was a bold move. "Prime Minister <PER>5982d0679855b7221e182f25</PER> is still popular. Although growth slowed slightly this year, 7.3% is a rate that the West would die for. Despite challenges, we see the growth drivers for the Indian economy continuing. There is huge opportunity akin to China, GST is expected to come in and that is expected to improve longer term public finances. I think demonetisation will have a short-term impact potentially on growth, but longer term it is the right thing for the economy," he said.Speaking on plans for India, Lisle said that AIA plans to bring its new product AIA Vitality into the Indian markets. <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184316</ORG> Vitality brings the concept of shared values by rewarding policyholders for staying healthy. There are three aspects to insurance plans under the Vitality programme. The first part involves getting the insured to undergo regular tests and diagnostics.In the second part, the company tells the insured what they need to do to get health and measure their adherence to an exercise regime through connected devices. If the insured achieves the goals, he is rewarded with discounts and deals. "The healthier our clients are, the lesser they claim. We pass our savings to them in the form of discounts," said Lisle. The company is also bringing its group protection solutions and has started working with TCS.(The writer was in Hong Kong at the invitation of AIA)
Hong Kong: Asian insurer <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184316</ORG> , the world's second largest by m-cap, will scale up its business in India undeterred by either the boardroom battle at its joint venture partner <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184314</ORG>>5982d07f9855b7221e184315</PER> or the heat and dust of demonetisation . AIA, which was spun off from the <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e18431b</ORG> through a nearly $18-billion IPO in 2010, has emerged as the largest pan-Asian insurer.In an interview to TOI, <PER>5982d07f9855b7221e184311</PER> , regional chief executive, AIA, said that the Indian joint venture Tata AIA Life Insurance has moved up ten positions in rankings to become the sixth largest life insurance company. "Looking at the Tata brand, we should be among the top three players. In the life business, we had some stop-starts. A key part of that was not having a bancassurance partner. But we turned that corner by partnering <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184319</ORG> and <ORG>5982d0959855b7221e185544</ORG>. We are still a bit away from the top three or four, but we are building the right foundations," said Lisle.On the ongoing boardroom tussle in <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184317</ORG>, Lisle said, "We do not have any concerns. We are in partnership with the Tatas and we trust them to take the right decisions."Lisle sits on the Tata AIA board along with <PER>5982d07f9855b7221e184312</PER>, finance director, <ORG>5982d07b9855b7221e183f82</ORG>. "We have been around for 100 years and Tatas have been around for more than a 100 years. From our perspective, this is very much business as usual," said Lisle.On demonetisation, Lisle said that it was a bold move. "Prime Minister <PER>5982d0679855b7221e182f25</PER> is still popular. Although growth slowed slightly this year, 7.3% is a rate that the West would die for. Despite challenges, we see the growth drivers for the Indian economy continuing. There is huge opportunity akin to China, GST is expected to come in and that is expected to improve longer term public finances. I think demonetisation will have a short-term impact potentially on growth, but longer term it is the right thing for the economy," he said.Speaking on plans for India, Lisle said that AIA plans to bring its new product AIA Vitality into the Indian markets. <ORG>5982d07f9855b7221e184316</ORG> Vitality brings the concept of shared values by rewarding policyholders for staying healthy. There are three aspects to insurance plans under the Vitality programme. The first part involves getting the insured to undergo regular tests and diagnostics.In the second part, the company tells the insured what they need to do to get health and measure their adherence to an exercise regime through connected devices. If the insured achieves the goals, he is rewarded with discounts and deals. "The healthier our clients are, the lesser they claim. We pass our savings to them in the form of discounts," said Lisle. The company is also bringing its group protection solutions and has started working with TCS.(The writer was in Hong Kong at the invitation of AIA)
In 12 hours, there couldn't have been a starker difference to jeweller <PER>5982d1019855b7221e18b027</PER> 's fortunes. At 9 pm on November 8, just hours after Prime Minister <PER>5982d0649855b7221e182d18</PER> announced the demonetisation of Rs 500 and Rs 1,000 notes, his store in north <LOC>5982d0659855b7221e182d40</LOC> was besieged by customers buying all that was available, paying with wads of currency, seeking to convert cash into more agreeable holdings in gems and jewellery.The next morning was just the opposite  an almost empty store, with barely a dozen walk-ins and just a couple of low-value purchases. "There's lots of cash floating around and people are now scared they will lose their money in this fight against black money," says Mehta. "We expect to be back in business next week."For the next couple of days, the bustling market where this store is located  and thousands across the country  where cash is the primary source of income, will see business dealings plummet. From Zaveri Bazaar in Mumbai to <LOC>5982d0a79855b7221e186364</LOC> Bazaar in <PER>5982d1019855b7221e18b01d</PER> and <PER>5982d1019855b7221e18b01f</PER> Market in Bengaluru, businessmen sweated on the fate of their enterprises.A dealer of PVC pipes in the Bengaluru market, who bills Rs 1.5 crore a month and is dependent on cash for 80% of his payments, spent most of the week waiting for customers. "In three days, I had barely 10 customers walk in and of those just five made small orders," he grumbles.Across the country, businessmen saw the rise and fall of their enterprises. Nikhilesh Dhawan's business too took a pounding. A <ORG>5982d0749855b7221e1839d6</ORG> dealer in Jagatpuri in Delhi saw just three or four customers making purchases a day after the big announcement, paying by cheque; in happier times, 80% of his purchases were in cash. About 10 km away, in upscale Khanna Market, <PER>5982d1019855b7221e18b01b</PER>, promoter of RK Vision, a consumer electronics store, sold goods worth Rs 31 lakh until midnight, doubling his daily sales.Otherwise fussy customers bought air purifiers, refrigerators and LED televisions in a tearing hurry to dispose of their cash. After that storm, a lull quickly descended on Wednesday, with barely 15 bills raised, compared with over 100 on a normal business day.As businessmen, heavily reliant on cash, fretted about their wildly swinging fortunes, most people on the street spent much of Thursday and Friday standing in queues trying to get their hands on these new notes or figuring out how to manage with the limited, legal currency at their disposal. <PER>5982d0e89855b7221e189c33</PER>, a painter in suburban Mumbai, spent three hours on Thursday evening and a couple more on Friday before being able to finally withdraw money to pay his dues.For all of Wednesday, Kumar managed with Rs 60, before empty pockets compelled him to queue up. "This is a disservice to the poor who have to waste hours during a work day hunting for money," Kumar says.This pain is amplified away from big cities. In the small town called Ezhukone in Kerala, about 20 km from Kollam, <PER>5982d0de9855b7221e18944d</PER>, a 59-year old retired employee, uses cash to pay for her daily milk, vegetables and fish. Following the sudden demonetisation, she was left with Rs 259, with which she had to manage all her immediate purchases, with neither her neighbourhood grocer nor the pharmacist wired to accept cards or digital payments. To make ends meet, she pleaded with an auto driver to ferry her to and from the chemist to buy medicines she and her husband urgently required.She held on to her last few tenners and a desperate hope that the ATM-less Wednesday would pass without incident or emergency.If Radhakrishnan spent her time wondering how to manage with little cash, <PER>5982d0939855b7221e185397</PER> (name changed), in his cramped office in the Mumbai suburb of Andheri, is wondering how to dispose of the cash he has hoarded. An agent for the local road transport office, he keeps up to Rs 5 lakh in a locked cupboard in office and more at home. He has managed to buy some jewellery and electronics goods, but faces tough choices ahead. With fixed deposits over Rs 2.5 lakh facing tough scrutiny, that's another avenue shut, for now.Away from the chaos of managing too much or too little cash, experts divided on the efficacy of the long-term game out black money and counterfeiting of high-value notes. "It will tackle black money, corruption, terror money and counterfeiting  multiple with one stone," <PER>5982d0e09855b7221e1895d5</PER>, chairman of financial services company. "I call it gutsy because it's a move that any political party will know will be difficult and there will be plenty of reasons not to implement."<PER>5982d1019855b7221e18b016</PER> with <ORG>5982d1019855b7221e18b01c</ORG>, a management consultancy, calls this a great one time action to cleanse the system. While this is a great first move, the <ORG>5982d0659855b7221e182d78</ORG> needs to do much more to back this up. "Thus requires several follow-ups, especially tightening and better enforcement of PMLA (Prevention of Money Laundering Act) and deterrence in the form of far stricter punishment to be effective."A clampdown on black money may be meaningless with this one-off move. While this may serve as a strong notice of intent, the government faces a series of difficult choices ahead, targeting large sectors such as real estate, which are flush with these funds. "It is important to ensure the chain of black money doesn't return," says <PER>5982d1019855b7221e18b024</PER>, partner, <ORG>5982d06b9855b7221e1832b0</ORG>, a management consultancy. In the longer term, to achieve this, the government needs to build on a range of initiatives, including GST, access to bank accounts with initiatives such as <PER>5982d0659855b7221e182d95</PER> and technology enablers such as Aadhaar , to make a fist of its fight against black money.If the demonetisation has been a bigbang announcement with some immediate repercussions, it may take more gumption in the long term to strike a body blow in the fight against black money and indeed counterfeit currency. This is because a large chunk of this illicit money is squirrelled away in the form of real estate and jewellery or even overseas, away from the prying eyes of regulators. "People with malicious intent usually catch up with these changes and are quickly go one step ahead," says <PER>5982d1019855b7221e18b026</PER>, managing director, <ORG>5982d1019855b7221e18b021</ORG> , a forensics specialist."As India moves more towards a 'white' economy,' liquidating holdings overseas and stamping out counterfeiting, which thrived on operating in a cash-rich economy, must be key long-term goals."(Additional reporting by Malini Goyal)
INDORE : Cancellation of legal tender status of Rs 500 and Rs 1,000 has adversely hit the textile and garment industry.Unable to procure raw materials and pay contract workers , several textile units have slashed production by 20 - 30 per cent. Hit hard by the cash crunch, many units in the region have laid off contract workers.According to experts of the total working staff, about 20-30 per cent of the workers involved in non-perennial jobs are on contract.In the series of demonetisation , unorganized or daily wage workers are the most hit as majority of them are migrant workers and do not have bank accounts to receive direct payment through banking channel.<ORG>5982d11f9855b7221e18c652</ORG>'s managing director and chairman Madhya Pradesh Textile Mills Association Piyush Mutha said, "Demonetisation has led to severe shortage of funds for regular operations in the textile industry hitting day to day business operations."Industrialists said that scrapping of large currency notes has hit the purchase of raw material, sale of finished goods and other routine factory expenses and small machinery items.Industry participants said that the availability of raw material for textile mills - cotton has reduced as farmers are brining less produce in the market due to cash crunch. They said merchants do not have cash to give to farmers who do not accept cheques.The association secretary M C Rawat said, "The main worry is how to dispense payment to workers next month. Most of them do not have bank accounts. <ORG>5982d11f9855b7221e18c656</ORG> is a cash intensive industry where cash is required for running daily activities."Market experts said that sales of garments have also reduced sharply due to cash crunch as customers are avoiding purchase.Maharaja <ORG>5982d11f9855b7221e18c653</ORG> president <PER>5982d11f9855b7221e18c655</PER> said, "Sales have gone down drastically as purchasing power of consumers have declined. Rotation of money has stopped and businessmen are not in a position to accept new orders."Jain said workers payment is major issues as the withdrawal limit from banks for current accounts are very less.
<LOC>5982d0659855b7221e182d40</LOC>: <PER>5982d0bf9855b7221e187974</PER>, a resident of Bettiah in Bihar, is a movie buff who never used to miss any movie released in his nearest film theatre.However, he has not seen a single film since November 8, because he doesn't have cash to buy the Rs 50 ticket, thanks to the sudden demonetisation of Rs 500 and Rs 1,000 currency notes.The jury is still out on whether the government's demonetisation drive to combat black money will succeed, but the initiative seems to have created a digital divide in the cinema exhibition industry. Single screen theatres in smaller towns where there is no facility for card payment have suffered a direct blow from the note ban while multiplexes claim that their business is not hit much and is bouncing back.Most single screen owners in the country are staring at major losses with show cancellations and abysmal ticket sales. <PER>5982d1299855b7221e18ced3</PER>, who controls 35 theatres in Bihar and Jharkhand, told ET that collections are down to 15-20 per cent in his properties."At many places we have revised ticket prices  balcony from Rs 70 to Rs 40, and second class from Rs 50 to Rs 30, just to get people come to watch films. But they don't have cash, so how will they come," he said. "In big cities, you talk about credit cards and online payment; here we don't even have computerised ticketing in almost 95 per cent screens," Bairolia said.<PER>5982d1299855b7221e18cee2</PER>, who owns a small multiplex and a single screen property in Gujarat, said, "We have seen over 60 per cent drop in business. Cinema is luxury spend in areas where we operate. We will have to live with the situation till things normalise," he said.Incidentally, it's a double whammy for the single screen owners as producers are recalibrating film releases with limited prints considering the hard cash crunch across the country. <PER>5982d0c89855b7221e188086</PER>-starrer 'Dear Zindagi', for example, was released in just 1,200 screens this Friday.<ORG>5982d1299855b7221e18cee3</ORG> 2 and Befikre are working on their distribution strategy to release films in less number of screens. <PER>5982d1299855b7221e18cee0</PER>, joint managing director of digital cinema services company <ORG>5982d1299855b7221e18cedb</ORG>-Works that offers digital delivery of cinema to 330 screens in India, said for one week post the demonetisation announcement, the occupancy of single screen theatres in smaller centres had gone down to 5-7 per cent."Now it is slightly better but so far, from the logs that we have got, I can tell that more than 50 per cent shows have got cancelled because of no public," he said.<PER>5982d1299855b7221e18ced7</PER>, COO at <ORG>5982d1299855b7221e18cedc</ORG>, which operates 17 screens in smaller cities of <STA>5982d0659855b7221e182d26</STA>, Uttarakhand, Gujarat and Maharashtra, said, "Our business model revolves around screens in smaller towns at affordable prices, where most of the transactions happen in cash. My occupancy has come down to 5 per cent, while operational cost remains the same. My cost of running one show is Rs 4,000 and tickets we are generating worth Rs 500-700 only."In fact, demonetisation has impacted the industry at a time when it releawas just coming out of an extremely poor second quarter, which saw a lot of films tanking at the box office."Things had just started to look better with Shivaay and Ae Dil <PER>5982d0729855b7221e183874</PER>, and this order (demonetisation) came," said <PER>5982d1299855b7221e18ced0</PER> at <ORG>5982d1299855b7221e18cedd</ORG>, which runs Mukta A2 Cinemas in 13 cities."We have seen 30-40 per cent impact on business in the last two weeks, but I hope it will be less, going forward. Our cashless transactions have improved from 8-9 per cent earlier to 14 per cent now," he said.Puri said box office collection of 'Rock On 2' has been affected at least by 50 per cent. "Same with Force 2, which would have done better in single screens, but people had no cash," he said.Interestingly, multiplex operators are not perturbed with demonetisation. <PER>5982d11e9855b7221e18c5cb</PER>, director of <ORG>5982d11e9855b7221e18c5bc</ORG>, which has partnered with <ORG>5982d0659855b7221e182dd9</ORG> to allow cash withdrawals at its 106 properties across India, said his company is completely supporting the demonetisation drive."Initially there was a slight dip in the footfalls, but that was more because people were busy in sorting out their finances," he said. But since then its cashless transactions have doubled to 70 per cent."Cash transactions have gone down but cashless have doubled. We are seeing that Indians love films and with Dear Zindagi, and things are coming back to normal," Jain said. <PER>5982d0a59855b7221e18624f</PER>, CEO at <ORG>5982d0a69855b7221e186252</ORG>, said that while first week was a bit drastic, situation is much better now."Business is bouncing back, on Saturday we registered 74 per cent occupancy. When content is good, people do spend. Plus we have also doled out a lot of incentives, including up to 35 per cent discounts and complete waiver of the convenience fee, which is helping," he said."Now 82 per cent of our transactions are cashless," Dutta added.
<LOC>5982d0659855b7221e182d49</LOC>: <PER>59899c7a9855b71f847ce553</PER>, the estranged partner of <ORG>59899c7a9855b71f847ce559</ORG>, will soon move the <ORG>5982d0a19855b7221e185ef6</ORG> seeking his reinstatement as the managing director of their equal joint venture, two persons aware of the development said.He is also likely to ask the Company Law Board (CLB) to stop the US company from hampering the operations of the <ORG>5989983f9855b71f84791590</ORG>, <ORG>59899c7a9855b71f847ce558</ORG>, which runs 154 McDonald's outlets in the northern and eastern parts of India. Bakshi is expected to allege that McDonald's has treated him in an unfair and discriminatory way as compared with <ORG>59899c7a9855b71f847ce555</ORG>, its other partner in India, that operates the burger and fries chain's outlets in the western and southern parts of the country.Bakshi, who was the managing director of the JV for 17 years, declined comment on his future strategy. "The matter is now being addressed by my lawyers. It would be inappropriate for me to comment on any issue that is confidential and between my partner and myself at this stage," he said.Bakshi's term as managing director expired on July 17. At the company's board meeting on August 6, the two McDonald's nominees on the four-member board rejected the proposal to re-nominate him as MD. On August 30, McDonald's India issued a public notice saying Bakshi had ceased to be the managing director of the joint venture.A person familiar with the situation said Bakshi will challenge the striking down of his reappointment on the basis of 'certain provisions of the shareholder agreement', but refused to elaborate on what these provisions were.Bakshi is expected to appeal to CLB to resolve the deadlock over the appointment of the company's MD, this person said. At present, there are two nominees of Bakshi and McDonald's on the board, and his renomination has to be ratified by the majority of the board.This person added that at the August 6 board meeting, the McDonald's nominees had ratified all the decisions taken by their Indian partner as managing director. "If he had done something wrong or had misused his position, why would they ratify his decisions?" he said.In his petition to CLB, Bakshi is also likely to say he has been unfairly treated compared with McDonald's other partner Hardcastle Restaurants Pvt Ltd.Both Connaught Plaza Restaurants and Hardcastle Restaurants had started off as equal joint ventures between McDonald's and their Indian partners when the fast-food chain entered India in 1995-96. But in 2011, the US company allowed <PER>5982d09f9855b7221e185da4</PER>, the Indian partner in Hardcastle, to buy its 50% stake at an attractive price and convert the company into a franchisee operation in the south and west. It is also understood that McDonald's agreed to reduce Hardcastle's royalty payment.Bakshi, too, wanted to convert his joint venture into a similar franchise arrangement, but McDonald's did not agree, said people familiar with the situation. He wanted a free hand, expand the business and take the company public, the way <ORG>5982d0749855b7221e183a23</ORG> did, which has now become a benchmark for all restaurant companies in India. Relations between the two partners soured when McDonald's did not accede to his request, said these people.In addition, between 2008 and 2012, Connaught Plaza Restaurants' debt was frozen at the insistence of McDonald's, which reduced the JV's ability to invest and grow. "The joint venture company had to keep its debt at less than Rs 134 crore until 2012. After much discussion on growth, the debt level was raised to Rs 161 crore," said the person quoted earlier.Now, McDonald's is asking Bakshi to exit, and the deadlock is over valuation. "The American company is unwilling to pay the price Bakshi wants," he said.Meanwhile, Hardcastle was allowed to increase its debt, and later freed from McDonald's control, enabling it to grow at a faster rate. The company now operates 166 outlets compared with Connaught Plaza Restaurants' 154. Hardcastle has also concluded a reverse merger with a promoter-owned company  <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9a</ORG>, whose shares have risen four-fold from Rs 86.20 on December 7, when the announcement was made, to Rs 344.95 last Friday.An email to McDonald's spokesman in Hong Kong met with the following auto reply: "I am currently on holiday with limited access to emails or phone calls."
<LOC>5982d0659855b7221e182d49</LOC>: <PER>59899c7a9855b71f847ce553</PER>, the estranged partner of <ORG>59899c7a9855b71f847ce559</ORG>, will soon move the <ORG>5982d0a19855b7221e185ef6</ORG> seeking his reinstatement as the managing director of their equal joint venture, two persons aware of the development said.He is also likely to ask the Company Law Board (CLB) to stop the US company from hampering the operations of the <ORG>5989983f9855b71f84791590</ORG>, <ORG>59899c7a9855b71f847ce558</ORG>, which runs 154 McDonald's outlets in the northern and eastern parts of India. Bakshi is expected to allege that McDonald's has treated him in an unfair and discriminatory way as compared with <ORG>59899c7a9855b71f847ce555</ORG>, its other partner in India, that operates the burger and fries chain's outlets in the western and southern parts of the country.Bakshi, who was the managing director of the JV for 17 years, declined comment on his future strategy. "The matter is now being addressed by my lawyers. It would be inappropriate for me to comment on any issue that is confidential and between my partner and myself at this stage," he said.Bakshi's term as managing director expired on July 17. At the company's board meeting on August 6, the two McDonald's nominees on the four-member board rejected the proposal to re-nominate him as MD. On August 30, McDonald's India issued a public notice saying Bakshi had ceased to be the managing director of the joint venture.A person familiar with the situation said Bakshi will challenge the striking down of his reappointment on the basis of 'certain provisions of the shareholder agreement', but refused to elaborate on what these provisions were.Bakshi is expected to appeal to CLB to resolve the deadlock over the appointment of the company's MD, this person said. At present, there are two nominees of Bakshi and McDonald's on the board, and his renomination has to be ratified by the majority of the board.This person added that at the August 6 board meeting, the McDonald's nominees had ratified all the decisions taken by their Indian partner as managing director. "If he had done something wrong or had misused his position, why would they ratify his decisions?" he said.In his petition to CLB, Bakshi is also likely to say he has been unfairly treated compared with McDonald's other partner Hardcastle Restaurants Pvt Ltd.Both Connaught Plaza Restaurants and Hardcastle Restaurants had started off as equal joint ventures between McDonald's and their Indian partners when the fast-food chain entered India in 1995-96. But in 2011, the US company allowed <PER>5982d09f9855b7221e185da4</PER>, the Indian partner in Hardcastle, to buy its 50% stake at an attractive price and convert the company into a franchisee operation in the south and west. It is also understood that McDonald's agreed to reduce Hardcastle's royalty payment.Bakshi, too, wanted to convert his joint venture into a similar franchise arrangement, but McDonald's did not agree, said people familiar with the situation. He wanted a free hand, expand the business and take the company public, the way <ORG>5982d0749855b7221e183a23</ORG> did, which has now become a benchmark for all restaurant companies in India. Relations between the two partners soured when McDonald's did not accede to his request, said these people.In addition, between 2008 and 2012, Connaught Plaza Restaurants' debt was frozen at the insistence of McDonald's, which reduced the JV's ability to invest and grow. "The joint venture company had to keep its debt at less than Rs 134 crore until 2012. After much discussion on growth, the debt level was raised to Rs 161 crore," said the person quoted earlier.Now, McDonald's is asking Bakshi to exit, and the deadlock is over valuation. "The American company is unwilling to pay the price Bakshi wants," he said.Meanwhile, Hardcastle was allowed to increase its debt, and later freed from McDonald's control, enabling it to grow at a faster rate. The company now operates 166 outlets compared with Connaught Plaza Restaurants' 154. Hardcastle has also concluded a reverse merger with a promoter-owned company  <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9a</ORG>, whose shares have risen four-fold from Rs 86.20 on December 7, when the announcement was made, to Rs 344.95 last Friday.An email to McDonald's spokesman in Hong Kong met with the following auto reply: "I am currently on holiday with limited access to emails or phone calls."
The <ORG>5982d06a9855b7221e183139</ORG> will set up centres of excellence in various sectors such as construction, retail and tourism. The first of such centres, the <ORG>598995b89855b71f8476d4a1</ORG>, will be established shortly.Envisaged to have private participation, the institute will be of global standards, <ORG>5982d0799855b7221e183dc0</ORG> Minister <PER>5982d0d59855b7221e188ca6</PER> has said.Addressing a seminar on skill development, held here as part of the Pravasi Bharatiya Divas celebrations, he said the employment exchanges in the State would undergo major changes.The government is planning to convert them as employability centres.The candidates who register at the centres would be provided with opportunities for getting appropriate training to enhance skills.The industrial training institutes will be assigned a greater role in the skill development programme.Every district will have an ITI with specialisation in certain subjects.The government intends to provide information on skill development to prospective candidates through telephone. The minister urged the industry to coordinate with educational institutions to extend skill training.<PER>59899ce59855b71f847d476c</PER>, Secretary, <ORG>5982d06d9855b7221e1833fb</ORG>, said that under a skill development initiative of the union government, over 1000 modules have been identified. Flexible periods and timings would be allowed to pursue the courses.P.Mohamed Ali, NRI businessman, said skill improvisation was necessary to utilise the opportunities in foreign countries. It is time to create brand value and market the potential properly. Skill training facility was grossly inadequate in India.<PER>59899ce59855b71f847d476b</PER>, Managing Director of <ORG>5982d0779855b7221e183c9e</ORG>, and others spoke.
The <ORG>5982d06a9855b7221e183139</ORG> will set up centres of excellence in various sectors such as construction, retail and tourism. The first of such centres, the <ORG>598995b89855b71f8476d4a1</ORG>, will be established shortly.Envisaged to have private participation, the institute will be of global standards, <ORG>5982d0799855b7221e183dc0</ORG> Minister <PER>5982d0d59855b7221e188ca6</PER> has said.Addressing a seminar on skill development, held here as part of the Pravasi Bharatiya Divas celebrations, he said the employment exchanges in the State would undergo major changes.The government is planning to convert them as employability centres.The candidates who register at the centres would be provided with opportunities for getting appropriate training to enhance skills.The industrial training institutes will be assigned a greater role in the skill development programme.Every district will have an ITI with specialisation in certain subjects.The government intends to provide information on skill development to prospective candidates through telephone. The minister urged the industry to coordinate with educational institutions to extend skill training.<PER>59899ce59855b71f847d476c</PER>, Secretary, <ORG>5982d06d9855b7221e1833fb</ORG>, said that under a skill development initiative of the union government, over 1000 modules have been identified. Flexible periods and timings would be allowed to pursue the courses.P.Mohamed Ali, NRI businessman, said skill improvisation was necessary to utilise the opportunities in foreign countries. It is time to create brand value and market the potential properly. Skill training facility was grossly inadequate in India.<PER>59899ce59855b71f847d476b</PER>, Managing Director of <ORG>5982d0779855b7221e183c9e</ORG>, and others spoke.
<ORG>5982d2829855b7221e19ec2e</ORG>, a joint venture between <ORG>598996f39855b71f8477d461</ORG> and <ORG>5982d23d9855b7221e19b459</ORG> of South Africa, has inked a memorandum of understanding (MOU) with Tamil Nadu Co-operative State <ORG>59899d6b9855b71f847dc13b</ORG>The objective is to jointly promote, market and distribute life insurance products to all their customers. In addition to procuring business under traditional endowment plans and unit-linked insurance plans of the company, the cooperative bank will insure their borrowers and agricultural land owners under the Shriram Credit Guard Plan. This plan ensures repayment of loan amount to the bank in case of the untimely death of the land owner.SLIC, according to <PER>59899d6b9855b71f847dc139</PER>, Managing Director, is the only private company to report under-writing profits.Following its tie up with the Tamil Nadu agri bank, the joint venture, she said, would now be able to extend its footprint to the untapped rural market and provide life insurance cover to every household in Tamil Nadu.
BENGALURU : The $143-billion IT/IT-enabled services sector is going through a paradigm shift on the back of increased commoditisation of traditional services and adoption of digital technologies. And, the sector is looking up to the government for some direction to tide over the temporary turbulence.Section 35(2)(AB) should be amended to include information technology along with biotechnology so that there is a clarity that the weighted deduction would be available to an assessee engaged in production of computer software and business of information technology so that all R&D activities are enabled for weighted deduction, said P N Sudarshan, partner, <ORG>5982d0ee9855b7221e18a182</ORG>.K V <PER>5982d06a9855b7221e18312e</PER>, chief finance officer of <ORG>59899ded9855b71f847e30f2</ORG>, an IT product company, says with the <ORG>5982d0ad9855b7221e186893</ORG> getting more and more tough on visas and restrictions, things will change in the IT sector. We want a roadmap from the government on how it plans to bring down the corporate tax from 30 to 25 per cent.According to him, there should be specific guidelines for minimum alternate tax. This penal provision by the government where you need to pay taxes if you show profits in your account has gone up from 4 per cent to almost 20 per cent. So, the difference between a normal tax which is 30 per cent and a penal tax is only 10 per cent. Most IT companies in the SEZ are not taxed, but with the introduction of MAT the whole purpose of an SEZ was defeated.He believes the rules for place of effective management, which the government wanted to implement, should be looked at carefully as this will make most of the Indian IT companies having subsidiaries abroad liable to pay tax in India.<PER>598996ac9855b71f84778e2d</PER>, co-founder of <ORG>5982d1b39855b7221e193f31</ORG> and executive chairman of <ORG>59899ded9855b71f847e30ec</ORG>, pointed out that the only thing which is going to be a little difficult is GST and they need to make sure it doesnt create difficulties for the IT industry.There is also scope for double taxation, says <PER>5982d1139855b7221e18be3d</PER>. The impact of equalisation levy is on the recipient foreign company at six per cent of the consideration for services to be witheld by Indian payers. If the home country does not give credit for equalisation levy, this could lead to double taxation. The government may examine the possibility of entering into reciprocal agreements for credit with countries that impose a similar levy.
Strength and compassion should define the woman of today, said <PER>598996e39855b71f8477c3d5</PER>, former judge of the <ORG>5982d0ca9855b7221e1882c5</ORG>. Inaugurating new facilities at Lady Sivaswami Ayyar Girls' <ORG>5982d0f29855b7221e18a4ae</ORG> here on Monday, she spoke about the qualities of Sita of <ORG>5982d30b9855b7221e1a6fff</ORG> that every woman should personify. Sita was extremely independent, and faced all situations, yet she stood tall, Ms. Prabha Sridevan said .Talking about how education today is available mainly for the rich, Ms. Prabha Sridevan said more donors should come forward to make education accessible to all. Education should be inclusive and be available for all children. That is the dream of Mahatma <PER>5982d0699855b7221e183005</PER>, she added. The five new facilities of the school that were declared open on Monday are  TAG Auditorium, <ORG>59899edb9855b71f847f0be9</ORG>, <ORG>59899edb9855b71f847f0bed</ORG>, <ORG>59899edb9855b71f847f0bec</ORG> and <ORG>59899edb9855b71f847f0be8</ORG><PER>59899d6b9855b71f847dc139</PER>, Managing Director, <ORG>5982d2829855b7221e19ec2e</ORG>, said the school has been doing yeoman's service, and lauded the efforts of the donors. She also offered the support of the Give Life, an initiative to help under-privileged children of which she is a Trustee.<PER>5982d0eb9855b7221e189e5b</PER>, Managing Director, <ORG>5982d20a9855b7221e198a57</ORG> and <PER>5982d0a19855b7221e185f5c</PER>, Managing Director, <ORG>59899edb9855b71f847f0bee</ORG>, the two main donors, said the students will be benefited with the addition of the facilities. We have also planned different activities for different classes by adding amenities to the labs, said Mr. Chari.
Coimbatore chapters of <ORG>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b53</ORG> will organise a panel discussion here on January 10 on Enigma of Funding. According to <PER>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b4b</PER>, chair-learning vertical of Yi, Coimbatore, there are a large number of first and second generation entrepreneurs here. They get funds from family, banks or personal savings. The programme aims at creating awareness among them on the funding options  angel investments, venture capital, equity, etc. They will learn more about when entrepreneurs should go for such funding, case studies, and where to get the funds. Industries such as foundries or textile machinery need to focus on value addition to get such funding, he said. <PER>5982d2969855b7221e19fead</PER>, Managing Director and CEO of <ORG>5982d1989855b7221e192660</ORG>, will deliver the keynote address. The panel speakers will be <PER>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b4e</PER>, Director  Finance, <ORG>5982d09c9855b7221e185af9</ORG>, Vipul Rawal, Principal Investments, Elevar Equity, B.P. Singh, ED and Chief Investment Officer of <ORG>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b51</ORG>, <PER>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b50</PER>, former co-founder of <PER>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b4c</PER>982d2ff9855b7221e1a63ce</ORG> and <PER>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b4d</PER>, Director of <ORG>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b52</ORG>.The programme aims at creating awareness on the funding options - angel investments, venture capital, equity
Coimbatore chapters of <ORG>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b53</ORG> will organise a panel discussion here on January 10 on Enigma of Funding. According to <PER>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b4b</PER>, chair-learning vertical of Yi, Coimbatore, there are a large number of first and second generation entrepreneurs here. They get funds from family, banks or personal savings. The programme aims at creating awareness among them on the funding options  angel investments, venture capital, equity, etc. They will learn more about when entrepreneurs should go for such funding, case studies, and where to get the funds. Industries such as foundries or textile machinery need to focus on value addition to get such funding, he said. <PER>5982d2969855b7221e19fead</PER>, Managing Director and CEO of <ORG>5982d1989855b7221e192660</ORG>, will deliver the keynote address. The panel speakers will be <PER>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b4e</PER>, Director  Finance, <ORG>5982d09c9855b7221e185af9</ORG>, Vipul Rawal, Principal Investments, Elevar Equity, B.P. Singh, ED and Chief Investment Officer of <ORG>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b51</ORG>, <PER>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b50</PER>, former co-founder of <PER>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b4c</PER>982d2ff9855b7221e1a63ce</ORG> and <PER>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b4d</PER>, Director of <ORG>59899f3d9855b71f847f6b52</ORG>.The programme aims at creating awareness on the funding options - angel investments, venture capital, equity
<LOC>5982d0659855b7221e182d49</LOC>: <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9e</ORG> is ramping up its brand extension business in India. Although burgers continue to be the backbone of the US fast food chain, it now earns a fourth of its revenues from ice cream, smoothies and coffee.To speed up its brand extension business, the company has started a remodelling exercise to make its stores look fast-casual in South and West India. "We are trying to blur the line. This is what McDonald's will look like to millennials in the future," said <PER>5982d09f9855b7221e185da4</PER>, vice-chairman of <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9a</ORG> and McDonald's partner in West and South India.The burger chain has four brand extensions: Delivery, breakfast, dessert kiosks and McCafe. Jatia said sales value of these may touch Rs 850 crore in four years. Along with selling burgers, that's roughly the sum Jatia makes from 216 McDonald's stores in the country. "However, I want to be clear about the fact that our brand extension lines don't cover all our restaurants. We are working on it. For instance, we have opened 52 McCafes. In three years, we expect our coffee business to earn around Rs 250 crore," he said.McCafe is a coffee-house-style food and drink chain owned by the burger chain. Interestingly, it has yielded more revenues for McDonald's than its regular stores in some markets. McCafes are housed inside regular McDonald's in India.Jatia said he has earmarked an investment of Rs 750 crore to open around 200 new restaurants in five years. His company Westlife Development operates McDonald's stores through its subsidiary, <ORG>59899c7a9855b71f847ce555</ORG>. While Westlife reported a 21% increase in revenue for the September quarter led by its restaurant business, McDonald's has been juggling with the dual problem of a sluggish economy and a legal battle with its estranged partner in North India, <PER>59899c7a9855b71f847ce553</PER>, the owner of Connaught Plaza Restaurants.One of the <ORG>59899f999855b71f847fbd12</ORG> restaurants (QSR) to enter the domestic market, McDonald's was ousted from the position of the country's largest QSR player by US pizza maker <ORG>5982d0749855b7221e183a23</ORG> in 2013. Subsequently, it slipped behind its US rival <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9f</ORG> and now resides in the third position, according to a Euromonitor report from August. The organized QSR business in the country is poised to grow at a CAGR of 25% to reach around Rs 16,800 crore by 2018, Jatia said.
<LOC>5982d0659855b7221e182d49</LOC>: <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9e</ORG> is ramping up its brand extension business in India. Although burgers continue to be the backbone of the US fast food chain, it now earns a fourth of its revenues from ice cream, smoothies and coffee.To speed up its brand extension business, the company has started a remodelling exercise to make its stores look fast-casual in South and West India. "We are trying to blur the line. This is what McDonald's will look like to millennials in the future," said <PER>5982d09f9855b7221e185da4</PER>, vice-chairman of <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9a</ORG> and McDonald's partner in West and South India.The burger chain has four brand extensions: Delivery, breakfast, dessert kiosks and McCafe. Jatia said sales value of these may touch Rs 850 crore in four years. Along with selling burgers, that's roughly the sum Jatia makes from 216 McDonald's stores in the country. "However, I want to be clear about the fact that our brand extension lines don't cover all our restaurants. We are working on it. For instance, we have opened 52 McCafes. In three years, we expect our coffee business to earn around Rs 250 crore," he said.McCafe is a coffee-house-style food and drink chain owned by the burger chain. Interestingly, it has yielded more revenues for McDonald's than its regular stores in some markets. McCafes are housed inside regular McDonald's in India.Jatia said he has earmarked an investment of Rs 750 crore to open around 200 new restaurants in five years. His company Westlife Development operates McDonald's stores through its subsidiary, <ORG>59899c7a9855b71f847ce555</ORG>. While Westlife reported a 21% increase in revenue for the September quarter led by its restaurant business, McDonald's has been juggling with the dual problem of a sluggish economy and a legal battle with its estranged partner in North India, <PER>59899c7a9855b71f847ce553</PER>, the owner of Connaught Plaza Restaurants.One of the <ORG>59899f999855b71f847fbd12</ORG> restaurants (QSR) to enter the domestic market, McDonald's was ousted from the position of the country's largest QSR player by US pizza maker <ORG>5982d0749855b7221e183a23</ORG> in 2013. Subsequently, it slipped behind its US rival <ORG>5982d09f9855b7221e185d9f</ORG> and now resides in the third position, according to a Euromonitor report from August. The organized QSR business in the country is poised to grow at a CAGR of 25% to reach around Rs 16,800 crore by 2018, Jatia said.
It was not a regular morning at Orchids, a beauty salon in Adyar. Policemen were at the door with sheets of paper in their hands. Even if they have left, it is fine. This is not some enquiry. We have come to tell you that you are safe and we are responsible for your safety, said the policemen, after which a woman spoke to the staff all from <STA>5982d0f09855b7221e18a31f</STA> and Darjeeling - in Nepali and handed over sheets with helpline numbers to them, urging them to report, anytime they received a threat message or felt any danger-like situation.This was one of the confidence building initiatives launched by the city police. Commissioner of <ORG>59899d269855b71f847d8554</ORG> said policemen fluent in Hindi spoke to people from Assam while members of various community associations spoke to people from other States. A manager at Naturals salon said that the situation was more or less under control. Most people are coming back to work after we assured them about safety.RPF officials estimate over 18, 000 people to have left the city in the last five days including people who came to Chennai on their way home.<ORG>5989954d9855b71f847684bc</ORG> Principal <PER>598998349855b71f84790aab</PER> said they are in regular touch with the students and have assured them of all support. <ORG>5982d18c9855b7221e191b3b</ORG> professor <PER>59899fba9855b71f847fdc44</PER> said the students have been counselled so that they are not pressurised to leave. <PER>59899fba9855b71f847fdc47</PER> of <MISC>5982d18c9855b7221e191b3b</MISC>, a native of <STA>5982d0929855b7221e185321</STA> says: We have a good support system here.Some of the students were also angry. Ahum, who hails from Manipur,feels that the ones who left did so because there was no assurance of safety then. Instead of reassuring them, they just added more trains, and encouraged them to leave."Since many reports of alleged attacks in other cities involved Nagas and Mizos, people from both the communities have fled the city.<PER>5982d1289855b7221e18cdf8</PER>, president of the <ORG>598999d39855b71f847a8c78</ORG> said though the situation has stabilised now.
<ORG>5982d20a9855b7221e198a39</ORG>, a joint venture between <ORG>5982d2199855b7221e1997fa</ORG> (50.1 per cent) and <ORG>5982d07b9855b7221e183fa9</ORG> (49.9 per cent), has reported a 19 per cent increase in its net profit to Rs.151 crore for the year ended March 31, 2014, from Rs.126 crore in the same period previous year.Home loan disbursements for the year went up 13 per cent to Rs.1,740 crore (Rs. 1,543 crore). Non-housing loan disbursements (financing against mortgaged house properties), however, dropped by 27 per cent to Rs.753 crore (Rs.1,029 crore). Since the company consciously decided to go slow on the non-housing loans business, the overall disbursements were down by three per cent to Rs.2,493 crore (Rs.2,572 crore).The net non-performing asset (NPA), as on March 31, 2014, stood at 0.46 per cent, up from 0.23 per cent. The companys net worth stood at Rs.698 crore as on March 31, 2014.Challenging yearAddressing a press conference here on Tuesday, <PER>598996259855b71f8477264b</PER>, Managing Director, Sundaram BNP Paribas Home Finance, said, it has been quite a challenging year for us.The 13 per cent growth in home loans disbursements in challenging market conditions were driven by our strong presence in various locations in the south market, and the increased investment in manpower, he added. The company, he said, was looking at a 10 per cent growth this year.Fielding a range of questions, he said the two shareholders had brought in Rs.80 crore through equity in March this year. They had invested Rs.100 crore in the previous financial year.To a question, he said Sundaram Home Finance would raise Rs.3,800 crore this year, including about Rs.1,400 crore through non-convertible debentures and Rs.670 crore through issue of commercial paper. It would access NHB (<ORG>5982d07b9855b7221e183f53</ORG>), sub-ordinate debt and term-loans to raise the remaining fund needs, he added.We can access <ORG>5982d06b9855b7221e1832a0</ORG> (external commercial borrowings) from this year onwards. The company could look at ECB route to fund-raising. This will, however, depend on the exchange rate fluctuation, he said.The choice of ECB would be driven by overall cost of funding, he added.To a specific query, he said the company could look at financing builders by the end of this year. To a question, he said delays in approval and lack of an organised funding window for builders were the two main challenges facing the sector.
<ORG>5982d20a9855b7221e198a39</ORG>, a joint venture between <ORG>5982d2199855b7221e1997fa</ORG> (50.1 per cent) and <ORG>5982d07b9855b7221e183fa9</ORG> (49.9 per cent), has reported a 19 per cent increase in its net profit to Rs.151 crore for the year ended March 31, 2014, from Rs.126 crore in the same period previous year.Home loan disbursements for the year went up 13 per cent to Rs.1,740 crore (Rs. 1,543 crore). Non-housing loan disbursements (financing against mortgaged house properties), however, dropped by 27 per cent to Rs.753 crore (Rs.1,029 crore). Since the company consciously decided to go slow on the non-housing loans business, the overall disbursements were down by three per cent to Rs.2,493 crore (Rs.2,572 crore).The net non-performing asset (NPA), as on March 31, 2014, stood at 0.46 per cent, up from 0.23 per cent. The companys net worth stood at Rs.698 crore as on March 31, 2014.Challenging yearAddressing a press conference here on Tuesday, <PER>598996259855b71f8477264b</PER>, Managing Director, Sundaram BNP Paribas Home Finance, said, it has been quite a challenging year for us.The 13 per cent growth in home loans disbursements in challenging market conditions were driven by our strong presence in various locations in the south market, and the increased investment in manpower, he added. The company, he said, was looking at a 10 per cent growth this year.Fielding a range of questions, he said the two shareholders had brought in Rs.80 crore through equity in March this year. They had invested Rs.100 crore in the previous financial year.To a question, he said Sundaram Home Finance would raise Rs.3,800 crore this year, including about Rs.1,400 crore through non-convertible debentures and Rs.670 crore through issue of commercial paper. It would access NHB (<ORG>5982d07b9855b7221e183f53</ORG>), sub-ordinate debt and term-loans to raise the remaining fund needs, he added.We can access <ORG>5982d06b9855b7221e1832a0</ORG> (external commercial borrowings) from this year onwards. The company could look at ECB route to fund-raising. This will, however, depend on the exchange rate fluctuation, he said.The choice of ECB would be driven by overall cost of funding, he added.To a specific query, he said the company could look at financing builders by the end of this year. To a question, he said delays in approval and lack of an organised funding window for builders were the two main challenges facing the sector.
AHMEDABAD: A green hurdle seems to have hit construction activity around Thol lake. The <ORG>59899b209855b71f847bb503</ORG> (Auda), which gives clearance for development in the vicinity of the lake has issued a diktat that is likely to hinder construction activity within the 10-km radius of Thol.Auda's orders follow a state government's general resolution (GR) issued last month regarding construction activity around eco-sensitive zones.The <ORG>5982d0669855b7221e182e87</ORG> had in 2002 issued an order directing state governments to identify eco sensitive zones in their respective regions and stall all non-forest activity in these areas. As per the new resolution, all construction and development activity within the 10-km radius of an eco-sensitive zone - an animal or bird sanctuary or wetland - could be carried out only after clearance from Standing Committee of <ORG>598994f79855b71f8476433d</ORG> for Wildlife.The resolution will hit development in more than 70 villages around Thol where around Rs 30,000-crore worth of projects have been launched in the last five years."We respect the Supreme Court directives to preserve wildlife sanctuaries. But, we would like the government to simplify land acquisition and environmental clearance procedures. Else, development would suffer," says <PER>59899df89855b71f847e3b75</PER>, vice-president, <ORG>5982d0689855b7221e182ff9</ORG>' Associations of India (Credai).However, there seems to be ambiguity as to which state government agency will monitor illegal construction. When contacted senior Auda officials said that clarity on the issue will come only after consultations with concerned state government departments. The new resolution says developers who had taken permission for construction and development activity after 2008 will have to once again apply for permission with the union environment ministry.
The automotive industry has set up an electronic platform AutoDX to help manufacturers and suppliers exchange industry data, which would save their processing, cost and time.AutoDX would be formally launched during the Auto Expo 2014, which is starting on Wednesday, <ORG>598996dd9855b71f8477be91</ORG> (ACMA) President <PER>5989a07e9855b71f84809454</PER> said. The <ORG>5982d0949855b7221e185496</ORG> and ACMA have jointly developed the platform.  PTI
